<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/baby-tips.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/diaper-bag-essentials-checklist</id>
    <published>2021-02-19T14:00:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-10T23:45:04-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/diaper-bag-essentials-checklist"/>
    <title>Diaper Bag Essentials Checklist</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Is your diaper bag overflowing? Simplify your life with these great tips on organizing your diaper bag and packing it with just the essentials.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/diaper-bag-essentials-checklist">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Being on the go with baby is hard enough. Tack on an overflowing, disorganized diaper bag, and you have the perfect recipe for frustration. Whether you’ve got a nursing newborn or a teething toddler on your hands, having the right supplies can help you be the ultimate </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">mobile mom</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking to clean up the inside of your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-diaper-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, check out these handy tips to stay prim, proper, and—most importantly—</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">prepared</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Read on for the ultimate diaper bag checklist!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Do You Really Need in a Diaper Bag?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The difference between a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">terribly</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> stressful day and a breezy one can often come down to a well-packed diaper bag. When you’re toting around the ultimate baby essentials, you’ll be prepared for even the fastest curveballs life (and your little one) can throw at you.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To that end, here’s the ultimate diaper bag checklist that every mom needs:</span></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diaper-related essentials</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They’re called diaper bags</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for a reason. And although your diaper bag will probably end up doubling as a purse for the foreseeable future, that doesn’t take away from its </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">original purpose</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are the basic diaper bag essentials every mom needs:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Extra diapers</strong> – This one may seem like a no-brainer—but you’d be surprised by just how <i>many</i> diapers babies will go through in a day. Moms should expect to change their newborn’s diaper up to 12 times a day (and closer to 8 times a day for older babies).<sup>1</sup> The perfect diaper bag will have enough compartments for all the extra diapers you need, and prevent a diaper tornado from brewing inside. </li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Wipes</strong> – A full pack of wipes is another essential for quick changes. All the diapers in the world won’t be much help if you don’t have a baby wipe for your baby’s bottom.<br><br>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Changing mat</strong> – Depending on where you’re going, there may not always be a changing table available. That’s why many moms opt for a portable changing mat—like our <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-portable-changing-pad?variant=34521778880648" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel changing pad</span></a>. This padded, easy-to-clean material will quickly become your diaper bag must-have, and the changing pad even has additional pockets for diapers and wipes (in case your bag is running out of space).<br><br>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Rash ointment</strong> – Even the quickest diaper change can’t always prevent a dreaded diaper rash. Fortunately, a small tube of diaper cream or rash ointment can go a long way—<i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">without </span></i>taking up much space in your diaper bag. </li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>A change of clothes</strong> – As much as we’d love for accidents to stay within the confines of your baby’s diaper, this isn’t always the case. On particularly messy days, it never hurts to have an extra outfit in your diaper bag, <i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">just in case. </span></i>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your baby may not have a cell phone yet, but that doesn’t stop nature from calling. And when nature calls while you’re out and about, having all the necessary supplies will make a quick clean up possible. </span></p>
<h3><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" title="baby travel bags"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/BEIS_CTA3.png?v=1617301804" alt="" width="450" height="225"></span></a></h3>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Non-diaper essentials</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that we have the basics covered, it’s time to delve into the more creative items. In addition to ointment and wipes, your diaper bag can carry all the little things that make mom life easier. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here’s a checklist of </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">non-diaper</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> diaper bag essentials for newborns and toddlers:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Pacifier <span style="font-weight: 400;">– If your baby is teething, it’s always good to keep something soothing on hand for their pain. Pacifiers are small, inexpensive, and won’t take up much space—and the BÉIS diaper bag even comes with a pacifier slot </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> an attached teething ring (for gum-related emergencies). </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Bottles and snacks <span style="font-weight: 400;">– When your baby is hungry, they let you know right away. It doesn’t matter what time of the day it is, the munchies are the munchies (or </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">sippies</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, if they’re still on the bottle). You’ll want to make sure you’ve picked out a diaper bag with enough room for any</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> baby food </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">or feeding gear, like pumps, bottles, and milk bags. Nursing moms who want to stay extra organized can opt for our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-bottle-cooler" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">bottle cooler</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">—a sleek, insulated bag that holds up to two bottles at a time. Simply slide this bad boy in your diaper bag and you’ll be ready to go. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Toys <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Who said your diaper bag can’t be fun? While it’s probably never going to look like Santa’s toy sack, having a few entertainment options on hand never hurts. Pack away at least one small toy—like a stuffed animal or a rattle—for emergency cases of boredom. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Seasonal necessities <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Depending on the time of year, your diaper bag may benefit from a few seasonal necessities to keep your baby safe and comfortable. In the summer, you’ll want to pop a cute little hat and some baby-safe sunscreen in your bag. For chilly winter days, an extra </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">swaddle</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> blanket and mittens will always come in handy.</span>
</li>
</b><br>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/COPY_IMAGE_1.jpg?v=1616791608" alt="Cute afro-american toddler wearing his diaper bag on his back and funny. too big dad’s shoes on his feet" style="float: none;"></div>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;"></span></h2>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Keep a Diaper Bag Organized</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">what</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to put in your diaper bag, it’s time to learn </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">how</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to pack it properly for maximum effectiveness. Having all the essentials will only be so helpful if you’re still struggling to find them.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Here are </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">some of the best tips to utilize when packing a neat, organized </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> diaper bag:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Have Ziploc bags on hand <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Sometimes you’ve got a dirty diaper on your hands, and simply no place to put it. The last thing you want</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are soiled diapers</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> staining the lining of your bag (or, even worse, wafting out an unpleasant smell). That’s where </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">a</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Ziploc</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bag </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">comes in handy. Keeping a few disposable, resealable bags can save you when a trash can simply isn’t within reach. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Pick a side <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Your diaper bag isn’t just for baby belongings. Your stuff should fit too. But having two people’s belongings in the mix can sometimes lead to confusion. In order to avoid pulling out lipstick when you were looking for a pacifier, designate one side of your bag to personal items. Searching for your wallet will be a lot easier when it's not lodged in the same pocket as the extra diapers!</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Pockets, pockets, <i>pockets</i> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– If it wasn’t clear, pockets are crucial. When you’re lugging around everything under the kitchen sink, it’s important to have enough places to put your stuff. Fortunately, all of the BÉIS baby collection bags come with pockets galore! Moms can stay organized with ease by having separate pouches for wipes, bottles, toys, and even a handy laptop sleeve (after all, having a baby doesn’t mean you can’t send a quick work email). </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS even carries a diaper bag backpack loaded with pockets as well as a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-tote-insert" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper bag organizer insert</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for your tote! </span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Is a Diaper Bag Really Necessary?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a new mom, your diaper bag is likely going to replace your purse. When you’re <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/6-tips-for-traveling-with-toddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">traveling with </a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/6-tips-for-traveling-with-toddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">toddlers</a>, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">the load becomes a lot heavier than your wallet, keys, and an extra lip</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> balm</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Babies come with a whole bunch of needed supplies. From feeding to changing (and everything that happens in between) you’ll need a new tool every hour. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is why it’s so important to have a sturdy, spacious diaper bag—but the traditional one-size-fits-all bag isn’t for everyone. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÉIS, we’ve created a lineup of baby bags that fit any mom’s style. From small totes to large bags, and even stylish <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">backpacks</a>, you have options when it comes to your diaper bag. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bottom line? You’re going to need </span><b>something</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Might as well make it fashionable too.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/COPY_IMAGE_2.jpg?v=1616791828" alt="Dad holding smiling baby on the bed next to a diaper bag" style="float: none;"></div>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;"></span></h2>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Age Do You Stop Using a Diaper Bag?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A diaper bag typically stops being necessary when your baby is no longer in diapers. Most kids start using the toilet between 18 and 24 months, but some may take up to three years to leave diapers behind fully.<sup>2</sup></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With that in mind, it’s important to note that many moms end up </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">liking </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">their diaper bags. Even after your baby has mastered the art of potty training, there’s still plenty of items you’ll be hauling around, like even </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">bigger</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> toys and clothes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Put simply, everyone is different. While some moms may ditch the diaper bag as soon as possible, others choose to stick with the big-bag lifestyle. It’s really up to you!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br></span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS: The Diaper Bag You’ll Want to Keep Using</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking for a diaper bag that’s both utilitarian </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> stylish, look no further than BÉIS. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our baby collection is designed to make busy moms feel fashionable, even when they’re lugging around a value pack of Huggies. Choose from a variety of designs, like our Backpack Diaper Bag, Pumping Tote, and even a portable Stroller Caddy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No matter what’s on your diaper bag checklist, you can carry it in style with BÉIS!</span></p>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<i>“How to change your baby's nappy“</i>, NHS, <a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/baby/caring-for-a-newborn/how-to-change-your-babys-nappy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL<br><br></a>
</li>
<li>“Potty Training: How to Get the Job Done.” <i>Mayo Clinic</i>, Mayo Foundation for Medical Education and Research, 5 Oct. 2019, <a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/infant-and-toddler-health/in-depth/potty-training/art-20045230" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL<br><br></a>
</li>
<li>“What to Pack in Your Diaper Bag.” <i>Pampers</i>, <a href="https://www.pampers.com/en-us/newborn-baby/care/article/diaper-bag-checklist" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a>
</li>
</ol>
<ol></ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-organize-a-diaper-bag</id>
    <published>2020-12-18T12:52:40-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:54:45-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-organize-a-diaper-bag"/>
    <title>How To Organize a Diaper Bag</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">New mommy problems? At the top of the list is an unorganized diaper bag. Check our guide for how to organize a diaper bag here.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-organize-a-diaper-bag">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ultimate parenting accessory. The box of treasures every new mom relies on for the many, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">many</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> items your baby needs. We’re talking, of course, about the diaper bag.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you spend a good chunk of your time with a newborn, it’s likely that you’ll be trading in clutches and wristlets for something with a little more space (and a lot more diapers). New mothers often find their <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/diaper-bags%20">diaper bag</a> turning into their everyday purse, and why not? With so many </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">interior</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> pockets, it’s a no brainer that you’d use it to carry both <a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">diaper bag essentials</a> and personal goodies (who says rash cream and lip gloss can’t be side-by-side?). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re a newcomer to the diaper bag lifestyle, you may be looking for some advice on making the transition from cross-body bag to cross-</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby</span></i> <span style="font-weight: 400;">bag. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, BÉIS has you covered in this department. Read on for everything you need to know about how to organize a diaper bag like a pro.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do You Really Need a Diaper Bag?</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/copyimage1_872224a0-9f4f-4728-9b09-437d22e29db5.jpg?v=1608324358" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Does a fish really need water?</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It can feel next to impossible to forge the land of motherhood without a reliable diaper bag. This is especially true for moms with busy schedules. When you’re constantly on the move, it’s going to be tough to keep up with the baby’s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">dirty </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">s</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> when you’re miles away from the comfort of home (and the fancy changing table your aunt picked out from your baby shower registry).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As much as you love staying home with your baby all day, it’s just not practical for most moms. That’s why the right </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper bag essentials</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are going to be a crucial part of mobile motherhood (because as wonderful as your pride and joy may be, no baby is capable of holding it in when nature calls!).</span></p>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Yes, you need a diaper bag—one that fits your lifestyle. </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Should You Put in a Diaper Bag?</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/copyimage2_8a89b113-f639-4fe3-bdb6-f2d2a2f6fa86.jpg?v=1608324392" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now it’s time to figure out what to put in </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">your baby <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/tote-bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tote bag</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. While it might be called a </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bag, it’s really more like your “everything” bag. Aside from your own personal items, there are a few key things you’ll want to make sure you’ve packed each time you leave the house. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below is a foolproof diaper bag checklist that will have you prepared for any baby bumps in the road:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Diapers galore </span><span>– The amount of diapers you pack will usually vary depending on where you’re going. With that in mind, it’s always good to keep </span><i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">some</span></i><span> diapers on hand no matter the situation. On average, most babies need a diaper change every two hours or so. If you keep a solid stash on hand that will last several days, you should be good to go.<br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<b>Soothing rash cream</b><span> – Diaper rash loves popping up at the worst moments, especially when you’re traveling. A long car ride can quickly turn your destination into Rash City, USA. The trick to keeping this </span><i><span>literal</span></i><span> pain in the butt at bay? Always packing rash cream in your diaper bag. Keep a travel-sized tube on hand for fast relief at any time (and to avoid a tear-filled car ride home).<br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<b>Extra clothes</b><span> – Diapers are great—but they’re not exactly an impenetrable force field. Sometimes little accidents can turn into </span><i><span>big </span></i><span>messes. Instead of having to run home every time a diaper fails to do its job, keep an extra change of baby clothes tucked away in your bag! This emergency outfit will save you in times of deep </span><i><span>you know what</span></i><span>—plus, who doesn’t love a mid-day outfit change once in a while? </span><i><span>Work it, baby!<br><br></span></i>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Yummy snacks </span><span>– Your diaper bag isn’t limited to just—well—</span><i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper</span></i><span>-related things. You’ll want to utilize the zippered pouches as much as possible by packing everything your baby might need throughout the day. A heavy weight item on this list? Snacks, snacks, and more snacks. Obviously, if your baby is still on milk or formula, snacks won’t be necessary just yet. However, if you know your little one tends to get the afternoon munchies, it’s best to prepare for this by throwing a few non-perishable num nums into your diaper bag. And hey, worst case scenario, </span><i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">you</span></i><span> get to eat the snacks if they don’t want them. It’s pretty much a win-win with this one!</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What If Your Bag Can’t Hold Everything?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For larger items that won’t quite fit in your diaper bag, you may need some extra support. Some common examples of additional bags that help carry the rest of your baby load include:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Breast pump bag <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Nursing can be a complicated process, and it typically comes with its own set of must-haves. If all your pumping gadgets and gizmos are infringing on your diaper space, opt for a breast pump bag as well. This will give you a place to store shields, tubing, and even some extra milk bags and bottles </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">for <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/4-tips-for-breast-pumping-on-the-go" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">breast pumping on the go</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Personal tote <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Sometimes you don’t want to share. It’s totally normal to bring along your own purse, separate from the diaper bag. If you’re willing to carry both, this can help keep your belongings more organized. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Lunch box <span style="font-weight: 400;">– If you want to bring some cold treats on your outing, a lunchbox is a great option for packing snacks. An insulated lunchbox can also double as a cooler for bottles of milk or formula!</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Diaper bag backpack <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Is a backpack more your style? We’ve got you covered. The BÉIS </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-diaper-bag?_pos=1&amp;_sid=61272aebe&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">backpack diaper bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is a great option for moms who want a more hands-free changing experience. With tons of pockets, adjustable straps, and even an odor-proof pouch for when there’s no trash can in sight for that dirty diaper. This backpack even has pouches for a pacifier and two extra baby bottles, all tucked away in a sleek, stylish design.</span>
</li>
</b><br>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> While diapers, wipes, and cream are the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper bag</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> essentials, plenty of moms opt for extras, like snacks and clothes. If your diaper pack is getting full, a second bag may be helpful!</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/4_5f4466bb-02df-479c-8b30-6beb9ac1b868.png?v=1619031859" alt="shop beis baby" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Do You Make Diaper Changes Easier On-The-Go?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mastering the art of the quick diaper change is a skill that takes practice—but some handy tips and tools don’t hurt either. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you’re out and about with your baby, you want to be prepared for any diaper-related emergencies. These </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby travel essentials</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can help step up your mom-game, no matter where life takes you.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Portable Changing Pad</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let’s be real, most moms can turn any surface into a changing table (in a pinch). Unfortunately, spur of the moment diaper changes can lead to some awkward conversations when you’re in public—like when the restaurant manager reminds you that the table is for eating, not changing. Of course there’s always the public restroom changing tables, but you can never be sure when those were last sanitized—plus, not every destination will even </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">have</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a restroom.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That’s where the BÉIS </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-portable-changing-pad" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Portable Changing Pad</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> comes in handy. With this lightweight pad you’ll be able to whip up a comfortable diaper change no matter where you are. It has a wide layout that gives your baby plenty of room to roll and squirm (though you’d probably prefer they didn’t), and even a built-in pouch for wipes! The best part? It rolls up into a stylish wristlet that can be carried inside your organized diaper bag or on its own.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diaper Bag Organizer</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you’re short on time, the last thing you want is to be rummaging around for lost items (like how pacifiers always seem to disappear when you need them the </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">most</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">). If you’ve opted to transform your regular purse into a diaper bag, you’ll need a way to keep things organized. After all, most bags aren’t built for baby essentials. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The question is, how does one keep their bag neat when there’s so many things in it? Enter: a tote insert! The BÉIS <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-tote-insert" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Diaper Bag Organizer</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is the perfect solution for moms who want organization, without sacrificing style. Multiple pockets provide the space you need for all your baby’s accessories, both large and small. The insert even comes with a laptop sleeve for the mom who needs to take business on the go. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking to pair down to a single bag, the tote insert is a great way to make your go-to purse more versatile and baby-friendly!</span></p>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Public diaper changes will go smoother with the right tools. A portable changing pad and bag organizer can lighten your load without leaving you ill-equipped.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elevate Your Diaper Game with BÉIS</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To all the moms who believe style and baby wipes </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">can</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> coexist, BÉIS couldn’t agree with you more!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our wide selection of diaper bags, backpacks, and organizing accessories will have you ready to take on even the toughest changing moments—and look good while doing it. With the right gear, and these packing-savvy tips, you’ll be on your way to having the ultimate changing setup.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just remember to pack extra diapers, wipes, and </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">of course,</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> snacks (for you and your little one). You’ve got this in the bag, mama! </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Literally</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<br>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Munchkin. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing Diaper Bag. </span></i><a href="https://www.munchkin.com/blog/packing-diaper-bag/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.munchkin.com/blog/packing-diaper-bag/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Babycenter. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diaper Bag Checklist: What to Put In Your Diaper Bag. </span></i><a href="https://www.babycenter.com/baby-products/diapering-essentials/checklist-what-to-put-in-your-diaper-bag_40007214" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.babycenter.com/baby-products/diapering-essentials/checklist-what-to-put-in-your-diaper-bag_40007214</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/4-tips-for-breast-pumping-on-the-go</id>
    <published>2020-12-17T04:00:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T12:11:15-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/4-tips-for-breast-pumping-on-the-go"/>
    <title>4 Tips For Breast Pumping On the Go</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">We see you Mama! Life can get pretty hectic with a new baby and a busy schedule. Learn how to tackle it all with these 4 easy tips.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/4-tips-for-breast-pumping-on-the-go">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Moms seem to do it all. From globetrotting to breastfeeding, life can get pretty hectic when you have a new baby and a packed calendar. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you first start breastfeeding in the privacy of your home, it might not be</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> too</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> complicated. However, this simplicity often disappears once you start pumping. Between the pads and the tubing, plus more bottles that need to be cleaned than you thought possible—breast pumping can be a pretty intricate part of motherhood. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not to mention pumping in public, while completely normal, is a new hurdle to cross (although a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-pumping-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">breast pump bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can make your life a whole lot easier.)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With a busy schedule and places to be, new moms may feel overwhelmed by this feeding strategy. Don’t worry, this is completely natural. That’s why we put together these four tips, so you can become an expert at breast pumping on the go!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#1 How Do You Pump Breast Milk On the Go?</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/copyimage1.jpg?v=1608323353" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first of these breastfeeding tips for new moms will cover the basics—how </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">do</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> you pump breast milk when you’re out and about? The best way to facilitate your mobile pumping is by investing in some handy </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">portable pump </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">accessories, such as:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Nursing bra <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Many new moms ditch their uncomfortable underwire for the ease of a nursing</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">bra. Why is a nursing bra such a lifesaver for new moms? First and foremost, they have cups that flip down for easy access without taking off your whole bra. Secondly, the material of a nursing bra will keep you comfortable even on your heaviest pumping days. Any mom on the go will find that pumping is much more portable with the right undergarments.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Pumping bra <span style="font-weight: 400;">– A pumping bra is a little different from a nursing bra. This type of bra is equipped with holes on the cups. Your pump can be hooked up to these holes to extract </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">milk </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">supply </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">without revealing your breast at all. This is a great alternative for </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">pumping </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">moms who want as much privacy as possible when pumping publicly—though they can be a bit more challenging to wear under regular clothing.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Manual pump <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Electric pumps are great, especially when your arms are tired from holding the baby all day (are newborns </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">supposed</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to be this heavy?). The downside to these gadgets, however, is that they aren’t very portable. From dying batteries to tangled charging cords, an electric pump won’t always work when you’re out on the town. As a backup, it’s always good to bring a manual pump when traveling. Though they may be a bit harder on your hands, they’re reliable and easily transported.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Portable cooler <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Does your fridge have more </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">milk supply </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">bottles than it does condiments? Or did you opt for a separate, mini-fridge that’s just for breast milk? Either way, these handy appliances can’t exactly hit the road with you. That’s where a portable cooler comes in handy. For maximum mobility, you’ll want to pick up something that’s lightweight and insulated—more of a lunchbox than an icebox. This will give you a cool place to store milk when you’re not home.</span>
</li>
</b><br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This list isn’t exhaustive. There are </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">tons</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of helpful tools that breastfeeding moms can utilize. If you’re looking to step up your pumping game, don’t be afraid to browse for new accessories. Plus, who </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">really</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> needs an excuse to do some online shopping?</span></p>
<br>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Pumping on the go isn’t always easy. Having the right tools can make a dramatic difference and offer you peace of mind.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#2 Is it Illegal to Pump in Public?</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/copyimage2.jpg?v=1608323423" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breastfeeding and pumping are subject to a ton of needless taboo. Something so natural has no place in lawmaking—yet many rules and restrictions still stand in the way of normalizing nursing. Breast pumping mothers want to do what’s best for their child, without receiving a scolding in public (we know, talk about </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">ridiculous</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To that end, here’s what you need to know about pumping laws:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Public breastfeeding <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Since 1999, federal law has allowed mothers to publicly breastfeed in all fifty states, Washington D.C., the U.S. Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico. The specifics of breast </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">pumping,</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on the other hand, is more of a gray area. Most states have laws that protect breastfeeding activities from being considered “public indecency,” but researching the laws for your own state will help you avoid any issues. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Spaces for pumping <span style="font-weight: 400;">– The Fairness for Breastfeeding Mothers Act of 2019 requires many public spaces to offer clean, private areas for new mothers to nurse or pump. These facilities include workplaces, federal buildings, airports, and more. Lactation rooms must be separate from the restroom, and provide a place for mothers to sit comfortably. So, if you’re ever in doubt of whether or not pumping is allowed, always check to see if there’s a designated space for it.</span>
</li>
</b><br>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Breastfeeding in public is legal—though there are some questions surrounding </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">public pumping </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">session</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. If you’re feeling uncomfortable, many public places offer lactation rooms where new mothers can pump safely.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/4_5f4466bb-02df-479c-8b30-6beb9ac1b868.png?v=1619031859" alt="shop beis baby" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h2>#3 Can I Take My Breast Pump On a Plane?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If there’s anyone that gets a little break from the strict TSA guidelines—it’s moms.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New moms have a lot on their plate, and even more in their <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/diaper-bags%20">diaper </a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/diaper-bags%20">bag</a>.  </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make sure you are on top of <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-organize-a-diaper-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">how to organize a diaper bag</a>. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, there’s flexibility with packing when you and your little one are on the go. The following items can be carried onto your flight without causing any security issues (because who has time for a pat down when you’re carrying a </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">):</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breast pumps</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 3.4 ounces of breastmilk </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">in a milk bag</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Larger quantities of milk (that won’t fit in a quart sized </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">milk </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">bag)</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A baby bottle cooler for milk storage</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best tips when it comes to flying with breast pumping gear is to let the TSA agents know beforehand. This will allow for a speedier process and less holdup of the line. Bottles can either be removed from your bag and screened separately, or the entire cooler bag can be sent through the x-ray machine. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In some cases, security agents may request your permission to open the bottles and inspect their contents. In such a situation, you do have the option to forgo this step and opt for an alternative screening process (though this will be more thorough and take longer). It’s also perfectly legal to travel with larger amounts of breast milk, even if your child is not with you. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A breast pump—and all its accessories—are considered medical devices and will always be allowed on a plane. During your flight, you’ll be allowed to grab the pump from your carry on and get to work! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because—let’s be honest—breast milk doesn’t wait for the seatbelt sign to turn off.</span></p>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Breastfeeding moms shouldn’t have fear of flying! Pumps, bottles, and other </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can be packed directly in your carry on.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#4 How Do I Pack My Pump Bag?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the O.K. to fly and a booked ticket, only one question remains: What do you carry in your breast pump bag?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing as a new mom can be tough. Whether you’re flying across the country, or simply driving to the store—the gear you need to bring can feel like you’re preparing to climb Mount Everest. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best way to break down this intimidating task? </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take it one step at a time</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<b>
<li>Step 1 <span style="font-weight: 400;">– First, you’ll want to pack the essentials. This includes your breast pump</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and any pieces that attach to it. These may include the breast shields, tubes and valves, and any electric parts if applicable. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Step 2 <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Once you’ve finished pumping, you’ll need a place to store the milk. This is where bags and bottles come in handy. The number of containers you bring will depend on how long you’ll be out, but most nursing mothers find that pumping every 2-3 hours does the trick. Storing milk in ziplock bags may save space, but pumping into bottles can save time later—the choice is up to you!</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Step 3 <span style="font-weight: 400;">– The last step to packing your pump bag will focus on the extras. While carrying around </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">more</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> stuff may not sound appealing, you’d be surprised what a difference the right items can make in terms of comfort. For example, a nursing towel can provide privacy in a pinch and help absorb stray milk droplets to prevent stains on your clothes. Wipes and disinfectants will also come in handy for quicker cleanup after a pumping session. Basically, anything that will help you get back on the move with greater efficiency may be worth packing in your pumping bag!<br><br></span>
</li>
</b>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New moms will need to leave a little extra time when packing. As much as we love our babies, you have to accept that they come with a lot of baggage—</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">literally</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Those little cheeks make it </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">all</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> worth it.</span></p>
<p><b><i>The Bottom Line:</i></b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Pack the basics as well as a few extras to make mobile pumping more comfortable. </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make Portable Pumping Stylish with BÉIS</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling doesn’t have to be impossible, even when you’re on a strict pumping schedule. And when you pack with BÉIS, it doesn’t have to be void of style either thanks to these breast pumping tips and tricks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our signature </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-pumping-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">pump bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is the perfect combination of style and utility. With pockets for your personal items, breast pump parts, pumping accessories, a laptop sleeve for working moms, and even water-resistant lining—this sleek breast pump <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/tote-bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tote bag</a> has everything you need.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make life as a pumping mom a whole lot easier with the BÉIS Pumping Bag! Now log off girl, you’ve got a flight to catch.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Mom Loves Best. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pumping on the Go: How to Breast Pump in Public. </span></i><a href="https://momlovesbest.com/feeding/breast-pumps/pumping-in-public" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://momlovesbest.com/feeding/breast-pumps/pumping-in-public</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Exclusive Pumping. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Pack Your Breast Pump Bag When You’re Going Back to Work. </span></i><a href="https://exclusivepumping.com/how-to-pack-your-breast-pump-bag/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://exclusivepumping.com/how-to-pack-your-breast-pump-bag/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Kindred Bravely. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nursing Bras 101: A Complete Guide for the Breastfeeding Mom. </span></i><a href="https://www.kindredbravely.com/blogs/bravely/nursing-bras-101" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.kindredbravely.com/blogs/bravely/nursing-bras-101</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Upgraded Points. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flying with Breast Milk—Everything You Need to Know. </span></i><a href="https://upgradedpoints.com/flying-with-breast-milk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://upgradedpoints.com/flying-with-breast-milk</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">TSA. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling With Children. </span></i><a href="https://www.tsa.gov/travel/special-procedures/traveling-children" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tsa.gov/travel/special-procedures/traveling-children</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Exclusive Pumping. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flying With a Breast Pump and Pumping on a Plane. </span></i><a href="https://exclusivepumping.com/flying-as-an-exclusive-pumper-how-to-pump-on-a-plane-with-your-baby/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://exclusivepumping.com/flying-as-an-exclusive-pumper-how-to-pump-on-a-plane-with-your-baby/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">NCSL. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breastfeeding State Laws</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><a href="https://www.ncsl.org/research/health/breastfeeding-state-laws.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.ncsl.org/research/health/breastfeeding-state-laws.aspx</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs</id>
    <published>2020-10-12T12:06:06-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:53:42-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs"/>
    <title>11 Baby Travel Essentials Every Parent Needs</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling with babies can be stressful and requires prime organization. Wondering what to bring? Read on for a list of baby travel essentials!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>When you’re traveling with a baby, you know there’s a lot out of your control—how your precious bundle will adjust to turbulence, noise, and time changes, for starters. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Besides these unknowns, your goal is to prepare for getting through security, onto your plane, and through your flight with the arsenal of things that keep your baby or little ones calm and happy, from fresh diapers to soothing toys.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The good news? The right </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing checklist </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">can help you avoid that moment of panic when you can't find the specific pacifier </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">in your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/11-baby-travel-essentials-every-parent-needs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that always stops tears in their tracks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below is our list of 11 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby travel essentials</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> must haves that can help you be prepared and organized for your baby's needs so that you can </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">both</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> enjoy your adventure. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black" target="_blank" title="black diaper bag" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/reg_diaper_480x480.jpg?v=1603998883" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#1 Car Seat/Booster Seat</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before you set foot on the plane, you have to make it to the airport. If you aren’t a car-owner, you could try requesting an Uber or Taxi with a baby seat—but wouldn’t you rather have a seat at hand, one with safety specs you know you can trust?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is why an infant car seat is #1 on our list of baby travel essentials.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you already use a convertible stroller with a detachable car bassinet and car seat, you’re all set. However, if your baby spends most of their time strapped to your chest, you’ll want to invest in a lightweight, functional car seat just for your trip to comply with the law and maintain peace of mind.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We like the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.gracobaby.com/car-seats/infant-car-seats/snugride-snuglock-35-lx-featuring-trueshield-technology/SAP_2053220.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Graco SnugRide® SnugLock® 35 LX</a><a href="https://www.gracobaby.com/car-seats/infant-car-seats/snugride-snuglock-35-lx-featuring-trueshield-technology/SAP_2053220.html"> </a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">car seat, which combines several sought-after features:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lightweight</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Easy to install</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Affordable</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keep your little ones safe on their trip to the airport, and cross your fingers that they’ll snooze underneath the canopy of your travel stroller while you pass through security. </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#2 A Functional and Stylish Diaper Bag</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-backpack-diaper-bag" target="_blank" title="black diaper bag backpack" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/backpack_480x480.jpg?v=1603998892" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You already have a go-to diaper bag so that you’re prepared when your baby does their business while you’re over at a friend’s or out shopping. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But is it organized enough for smooth sailing during travel days?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re on the lookout for the best baby travel bags, there’s no better time to buy than before your first big trip with your baby or toddler.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÈIS, we’ve designed 2 types of </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">diaper bags</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">A </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-backpack-diaper-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diaper Bag Backpack</span></a>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">A </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diaper Bag Tote</span></a>
</li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some parents prefer the convenience of being hands free with a backpack, while others prefer the easy access to baby essentials that a tote provides by slipping it down their shoulder. Whatever design best suits your needs, here are some of our favorite features:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Plenty of pockets</b> <b> </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– With dedicated compartments for wipes and diapers as well as a detachable odor-proof pouch for a dirty diaper, it’s easy to store your essentials </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> any waste on-hand (until you can find a trash can). There’s even a pacifier pouch and bottle pocket(s)!</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Different sets of straps </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– An adjustable strap makes it easy to customize your travel bag’s look and functionality. Strap either bag to your baby’s stroller and make changes on-the-go to suit the setting.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<b>
<li>A luggage slip-on panel<span style="font-weight: 400;"> – When you’re traveling, you have your hands full—literally. Slip one of these stylish <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/diaper-bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">diaper bags</a> onto your carry-on luggage, roll, and go.</span>
</li>
</b>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best feature of all? These baby bags for air travel don’t scream “diaper bags.” You’ll feel like you’ve got one of the most stylish baby bags on the whole plane. They’re elegant enough to go wherever you’re going—even a night off from mommy duty.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#3 Portable Changing Organizer</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-portable-changing-pad" target="_blank" title="portable changing organizer" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/portable_480x480.jpg?v=1603998920" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sometimes, it’s easy to find a restroom with a changing table. Other times, you’re unfolding your denim jacket and hoping against all odds that this diaper change won’t result in a permanent stain.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Say goodbye to this concern with a collapsible, liquid-proof, and easy-to-wipe-down </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-portable-changing-pad" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">portable changing pad</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This changing mat is a padded, protected and comfortable mat for your newborn or toddler. It’s compact, lightweight and even has pockets for diapers and wipes to make changing a breeze. That’s why it’s earned a prime spot on our list of best baby travel gear.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#4 Wet Wipes</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Need we say more?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wet wipes are some of the most essential baby travel items out there for cleaning up everything from spills to spit-up. In a pinch, you can stash used wipes in your diaper bag’s odor-proof pouch. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/4_2dd4ee97-85c6-4cdd-b62f-27786366529c.png?v=1623325037" alt="shop beis baby" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#5 Travel Stroller</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You need a stroller to keep your baby cozy as you hit up the attractions on your vacation adventures.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If it’s your first time traveling with an infant, you may be concerned about getting your stroller through security and onto a plane. Thankfully, airline attendants can help your family get through early boarding without a hassle.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the right stroller can make </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">everyone’s</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> life easier.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.besrey.com/home/product/detail.html?name=BR-C705S" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The BABYZEN Yoyo</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is lightweight and collapsible. This lightweight stroller has reached cult status for a reason—it folds and unfolds within instants, and you can even carry it over your shoulder.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With options for newborns and older babies, invest in this </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">lightweight stroller </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">and keep using it as your child grows.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#6 Stroller Caddy</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-stroller-caddy" target="_blank" title="stroller caddy" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/stroller_cad_480x480.jpg?v=1603999151" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keep your essentials at your fingertips with an adjustable stroller caddy. Designed to easily clip on to any stroller with a stroller strap, our <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-stroller-caddy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">stroller caddy</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is incredibly versatile. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">It has an interior pocket designed specifically for bottles and offers spacious mesh compartments for your burp cloth, snacks, a change of clothes, or extra diaper storage.<br></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zippered compartments are a perfect fit for your phone, keys, wallet, and other essentials.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">It comes with an adjustable shoulder strap to carry cross-body.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s never been easier to get off the plane, open your stroller, and keep your essentials at the ready.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#7 Bottle Cooler</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-bottle-cooler" target="_blank" title="bottler cooler" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/bottle_cool_480x480.jpg?v=1603999141" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best way to keep your breast milk safe and your little one</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">content during long and potentially uncomfortable voyages?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have plenty of food on-hand.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you’re breastfeeding or bottle-feeding, having a ready backup supply of food can make it easier to feed your baby when it’s convenient for </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">you</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (i.e., not when you’re waiting in line at passport control).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Enter our stylish </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-bottle-cooler" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">bottle cooler</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This insulated bottle holder is a travel must-have and includes ice packs, making it easy to keep your baby bottle(s) cool.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#8 Silicone Bibs</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The downside of keeping travel snacks at the ready? You know a mess is inevitable, and the last thing you want to do is change your tot’s jumper in a confined space!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bibs are a perennial favorite amongst on the go items for babies. But if you usually use cloth bibs, you probably aren’t looking forward to doing laundry on vacation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ingenious solution? </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">A silicone bib</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you place one of these on your baby, you know their outfit will make it through mealtime and burping.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Use one of those handy wet-wipes to clean off the silicone bib.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then, place it back in your liquid-safe baby diaper bag!</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#9 Sleep Sack</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's almost impossible to predict the temperature on planes. That's why our list of baby flight essentials includes something to keep your</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> little munchkin</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> warm!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you aren’t already using a </span><a href="https://www.halosleep.com/halo-sleepsack-wearable-blanket-100-cotton-blue-wb-cot-blue" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">wearable blanket</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> during nap time, now is a great time to start. A sleep sack is safe for your baby, and inverted zippers make it easy to take the sack on and off for diaper changes and temperature adjustments.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This way, you won’t have to worry about the complexities of swaddling while you deal with everything else on your tray-table! </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#10 Pumping Bag</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-pumping-bag" target="_blank" title="breast pumping bag" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/breastpump_480x480.jpg?v=1603998904" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best baby travel accessories ensure a smooth and comfortable travel experience for baby and mom. That’s why we created a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/the-baby-collection/products/the-pumping-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">pumping bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to make your life that much easier. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transporting your breast pump shouldn't be a hassle and you shouldn't have to sacrifice style for functionality or comfort. Our pumping bag doubles as a work bag with a laptop sleeve and a pocket just for mom. With features like a separate bag for clean and dirty </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">clothes</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, or a water resistant pocket, you can feel confident that your bag will stay clean and all your items will be safe.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">#11 Portable Crib</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond flight essentials for baby, it’s important to think ahead to your hotel. Once you arrive at your destination, you’ll want to start unpacking and get comfortable.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Is that really possible with a hotel crib?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While you can’t bring your whole crib on most trips, a portable crib can create a sleep environment that you can fully trust.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The </span><a href="https://www.babybjorn.com/baby-cradle-and-travel-crib/travel-crib-light/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby Bjorn travel crib</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> earns high marks for the following features:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Comfy mattress</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Highly collapsible</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel bag included</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Deluxe safety features</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breathable material</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We hope this travel crib will let your whole family rest easier.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don’t Forget Your Own Travel Essentials</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, you have the best travel items for baby to ensure your little one has everything they need.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Can you say the same for yourself?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you know, babies are more perceptive than we can imagine. If you’re stressed carrying your brand-new <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-diaper-bag-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">baby bag</a> on top of the janky suitcase you’ve been rolling around since college, it could have an effect on you both.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Likewise, if going through security is </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">extra</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> chaotic while you fumble to find your TSA-approved 3-1-1 liquid bag, it can impact the entire trip.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you're </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/vacation-ideas-tips-for-traveling-with-toddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">traveling with toddlers</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or embarking on a trip with a newborn, you should prepare your </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">own</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> luggage with the same love and care you extend to your little </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">munchkin</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">! So make sure that baby on the go items aren't the only things on your packing list. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take a look at our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing tip</span><b>s</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> so that you can make zipping up your own suitcase a well-organized, calm affair. (And if you don’t have the bandwidth, be sure to ask your partner or a friend for a helping hand.)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That way, you and baby can </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">both</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> get a little R&amp;R when you reach your destination.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Get Organized with BÈIS</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a mom on the go, you have a hundred things to keep organized. You sometimes head out the door, unsure if you actually remembered your passport, keys, wallet, cell phone, deodorant... oh, and your baby!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If style is at the forefront of your mind, then you’ve come to the right place. Our bags make sure you are not only prepared with the essentials, but you’ll look so chic, no one will even know it’s loaded top to bottom with baby diapers, toys, snacks, and more!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÈIS, our goal is to make family travel easy and stylish, whether you’re heading to the grocery store or out on your next family adventure with young kids. Shop our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and baby gear to find the perfect stylish bags for you.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">“What to Pack When Traveling With Baby.” What to Expect, WhattoExpect, 2 July 2018, </span><a href="http://www.whattoexpect.com/first-year/what-to-pack-when-traveling-with-baby/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.whattoexpect.com/first-year/what-to-pack-when-traveling-with-baby<br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lanin, Colleen. “Travel Mamas Packing List for Babies and Toddlers.” Parenting, <a href="www.parenting.com/travel/travel-mamas-packing-list-for-babies-and-toddlers" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.parenting.com/travel/travel-mamas-packing-list-for-babies-and-toddlers</a></span></li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-work-from-home-with-kids-and-stay-organized</id>
    <published>2020-03-25T09:14:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-10T23:15:09-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-work-from-home-with-kids-and-stay-organized"/>
    <title>How To Work From Home With Kids And Stay Organized</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If there’s one thing we know, it’s that everything can change in an instant. Take each moment to appreciate where you’re at during this moment and try to stay open-minded about the future. </span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-work-from-home-with-kids-and-stay-organized">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">﻿This content was updated for accuracy and relevance on October 21st, 2020.</span></em></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Parenting is tough, but so are </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">you. Being a working parent and working from home with kids can be one of the hardest things to balance</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">—</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">especially during this unprecedented time when our society is facing so much uncertainty and fear surrounding the coronavirus outbreak. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No one could have prepared for this situation, and we are all having to quickly adapt to these ever-changing situations. With a rising number of people shifting to work at home instead of heading into the office, our team wanted to share some tips on navigating the current environment and how to transition to a work from home schedule. No matter if you’re new to being a remote worker or you're a seasoned wfh parent, we’re sharing steps to create a healthy, organized work and home balance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read on to learn more about how to work from home with a baby and how to work from home with kids of other ages, while keeping y</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">our life and home organized with our brand-new BÉIS </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" title="Baby Travel Bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">baby travel bags</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. These bags aren’t just for when you’re on the go. They can make your everyday life more organized as well. </span></p>
<h2><b>Set Clear Expectations </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The world is a little crazy right now, and no one knows what to expect. Your kids are no different whether you have older kids or younger kids. That’s why it’s important to set a few expectations and boundaries during this time. Try your best to create some consistency. This starts with creating some ground rules for yourself and your family around dedicated work hours and school work time. Once you have some clear expectations outlined, it’s a good idea to sit down with your kids to briefly explain what is going on to keep everyone in the loop of what’s happening. This creates a better family balance, as everyone will know what to expect during this time.</span></p>
<h2><b>Create a Schedule </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you need to create a work at home mom schedule or dad schedule, , it’s essential to stick to a routine and set the right expectation for your family. When organizing your time and creating your remote work schedule, make sure to consider your kids’ schedules. As schools closures are still in effect for the next few months, you’ll want to carve out some school and learning time balanced with fun activities to keep them busy. When creating a work from home schedule </span><span data-slate-leaf="true">that aligns with your kids </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">remote learning</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> </span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIydGhhdCUyMGFsaWducyUyMHdpdGglMjB5b3VyJTIwa2lkcyUyMHJlbW90ZSUyMGxlYXJuaW5nJTIwc2NoZWR1bGUlMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">schedule</span></span>, write out everyone’s daily responsibilities, stick it on the fridge or somewhere where everyone in the family can refer to it throughout the day. We recommend creating a morning routine, afternoon routine (such as a lunch break or toddler nap) and evening routine (such as bedtime or dinner).</p>
<h2><b>Make a To-Do List</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Start off each workday by writing out a to-do list with tasks you need to accomplish for the day and week. This helps you stay organized of your goals and allows you to keep track of what you still have left on your plate. Plus, nothing beats the feeling of crossing off everything on your list! You can also do this with your kids to plan out activities and things for them to do during the day while you’re working.</span></p>
<h2><b>Minimize Interruptions</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let’s face it</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">—</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">you can plan as much as you want, but things are likely to go a little off track. Be prepared for interruptions throughout your day. Your kids are likely not used to your new schedule, but it’s important to try to minimize distraction as much as possible and not to let these small interruptions completely throw you off your routine. Creating your ideal schedule is the best way to try to combat these distractions and let you focus on getting your job done and create space for your family. </span></p>
<h2><b>Keep Kids Entertained</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When kids have a fun thing to look forward to, they are less likely to interrupt you. Try setting up an activity center so your children can have a specific space for them to do projects and keep busy with activities. You might even want to consider switching out their noisy toys for ones that don’t make any sounds. </span></p>
<div style="padding-left: 60px;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/mom_meme_large.jpg?v=1587571063" alt="" width="358" height="379"></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking for more ideas to keep your kids active throughout the workday, check out this article on </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-keep-kids-busy-and-stay-sane-at-home" title="How To Keep Kids Busy"><span style="font-weight: 400;">how to keep kids busy</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and stay sane at home.</span></p>
<h2><b>Start the Day Early </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rise and shine! It can be tempting to sleep in since you don’t have to worry about commuting to the office, but waking up early is a great way to start the day off right, especially as a busy mom. Instead of rushing to get to your desk and send an email, take the time to set your alarm and make yourself a cup of coffee or tea. This is a great tip for maximizing your workday and getting your kids ready for the day.</span></p>
<h2><b>Separate Spaces in Your House</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When work and home become the same place, it can be tough to figure out a balance between the two. One of the best things to do is to separate </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">work</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> life</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> from </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">home</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> life</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyJTIwd29yayUyMGxpZmUlMjBmcm9tJTIwaG9tZSUyMGxpZmUlMjBpbiUyMGRpZmZlcmVudCUyMHNwYWNlcyUyMiU3RCU1RCUyQyUyMnR5cGUlMjIlM0ElMjJwYXJhZ3JhcGglMjIlN0QlNUQ="> in different spaces</span>. Creating separate spaces in your house helps your brain focus on work mode or family mode and can help boost your productivity. If you have a home office or an empty guest room in the house, now is the time to utilize it. If you don’t have an office to work remotely in, try making a to-do list and leaving it in your workspace to revisit the next day. It’s up to you to decide which spaces are designated for work activities and which are for family.</p>
<h2><b>Take Regular Breaks</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breaks are absolutely ESSENTIAL w</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">hen working from home with kids. This</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> creates a healthy balance while giving you a much-needed mental break from the craziness. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only should you create breaks for your kids as they’re missing out on recess, but you should also make time to give yourself a break just for you (AKA without the kids). This could be as simple as making yourself a latte or heading out on the patio for five minutes to sit and clear your mind during their naptime.</span></p>
<h2><b>Stay Organized</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the midst of chaos, staying organized is not only therapeutic but necessary</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><span data-slate-leaf="true">, which is why we will help you figure out </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">how to stay organized </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">working</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> from </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyJTJDJTIwd2hpY2glMjBpcyUyMHdoeSUyMHdlJTIwd2lsbCUyMGhlbHAlMjB5b3UlMjBmaWd1cmUlMjBvdXQlMjBob3clMjB0byUyMHN0YXklMjBvcmdhbml6ZWQlMjB3b3JraW5nJTIwZnJvbSUyMGhvbWUlMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">home</span></span>. Don’t worry</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">—</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS has you covered with essentials that will help you get organized for every at-home activity. Here are some of our favorite things for life at home, work from home, and working out at home.</span></p>
<ol>
<li><b> Life at Home BÉIS</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Being stuck at home is more relaxing when everything has its place. Use this time to get your things organized, including your makeup collection, jewelry, hot tools and other clutter.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Hanging Jewelry Case</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Are your earrings all over the place and necklaces getting tangled up together? Our <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">jewelry case</a> helps you clearly separate your baubles and store  </span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Cosmetic Case</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: This smartly-designed <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">makeup case</a> expertly organizes your beauty products. Store it under your sink or hang it on the back of your bathroom door, so your beauty and skincare routine is hanging at your fingertips.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Hot Tools Cover</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: A stylish case lined with burn-proof lining. Whether you’re in a rush to get ready at home or you’re on the go you can be sure your kids, your hands, and your clothing are safe from being burned thanks to our <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/flat-iron-cover" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">flat iron cover</a>. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<div style="padding-left: 120px;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case?_pos=1&amp;_sid=b88c73e48&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="hanging jewelry case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/7W9A7183_large.jpg?v=1587571159" alt=""></a></div>
<ol start="2">
<li><b> Work from Home BÉIS</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We ma</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ke working from home with kids look easy </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">with the</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">brand-new BÉIS baby collection. From a chic diaper bag to sleek stroller caddy, we’ve got everything you need to get work done and stay organized with your kids.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Diaper Bag</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: We call this the anti-diaper <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">diaper bag</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">—</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">a bag with enough function to tote around all your baby-mama needs and chic enough that NO ONE will ever suspect you're carrying around a week old dirty diaper.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Bottle Cooler</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: We designed this must-have <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-bottle-cooler" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">baby accessory</a> to keep your babe's bottles at just the right temp, perfect for moms working from home. Ice packs keep things cool until you need to warm them to the babe's liking, while insulated bottles keep cool or warm for several hours</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Perfect for those quick walks around the block between meetings.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Stroller Caddy</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Featuring adjustable straps that snap around the handle of your stroller and shopping cart. This is one of those <a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">stroller bags</a> that is perfect for social distancing approved neighborhood walks and essential grocery store trips.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/work-totes">Work Totes</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Who says working from home can’t be stylish? Now you can store your work essentials all in one super-chic place. Similar to our <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-messenger" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">black messenger bag</a>, This on-the-go <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-black/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">work tote</a> lets you bring your remote work from the couch to the kitchen. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<div style="padding-left: 120px;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-beige" target="_blank" title="beige work tote" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/WorkTote_large.jpg?v=1587571080" alt=""></a></div>
<ol start="3">
<li><b> Workout from Home BÉIS</b></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Working out at home with kids can be just as difficult as working from home. Remember, exercise is an essential part of work-life balance too!</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Water Bottle</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Stay hydrated with a super lightweight <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-water-bottle?_pos=1&amp;_sid=2db96753d&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">water bottle</a>, that also happens to fit perfectly in your BÉIS bag side pockets!</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Duffle Bag</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Store your home workout essentials in one convenient duffle. Designed with extra pockets and compartments with your sweaty athleisure in mind, you can store sneakers and anything else you don’t want smelling up the rest of your <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-duffle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">duffle bag</a> in these compartments.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Cosmetic Pouch Set</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: This simple set of pouches can organize just about anything from your day to day needs to your post-gym essentials, keeping everything zipped up and tidy in two <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-cosmetic-pouch-set-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">compact pouches</a>!</span>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>Get Help If You Need It</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you are in quarantine with a partner at home, don’t be afraid to ask for help when you need it. Practice being open and honest in your daily routine. Communicate if you need assistance with keeping the kids busy or some quiet time to work alone. Just because we have to stay at home, doesn’t mean you can’t get a little help from others and be mindful of your mental health. Make uninterrupted time to schedule virtual meetings on Zoom, Skype, or FaceTime calls with coworkers, friends, a family member, or your therapist.</span></p>
<h2><b>Hang In There</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If there’s one thing we know, it’s that everything can change in an instant. Whether you're a working mom or a working dad, take each moment to appreciate where you’re at during this time and try to stay open-minded about the future. At <a href="http://beistravel.com">BÉIS</a>, one of our favorite healthy habits to bring joy to our days is planning for our next trip. We’ve realized that even though we can’t leave the house right now, creating plans for a trip once this is all over (and buying cute <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage">travel luggage</a> to hold you over) gives us something to look forward to. Try planning for something that brings you and your little ones joy, or looking back at old memories that make you happy. We’re all navigating work life balance during the COVID 19 pandemic together. You will get through this! </span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-keep-kids-busy-and-stay-sane-at-home</id>
    <published>2020-03-12T09:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:55:21-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-keep-kids-busy-and-stay-sane-at-home"/>
    <title>How To Keep Kids Busy And Stay Sane At Home</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let’s talk parent life while we stay at home. Keeping your kids busy and your own sanity during COVID-19 is no easy task. If you found yourself suddenly wonde</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ring how to work from home with kids, it’s safe to say your average day is looking quite different than usual.</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-keep-kids-busy-and-stay-sane-at-home">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><em>This content was updated for accuracy and relevance on October 21st, 2020.</em></p>
<p>Let’s talk parent life while we stay at home. Keeping your kids busy and your own sanity during COVID-19 is no easy task. If you found yourself suddenly wondering <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-work-from-home-with-kids-and-stay-organized" title="How To Work From Home With Kids And Stay Organized">how to work from home with kids</a>, it’s safe to say your average day is looking quite different than usual.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that families are spending a lot more time together, in closer quarters, to avoid the spread of the coronavirus outbreak, it can be tough to figure</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> out how to keep everyone busy at home. But just because we’re all stuck at home, doesn’t mean we have to spend it going stir crazy! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read on for our tips on how to keep kids busy at home while stayin</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">g sane as a working mom or dad at home.</span></p>
<h2><b>Keep a Routine</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just like taking a trip, the best ones start with a good itinerary!  Start by creating an itinerary to give yourself and your kids some structure. Make sure to include your normal everyday indoor activities, including consistent meals, bathing routines, and playtime. Don’t put too much pressure on your routine or stress about filling up every moment of the day. Focus on creating balance and allowing time for rest and transitions between activities and if you off task, just know that’s ok too!</span></p>
<h2><b>Get Organized</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can never be too organized! Take this time to help the little ones organize their closets, rooms, or toys. While they are busy sorting and cleaning you can do the same!  Whether it’s reorganizing your closets - tucking away rarely used items using our packing cubes with easy to read labels, cleaning out your cosmetic drawer, organizing your skincare and makeup items in convenient </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">cases</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">pouches</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or going through your wardrobe to store your winter clothing and pull out your spring &amp; summer clothing. This is a great opportunity for you to get your home organized AF. Put all your <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel accessories</a> to good use instead of letting them collect dust. So go ahead, channel your inner Marie Kondo and get to organizing!</span></p>
<h2><b>Stay Chic &amp; Put-Together</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the best ways to stay sane while you’re stuck at home is to be prepared for all your mom duties, without giving up being chic. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’ve got a little one at home, check out the newest edition to the BÉIS family: the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS <a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">baby travel bags</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. These chic baby bags are our favorite kind of mom fashion. They will keep you organized and make you feel like you have your life together even when you’re going to the grocery store with your hair in a messy bun, chipped nails, and in pajamas that you haven’t taken off in three days. </span></p>
<h2><b>Essentials For Mom: The BÉIS Baby Collection</b></h2>
<ul>
<li>
<span>BÉIS Diaper Bag</span><span>: The <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">diaper bag</a> is what we needed</span><span>—</span><span>a bag that we ALL want to carry. </span>Not only is this bag fit for "<span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">mom</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">style</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">" but it's fit for everyday </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">personal </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">style</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJjaGlsZHJlbiUyMiUzQSU1QiU3QiUyMnRleHQlMjIlM0ElMjJOb3QlMjBvbmx5JTIwZG9lcyUyMHRoaXMlMjBiYWclMjBmaXQlMjB3aXRoJTIwJTVDJTIybW9tJTIwc3R5bGUlNUMlMjIlMjBidXQlMjBpdCUyMGZpdHMlMjB3aXRoJTIwZXZlcnlkYXklMjBwZXJzb25hbCUyMHN0eWxlJTIwdG9vLiUyMCUyMiU3RCU1RCUyQyUyMnR5cGUlMjIlM0ElMjJsaXN0LWl0ZW0lMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIyYnVsbGV0ZWQtbGlzdCUyMiU3RCU1RA=="> too. </span>Featuring endless pocket bliss and all the extras, this bag also includes stroller straps, a changing pad, and a bag for dirty diapers, a pacifier pouch, two bottle pouches, and a teething ring to keep the baby occupied during changes.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Bottle Cooler</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: Baby’s bottles or Mommy’s bottles, no judgment here! This <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-bottle-cooler" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">bottle cooler</a> is insulated to keep bottles cool or warm, along with convenient ice tubes to keep that milk (or whatever you’re sipping on) chilled.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS Stroller Caddy</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">: This bag is a three-in-one baby mama essential. A stroller caddy, an extra organization tool for your Diaper bag, and a way to organize baby’s items in-flight (who else can’t to pack up and take a trip after this is all over?!) This is one of our favorite "mom must haves" and because it's one of the best <a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">stroller bags</a> for keeping all your baby needs organized on your daily walks and even around the house.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p style="padding-left: 90px;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/pages/baby-collection" target="_blank" title="stroller bags" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Walk_around_the_block_1_large.png?v=1587569123" alt=""></span></a></p>
<h2><b>Activities For Kids at Home (Boredom Busters)</b></h2>
<h3><b>1. Open Up the Kitchen</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A great way to keep kids busy throughout the day? Open up your kitchen, grab your cookbooks, and get to cooking! Baking and cooking with the family is a fun way to get the kids involved. Grab a high chair for babies, get some pots, pans, and wooden spoons for the younger kids, and recruit older children to explain what you’re making and how it’s done.  Learning new ways to hang out and interact with each other, reading recipes, gathering ingredients, and enjoying the meal you all just created together is a great way for the whole fams to learn some valuable life lessons! </span><span data-slate-leaf="true">We recommend grabbing your </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">food coloring</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> and </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">cookie cutters</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyV2UlMjByZWNvbW1lbmQlMjBncmFiYmluZyUyMHlvdXIlMjBmb29kJTIwY29sb3JpbmclMjBhbmQlMjBjb29raWUlMjBjdXR0ZXJzJTIwdG8lMjBnZXQlMjB0aGUlMjBraWRzJTIwZXhjaXRlZC4lMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE"> to get the kids excited.</span></p>
<h3><b>2. Family Exercise Routines</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Physical activity is a great way for kids to release energy and stay busy. As gyms are closing and sports teams are on hold, families have to think a little more out of the box with at-home workouts. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Check out YouTube for a variety of workout, yoga, and dance ideas you can join in together as a family at home. If you have a backyard or front driveway, this is a great space for kids to run around, jump rope, play games, and stay active.  And of course, there is always packing your baby bags</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and heading out for a walk.</span></p>
<h3><b>3. Clean Up the House </b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Grab your kids and some cleaning supplies! This is a great idea and a great chance for the kids to keep up with their chores. At the same time, this helps you keep your sanctuary clean while creating a relaxing and safe space. Sanitizing is extra essential at this point, so make sure to stress to your kids the importance of keeping countertops and shared areas like doorknobs and light switches clean. Make cleaning time a fun game with rewards and incentives, such as sticker charts or extra screen time.</span></p>
<h3><b>4. Family Game Night</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have older children, consider a family game night to spice up your weeknights! This is a great time to break out your favorite board game, host kid-friendly trivia night, or give charades a shot. Not only will you build connections and memories, but this is a chance for you to start teaching game strategies to your kids.  Putting this family activity on the calendar will also give the whole family something to look forward to. </span></p>
<h3><b>5. Get Crafty with Your Kids</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s time to let your creative juices flowing and start crafting! Explore online or browse Pinterest for a list of ideas of crafts you can set up or do with your child. From homemade playdough and paint to crayons, coloring books, and cardboard crafts, the opportunities to get crafty are endless. Not sure where to start? Check out some of our favorite craft supplies from Popsugar Family[1]</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<h3><b>6. Movie Marathon</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did someone say Disney+ movie marathon? Even if you’re strict when it comes to screen time, everyone should make time to watch a movie together as a family. There are tons of new shows and movies coming to the Disney+ platform this Apri</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">l[2], so you’ll have a variety of options to keep the younger and older kids entertained for the weeks and months to come.  Pop some popcorn, break out the good snacks and candy, and pile on the pillows for this easy indoor activity!</span></p>
<h3><b>7. Build Forts</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A fun way to ‘escape’ your house is through a DIY project to bring to your living room or kid’s bedroom - building a cozy, layered fort! Grab your comfiest pillows, blankets, and sheets and start making a fortress you and your kids can escape to. For an extra magical touch, try adding some twinkly fairy lights and keep them overnight for a fun and exciting makeshift sleepover. Losing yourself in a good book or reading, telling, and sharing stories is always the perfect complement to fort building.</span></p>
<h3><b>8. Video Chat Playdates</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Craving some more social interaction? Use Zoom, Skype, and FaceTime to plan virtual playdates for the kids and give them a chance to chat with family members. Don’t forget to set aside some time for yourself as well to catch up with family, friends, coworkers, or your therapist. Staying social and maintaining relationships is extra important during this time when we can’t physically be together.</span></p>
<h3><b>9. Get Outside</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you have a backyard, patio, balcony, or front porch, take some time every day to get some fresh air outside when possible. You can never underestimate what a good dose of vitamin D can do for your mood &amp; health.  Consider taking a short walk around the neighborhood, keeping in mind social distancing best practices and CDC guidelines. Here are some other great fun activity ideas to keep your kids entertained by spending a few minutes outside each day:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plant a garden</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Use a bubble wand</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Go camping (in the backyard or in nature)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Enjoy bird watching</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Set up a scavenger hunt or treasure hunt</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have an outdoor family BBQ</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play a game with sidewalk chalk</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Pack up your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/weekender" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">overnight bags</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and camp out in the backyard</span>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><b>Give Yourself a Break</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Making time for rest and relaxation is just as important as making time for activities and putting this time on your calendar will ensure you all take these much needed mental breaks.  Encourage nap or alone time throughout the week for both you and the little ones to enjoy some quiet time. It can be challenging being cooped up in one space with the same people for an extended time. Make sure the whole family gets a chance to rest and recharge with some alone time.  </span></p>
<h2><b>Make Space for Open Communication</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During this time, we’re all facing a lot of change and uncertainty. Make sure you are creating space to connect and communicate with your children. We are all facing the same thing together, so normalize their experience by reassuring them that we are all staying home to keep everyone safe. Try to set aside time for each of your kids to address any questions and worries they may have. Open communication is key during these stressful times at home. If your kids need extra support, don’t be afraid to reach out to a trained professional, including a children’s counselor, psychologist, or social worker.</span></p>
<h2><b>Pat Yourself on the Back &amp; Pour Yourself a Beverage When Needed!</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Figuring out fun quarantine activities for kids is no easy task. Take some time to acknowledge that you’re doing a great job and reward yourself with some new stylish bags from BÉIS for all your hard parenting work. You deserve it!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And since you won’t be working at home forever, treat yourself to one of our chic <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/work-totes">tote bags for work</a>. Return to the office with style, thanks to Beis Travel!</span></p>
<p style="padding-left: 120px;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-weekender-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/7W9A6731_large.jpg?v=1587568889" alt=""></span></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Sources:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[1] "250 Easy, Fun Ways to Get Crafty With Your Kids!" <em>PopSugar, </em><a href="https://www.popsugar.com/family/Kid-Friendly-Crafts-34458881" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.popsugar.com/family/Kid-Friendly-Crafts-34458881</a>.</span></p>
</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">[2] "Everything Coming to Disney Plus in April." <em>Polygon, </em><a href="https://www.polygon.com/disney-plus/2020/4/1/21193772/disney-plus-new-movies-tv-watch-april-2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.polygon.com/disney-plus/2020/4/1/21193772/disney-plus-new-movies-tv-watch-april-2020</a>.</span></li>
</ul>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
