<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/girls-trips.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/best-bachelorette-party-destinations-for-every-bride</id>
    <published>2020-11-19T03:37:11-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:54:35-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/best-bachelorette-party-destinations-for-every-bride"/>
    <title>Best Bachelorette Party Destinations For Every Bride</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Want your bachelorette party to be unforgettable? Learn more about the best bachelorette party destinations and treat your bridal party to a great time!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/best-bachelorette-party-destinations-for-every-bride">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>The wedding day is an event that every bride looks forward to. From sporting your beautiful gown to sharing that magical first kiss as a married couple, and then starting a new life together in holy matrimony—could anything be better than this?</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Enter the bachelorette party. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">maybe</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a bachelorette party isn’t “</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">better</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">” than your wedding, but it’s certainly something that’s worth looking forward to. There are many reasons <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">why traveling is important</a> but pulling out all the stops for your bachelorette party is a great way to celebrate your upcoming nuptials while also treating yourself to a great time. Spending time with your closest friends in a beautiful location is also your chance to thank the people who helped shape you into the confident, amazing woman you are today. </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ideas, Ideas, Ideas. But Where To? </span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So you’re on board with the idea of a memorable bachelorette party, but you’re not sure where to. Before you worry about <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/ultimate-guide-for-what-to-pack-in-a-carry-on" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">what to pack in a carry on</a>, you have to decide where you’re headed! Fortunately, we’ve got you covered with some incredible bachelorette party ideas. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Depending on what you like to do for fun, the perfect vacation can vary significantly from bride to bride. So whether you’re looking to catch some sun in Mexico, or taste an expensive pinot grigio in wine country, read on for the best bachelorette party destinations and incredible <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">girls trip ideas</a> for every bride! </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cabo, Mexico</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: left;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Cabo_Mexico.jpg?v=1605783795" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the beachy bachelorette looking to leave the U.S., Cabo is one of the best places to throw a bachelorette party filled with sun, sand, and celebration. Whether you want to relax by the ocean, rent a yacht or enjoy a roof top bar, pool party, sip on a beachy cocktail on one of Cabo's pristine beaches, or a little bit of both, here are some of the best bachelorette activities in Cabo!</span></p>
<b>
<li>Book a stay at the Grand Solmar <span style="font-weight: 400;">– One of the nicest resorts in all of Cabo San Lucas, the Grand Solmar is the epitome of luxury and ocean views. The hotel also offers an all-inclusive package, which comes with gourmet meals, golfing, and even whale watching. This resort also has amenities such as an adult-only pool, full spa, bars and restaurants, and even a private beach. You can also rent a luxury villa in San Jose del Cabo and hire a private chef and driver if you want your bachelorette party group to all be in the same house. <br><br></span>
</li>
</b><b>
<li>Happy Ending Cantina <span style="font-weight: 400;">– For the bride who wants to throw it back to her college days, the Happy Ending Cantina has everything you need. Beer pong, a dance floor, and $5.00 beer and shot combos are all served up at this rowdy venue.  </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Mango Deck <span style="font-weight: 400;">– For the perfect beachfront bar, give Mango Deck a try! Mango Deck is a famous spot in Cabo, known for its incredible view of Lover’s Beach (sounds fitting for a bride to be, right?). On weekends, you can enjoy a boozy brunch that serves up a perfect mix of Mexican delicacies and fun cocktails during your Cabo bachelorette party. </span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lake Tahoe, California</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Lake_Tahoe_California.jpg?v=1605783886" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not every bachelorette wants to celebrate their upcoming ceremony in the sweltering heat with their bride tribe, and that’s okay. For brides who want the ground as white as their wedding gown (winter wedding anyone?), try hitting the slopes of Lake Tahoe! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Situated in the Sierra Nevada mountains, this perfect destination is a surprising winter wonderland in the heart of California. For fun activities to include in a subzero Lake Tahoe bachelorette party, try some of these ideas:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Skiing and snowboarding <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Book a room at one of Lake Tahoe's lavish ski resorts, or split the cost of a rental house for more privacy. The proximity to the slopes will let you and your friends fill the days with exciting winter sports. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Turn up the heat at night <span style="font-weight: 400;">– A snowy bachelorette party destination doesn’t have to mean ditching the nightlife. Southern Lake Tahoe has a busy bar scene with tons of fun spots to choose from. Heavenly Mountain offers a live DJ for partying </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">directly </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">on the slopes, and Montbleu Casino brings a little slice of Vegas to the mountains for a rowdier bachelorette vibe.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Relax with a spa day <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Recover from the chilly temperatures outside with a nice, hot spa day at Stillwater Spa. This spa offers a ton of packages perfect for a bachelorette party. From massages to manicures and even a boozy brunch, you’ll be feeling completely recharged after a long day of skiing. </span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tulum, Mexico</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Tulum_Mexico.jpg?v=1605783955" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another destination for a bride-to-be who wants </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">to</span></i> <i><span style="font-weight: 400;">be </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">south of the border, Tulum has a killer nightlife that’s bound to be memorable (or not…if you know what we mean). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With close proximity to gorgeous beaches, the jungle and Mayan ruins, Tulum is the perfect place for a Mexico bachelorette party that requires wild energy. Some of the best ideas for a Tulum, Mexico bachelorette bash include:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Gitano <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Gitano is a popular beach bar in Tulum that has a live DJ every Friday night. The cost of entry is totally free, and artisanal cocktails are served all night long. While this bar has locations in Miami and New York, the Tulum spot is the place to be for special events. Bachelorettes can also choose to make a reservation and book a private party at this joint for an experience exclusive to </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">them</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">!<br><br></span></span>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/3.png?v=1619029886" alt="shop luggage accessories" style="float: none;"></a></div>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Playa Paraíso <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Spend relaxing, sunny days relaxing at this tropical beach club. Long nights of celebrating can take a lot out of you—but fortunately, it’s easy to recharge with Playa Paraíso’s beautiful beach beds, delicious food, and zesty margaritas.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Papaya Playa Project <span style="font-weight: 400;">– The Papaya Playa Project is a partner with Design Hotels that host events for Tulum’s tourists. From major parties with live music to more sophisticated dinners at five-star restaurants, they have an activity for everyone. Customers can even book more adventurous outings—like water sports and jungle tours—if they’re feeling brave enough. </span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Las Vegas, Nevada</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Las_Vegas_Nevada.jpg?v=1605784024" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sin City is a classic choice for the perfect bachelorette party destination, but there’s more to this getaway than slot machines and Penn &amp; Teller shows. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scene in Vegas has evolved over the years, and bachelorettes who choose to celebrate on the strip can find a much wider variety of activities now than ever before. </span></p>
<b>
<li>A pool party like no other <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Las Vegas may be known for casinos, but another popular bachelorette activity involves hitting up the daytime pool parties. Many hotels and clubs offer pool parties, and an entry fee will typically get you unlimited drinks and pool time. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Get a helicopter tour <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Celebrate in the sky with one of Las Vegas’ exciting helicopter tours! Starting at $89, you can see the bright lights of the strip from thousands of feet above. Up to six people can enjoy this high-flying tour, so choose wisely who you’re bringing along if this is an activity that interests you.</span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Take a pole dancing class <span style="font-weight: 400;">– This one is for the bold bride-to-be. Stripper 101 is a pole dancing class that will teach you these sexy moves for a starting price of $24. Laugh with your friends as you all try to maneuver the pole, and maybe even pick up a move or two for after the wedding! Make a reservation for your party ahead of time to get a personalized class at their Planet Hollywood location. </span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Napa Valley, California</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Napa_Valley_California.jpg?v=1605784086" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What bride doesn’t love a good glass of wine? </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Get your fix in now before you risk a cabernet stain on your wedding dress by spending a bachelorette weekend in Napa Valley, California. For some fun ideas on how to spice up a weekend getaway in wine country, try out these perfect bachelorette outings that your bridal party will love:</span></p>
<b>
<li>Take the Napa Valley Wine Tour <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Get a private tour of Napa Valley in a luxury vehicle for $1,200. This activity involves four to five hours of wine tasting for up to 12 people, learning interesting facts about winemaking, and a ride in a limousine or party bus! Don’t worry about finding a designated driver, either. The tour includes a safe ride back to your hotel at the end of the tastings. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Ride the Wine Train <span style="font-weight: 400;">– For a cheaper alternative to the wine tour (with a fun twist), try taking the Napa Valley Wine Train. For $233, you get to try wines from all over Napa, eat a gourmet lunch, and feel like a high-class train passenger from the industrial revolution. </span>
</li>
</b><br><b>
<li>Reserve a winery wine tasting <span style="font-weight: 400;">– If you’re looking to avoid post-wine motion sickness, try reserving a spot at one of Napa Valley’s 500 wineries. Most wineries and vineyards accept reservations for larger groups, so your NAPA bachelorette party will have plenty of time to sit down, relax, and try some delicious vino!</span>
</li>
</b><br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Come Prepared for Your Bachelorette Weekend With BÈIS</span></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Blog_Body_Image_1.jpg?v=1605783483" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sometimes, packing can turn a fun vacation into a stressful chore. You don’t always want to deal with a giant suitcase, checking a bag at the airport, or not having room for all your essentials especially when you're headed to one of the best bachelorette party destinations ever.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That’s where BÈIS steps in with our <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel essentials for women</a>.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/weekender" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weekender Bags</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are perfect for a quick getaway with your gal-pals. With spacious internal and external pockets, removable compartments, and even a zip nook for your favorite pair of heels—you’ll be fully prepared for whatever the weekend throws at you!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re planning a longer trip, you may need something with a bit more room (because you can’t be caught recycling outfits on your </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">own </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">bachelorette getaway). With our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-check-in-roller-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">29” Large Check-In Roller suitcase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, you’ll be able to fit every glittery dress, vineyard blouse, or ski jacket you need for the perfect bachelorette vacation!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are many bachelorette destinations to choose from so remember to pack appropriately, bring your favorite outfit, and have fun with your bridal party. Safe travels, and congratulations on your big day!</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2.png?v=1619029735" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Grand Solmar Resort. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Grand Solmar. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://grandsolmarresort.solmar.com/">https://grandsolmarresort.solmar.com/</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Seashine Adventures. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cabo bachelorette party: your ultimate guide to destination bachelorette party planning in cabo san lucas </span></i><a href="https://seashineadventures.com/2019/01/10/cabo-bachelorette-party/#bar-hopping-destinations" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://seashineadventures.com/2019/01/10/cabo-bachelorette-party/#bar-hopping-destinations</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Mango Deck Cabo. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mango Deck Restaurant &amp; Bar. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.mangodeckcabo.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.mangodeckcabo.com</a><a href="https://www.mangodeckcabo.com/">/</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Brides. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ultimate Guide to a Bachelorette Party Weekend in North Lake Tahoe.  </span></i><a href="https://www.brides.com/story/lake-tahoe-bacholerette-party" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.brides.com/story/lake-tahoe-bacholerette-party</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Wedding Wire. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Top 5 Ultimate Ski Bachelor Party Destinations. </span></i><a href="https://www.weddingwire.com/wedding-ideas/ski-bachelor-party-destinations" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.weddingwire.com/wedding-ideas/ski-bachelor-party-destinations</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Gypsy Sols. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tulum Nightlife. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.gypsysols.com/tulum-nightlife/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.gypsysols.com/tulum-nightlife</a><a href="https://www.gypsysols.com/tulum-nightlife/">/<br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">The Plunge. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Best Tulum Beach Clubs. <a href="https://www.theplunge.com/travel-hm/tu/best-tulum-beach-clubs%20" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>https://www.theplunge.com/travel-hm/tu/best-tulum-beach-clubs</span><span> <br><br></span></a></span></i>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Tripadvisor Advisor. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Las Vegas. </span></i><a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Products-g45963-zfc12026-zfg11864-Las_Vegas_Nevada.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Products-g45963-zfc12026-zfg11864-Las_Vegas_Nevada.html</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Jetse. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Private Napa Valley Wine Tour. </span></i><a href="https://68085.partner.viator.com/tours/Napa-and-Sonoma/Napa-Valley-Wine-Tour/%20" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://68085.partner.viator.com/tours/Napa-and-Sonoma/Napa-Valley-Wine-Tour/</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">JetSetChristina. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ultimate Napa Bachelorette Guide. </span></i><a href="https://www.jetsetchristina.com/the-ultimate-napa-bachelorette-guide/%20" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.jetsetchristina.com/the-ultimate-napa-bachelorette-guide/</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></a>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america</id>
    <published>2020-09-25T09:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:53:30-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america"/>
    <title>10 Dreamy Girls Trip Ideas Across America</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking for a reason to set your work status to OOO? We've got 10. These are our girls trip ideas to inspire your next vacay.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When was the last time you spent some quality time with your girl gang? Whether you’re living across the country or right down the street from each other, your daily hustle and bustle can sometimes make it difficult to nourish your friendships. But every moment you make for each other provides a much-needed break from the daily grind—along with inspiration to dedicate more time to self-care. Before you get your <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" title="travel luggage">travel luggage</a>, you have to decide where you're headed!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since girls trips may only come around once in a while, it’s important to find the perfect destination for reminiscing over old memories and making new ones. And for the best girls trip ideas, you’ve come to the right place. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In fact, we’re calling all ladies as we’ve compiled a list of the ten best girls getaway</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">destinations with </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="packing tips"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing tips</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> included, to give you a few ideas for your next adventure with your besties!</span></p>
<h2><strong>#1 Savannah, Georgia</strong></h2>
<div style="text-align: left;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_244712833_480x480.jpg?v=1601048692" alt=""></div>
<div style="text-align: left;">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the top of our girls weekend ideas list? The gem of the South of course! Where else can you find a thriving arts scene, delicious Southern cuisine, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> gorgeous beaches? Savannah, Georgia provides the perfect mixture of small city culture and gorgeous beachfront with so many fun things to do.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A few of our favorite activities include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">A decadent dinner at </span><a href="https://www.elizabethon37th.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elizabeth’s on 37th</span></a>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Day trips to Tybee Island</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A visit to the historic home of Juliette Gordon Low, founder of the girl scouts</span></li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re traveling during beach season, stock your <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" title="luggage sets">luggage set</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with lightweight dresses so that you can stay cool in the summer heat! Get in on some <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women" title="stylish travel essentials">stylish travel essentials</a> before you pack up.</span></p>
</div>
<h2 style="text-align: left;"><strong>#2 New York’s Hudson Valley</strong></h2>
<p><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_502726537_480x480.jpg?v=1601048048" alt=""></strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re craving a Broadway show </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> a relaxing trip into nature, enjoy the best of both worlds by setting up camp in the Hudson River Valley.</span></p>
<p>The following towns and cities are within two hours of Manhattan. They also offer great proximity to swimming holes, farm-to-table restaurants, gorgeous hikes through the Catskill mountains, and more:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hudson</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beacon</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kingston</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Woodstock</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">High Falls</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saugerties</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Choose one perfect spot, rent a car, and prepare to spend your long weekend driving between breweries, farms, and lakes. Spend one day on a trip into the city, or immerse yourself in natural wonders for the duration of the trip!</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/14-road-trip-essentials-every-traveler-needs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="road trip essentials"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Road trip essentials</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">: The Catskills can get chilly at night, even in early summer. Be sure to pack plenty of layers so you’re prepared for potentially cooler evenings.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#3 Key West, Florida</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_153029399_480x480.jpg?v=1601048054" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Miami is a go-to destination for a bachelorette party and summer revelry, but Key West is an ideal spot for a chill beach weekend. Writers from Ernest Hemingway to Judy Blume found inspiration in its gorgeous landscape and architecture, and we know that you, along with your girl gang, will enjoy it too!</span></p>
<p>Keep busy with the following activities: </p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Try snorkeling around gorgeous coral reefs</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Go shopping on Duval St.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spend a day on a boat tour</span></li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Besides your swimsuit, make sure your <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/makeup-cosmetic-cases" title="makeup bag">makeup bags</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are packed with plenty of sunscreen for your face and body! Don't forget to learn <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup" title="how to pack toiletries and makeup">how to pack toiletries and makeup</a> before you head out.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2_ac80841b-d92f-43af-beed-4e16a4d1d267.png?v=1623325179" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>#4 Austin, Texas</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_769311505_480x480.jpg?v=1601048054" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Austin has a little of everything. Known for its live music scene, this bustling small city also has some of the most unique cuisine out there, including:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Famous barbecue</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Southern soul food </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amazing, authentic Mexican cuisine</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Outstanding Japanese bites </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spend your day snacking, then spend your girls night enjoying live music at one of Austin’s many bars. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A travel tip: bring a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-mini-crossbody-in-natural" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÈIS mini-crossbody bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> so that you can be hands-free throughout the day.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#5 Portland, Oregon</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_474991357_480x480.jpg?v=1601048056" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Portland is known for its towering forests, quirky culture, and breweries. You can spend your days immersed in natural wonder and your nights enjoying craft beers—including those infused with legal weed! </span></p>
<p>Some of our favorite spots and activities include:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multnomah Falls</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wine tasting in Willamette Valley</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Columbia River Gorge</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Snacking on Portland’s famous donuts</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Portland Japanese Gardens</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rent a car so you can get out of the city, or make your way around by bicycle!</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bring athletic pants and shoes so that you can fully explore the city’s array of cycling, hiking, and climbing options.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#6 California Wine Country</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_656309851_480x480.jpg?v=1601048055" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California wine country is just about unparalleled when it comes to natural beauty, year-round perfect weather, and plenty of fun activities for a gaggle of ladies looking to cut loose.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plan the perfect girls getaway with the following tips:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Napa Valley and Sonoma are popular destinations, but if you and your friends love spa treatments and a small town feel, consider Calistoga. Likewise, Healdsburg is a fantastic destination with plenty of bars and restaurants and great happy hour options.</li>
<li>When in wine country, do as the locals do—hire a professional to drive you to the best vineyards in the area. That way, you don’t have to take turns being the designated driver!</li>
<li>Visit the Armstrong Redwoods State Natural Reserve to take in some fresh air and see some of the oldest trees in the country. </li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take in the breathtaking views of the most gorgeous vineyards with a horseback riding tour of Jack London Estate. </span></li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you’re in wine country, you’ll need a stylish, yet functional </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-everyday-tote" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">beige tote</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> so that you can pick up a bottle or two as a souvenir from your weekend getaway!</span></p>
<h2><strong>#7 Sedona, Arizona </strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_1054046408_480x480.jpg?v=1601048052" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sedona’s scenic vistas are amongst the most stunning in the country. Bike, drive, or take a hot air balloon ride to visit natural wonders, including the Grand Canyon, which is only two hours away.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Staying local? Sedona is also known for the following:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">New age culture</span><span> – Are you and your friends into crystals, Reiki, and energy healing? Or are you interested in seeing a psychic for the first time to see what all the fuss is about? Sedona is chocked-full of new age stores and alternative practitioners.</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Spas</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Enjoy some of the country’s most beautiful spas, where you’ll find traditional mud wraps, saunas, and facials alongside alternative therapies.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Art scene</span><span> – There are galleries throughout the city showing off work by local artists and artisans. Your group can purchase matching hand-crafted jewelry to help you remember the road trip for years to come. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Be sure you have a camera on-hand to capture the natural beauty of this desert landscape (and to take a few group pictures, of course)!</span></p>
<h2><strong>#8 Charleston, South Carolina</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_1366721726_480x480.jpg?v=1601048053" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Charleston is an elegant port city that combines the best of Southern dining with easy accessibility to beaches and luxury shopping. It’s the perfect place for a girls weekend getaway filled with Southern decadence!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Be sure to:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Eat a southern breakfast of shrimp &amp; grits with your cocktail of choice</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Check out the Tavern at Rainbow Row, the oldest liquor store in the country </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shop from upscale boutiques and vintage stores on King Street</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take a break from eating to try out surfing at Folly Beach</span></li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You’ve got to try oysters on the half-shell, chicken-fried steak, and a dozen other Southern specialties. That means you’ll need a pair of elastic waist pants.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#9 Sun Valley, Idaho</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_567158326_480x480.jpg?v=1601048046" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Want to spend some time </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">really</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> getting away from it all? Relatively off the beaten track, Sun Valley, Idaho features some of the only hot springs in the country, along with a world of breathtaking views and natural wonders. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sun Valley has attractions for all seasons, including:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Frenchman’s Bend hot springs  </span><span>– In autumn, there’s nothing like dipping into a pool of naturally heated fresh water at the end of a day hiking and playing outdoors.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Skiing and snowboarding</span><span> – If your friends group boasts a few snow bunnies, you’ll enjoy the pristine slopes during this outdoor adventure!</span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Mountain lakes</span><span> – If you plan your trip during the balmy Idaho summer, cool off in icy mountain lakes and streams. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you’re back at home base, you’ll find plenty of delicious food at restaurants, bars, as well as spas in this resort town.</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re spending time in Sun Valley, you’re more likely than not to do something active! Bring a muscle balm to give yourself a little extra TLC on top of any spa treatment you book.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#10 Salem &amp; North Shore, Massachusetts</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/shutterstock_609835217_480x480.jpg?v=1601048046" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Although Salem is known for its history as the home of America’s witch trials, it’s also an oceanfront city on the North Shore of Cape Cod. That means it’s the perfect spot to summon your inner mystic </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> catch some waves, making it one of the best girls trip destinations imaginable.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We suggest the following:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>Tour the Salem Witch Museum and learn more about the city’s history. Don’t stop at the gift shop, though—there are countless witch stores throughout the city where modern women sell their homemade witchy wares!</li>
<li>Get a psychic reading or buy your own deck of tarot cards to play with all weekend long. Crow Haven is the oldest witch shop in Salem. We also enjoy HausWitch’s modern approach to magic. </li>
<li>Enjoy the beach during the peak months of July and August. While Dead Horse Beach has an ominous name, that’s all in keeping with the locale’s unique history! You could also check out Winter Island.</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond summer adventures, it goes without saying that Salem is the perfect place to spend Halloween.</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>What to Pack For Your Weekend Trip</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you choose Salem for your next girls trip destination, be sure to bring a jacket. Massachusetts starts to get chilly as early as August!</span></p>
<h2><strong>The Best Girls Trips Start with Your Best Girls</strong></h2>
<div style="text-align: left;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-dopp-kit-in-sakura-pink" target="_blank" title="light pink dopp skit" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/beis_photo_480x480.png?v=1601048064" style="float: none;" width="480x480" height="480x480"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you’re planning for a girls weekend getaway or a more extended besties-only vacation, it’s not about </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">where </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">you’re going, but </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">who </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">you’re with. So long as you’re with the most important women in your life, it doesn’t matter if you’re vineyard hopping in California or telling spooky stories in front of your Airbnb’s fireplace in Massachusetts—adventure, good times, and amazing memories will be sure to follow. </span></p>
<h2>
<span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Travel in Style With BÈIS</strong> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"></span>
</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your girlfriends probably won’t judge you if you’re still lugging around the same carry-on you had in college. But wouldn’t you feel better if you gave yourself an added treat with upgraded </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="travel luggage"><span style="font-weight: 400;">luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="travel accessories"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">? </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After all, it’s hard to get in the mood for a relaxing long weekend when you’re taping your suitcase shut and troubleshooting bum wheels on the way to the airport!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our #1 travel tip: Get your life organized with our functional, fashionable and affordable luggage so you can relax with your besties—and return home with your souvenirs safely in tow, too. </span></p>
<p>If you're looking for more girls' weekend ideas consider cities such as Tulum, San Diego, Palm Springs, Las Vegas, or San Francisco.</p>
<p> <b>Sources:</b></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elizabeth’s on 37th.</span></i> <a href="https://www.elizabethon37th.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.elizabethon37th.net/</span></a>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Roth, Jessica. “A Beginners Guide to Japanese Food in Austin.” </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Austin Chronicle.</span></i> <span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.austinchronicle.com/food/2019-06-14/a-beginners-guide-to-japanese-food-in-austin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.austinchronicle.com/food/2019-06-14/a-beginners-guide-to-japanese-food-in-austin</a><a href="https://www.austinchronicle.com/food/2019-06-14/a-beginners-guide-to-japanese-food-in-austin/">/</a></span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Charleston Spirits.</span></i> <a href="http://www.charlestonspirits.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">http://www.charlestonspirits.com/</span></a>
</li>
</ul>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
