<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/importance-of-travel.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone</id>
    <published>2020-11-18T02:45:34-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-10T04:35:49-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone"/>
    <title>10 Reasons Why Traveling is Important For Everyone</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling really lives up to the hype and has many surprising benefits. Learn why a new </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">life</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> experience in a different place could be just what you need.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’ve spent any time swiping on dating apps, you’ve probably noticed a theme: everyone</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> loves</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> traveling (along with brunch and long walks on the beach). And if traveling isn’t already your Tinder match’s favorite pastime, it’s probably on their bucket list.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why is this? Well, traveling </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">to a new destination</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is one thing that actually lives up to the hype (unlike many dating apps). By planning a trip, you can set yourself up for many surprising benefits.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Best of all, traveling doesn’t need to break the bank. There’s an abundance of cheap flights, affordable accommodations, and cute, cost-effective <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">luggage</a> options out there to make your next adventure possible. Before you Google “<a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel packing tips</a>,” learn why a new experience in a different place could be just what you need.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why Traveling Is Important</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you're wondering why you should travel, check out these 10 benefits</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of traveling:</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">1. Traveling Offers You a Healthy Escape</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For many people, the purpose of travel is to enjoy some much-needed relaxation. Sometimes, you just need a break from everything going on in your life, whether that’s:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Work stress</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A bad breakup</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gloomy weather</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Boredom</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regardless of why you’re craving an escape, travel is the ticket. It’s amazing how small your problems look when you're 40,000 feet up in the sky, gazing down at them from a tiny plane window. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hi problems… Bye problems.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On your vacation, you can indulge in a much-deserved reprieve. Maybe you spend your off-time soaking up the sun on a tropical beach somewhere, the sound of waves lapping, and a piña colada in hand (let's be honest, piña coladas could be the sole reason why traveling is important). Or maybe perusing Parisian art museums all afternoon is more your style. No matter how you choose to relax and unwind, taking a break from your responsibilities is healthy! It allows you to return home with a renewed sense of energy. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2_0a993aa4-416e-463b-a4e6-f9bd6a7daf06.png?v=1623324292" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">2. Traveling Helps You Grow as a Person</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ever hear the saying, “there’s no growth in your comfort zone”? Well, it’s true. If you’re currently stuck in a rut, traveling can help you shake free from stagnation and jumpstart your personal growth journey. Once you set foot in a new city or country, you’ll be given plenty of opportunities to challenge yourself by:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Navigating unfamiliar situations</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Communicating in a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">new</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> language</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meeting new people from diverse cultures</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Tasting new, daring cuisines (</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">escargot, anyone?</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">)</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Signing up for thrilling activities, like skydiving, ziplining, or horseback riding</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By venturing out of your comfort zone, you'll gain a fresh perspective </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">and new ideas</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on your preferences, goals, and values. You'll be able to see beyond the limitations of your day-to-day life and uncover what truly matters to you.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have a life-changing revelation with a change of scenery.</span></i></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-everyday-backpack-in-sakura-pink?_pos=1&amp;_sid=a12d5c189&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="pink backpack" rel="noopener noreferrer"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/1-change_of_scenery_480x480.jpg?v=1605696031" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></i></a></p>
<br><br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">3. Traveling Offers You Immersive, Real-World Learning Experiences</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling can also </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bishopjordan/2017/09/05/science-says-travel-makes-you-smarter/?sh=4f6f917f719a" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">make you smarter</a>.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> If you had a trip to Peru on the books, you might feel inspired to brush up on your Spanish or read up on the history of Machu Picchu. Once you arrive, all of those lessons will become much more memorable and salient. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In other words, traveling transforms the world into your classroom. There’s a reason why so many colleges promote study abroad programs. Even if you embark on your vacation for relaxation’s sake, you can still pick up culinary tips, spiritual practices, and problem-solving skills along the way. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling also helps you dispel any preconceptions you have about other countries and cultures. If your only exposure to a foreign country is what you hear on the news, you could have an overly-negative perception of it. By booking a trip and checking it out for yourself, you’ll see first-hand what it has to offer, allowing you to develop a more accurate (and positive) perspective on the world. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">4. Traveling Enhances Your Understanding of Other Cultures</span></h3>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/the-importance-of-understanding-different-cultures" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Understanding different cultures</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is a reason to travel all on its own. It’s fascinating how diverse different cultures can be, from their pace of life to their long-held traditions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By immersing yourself in a new culture, you’ll reevaluate your assumptions about how life must be lived. Maybe you notice that you savor the slow pace of “island time” in Hawaii. Or maybe you’re invigorated by the lively nightlife of Buenos Aires. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By experiencing a different culture and other values, you’ll learn why traveling is important by discovering there are many ways to live.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">5. Traveling Deepens Your Connection to Humanity at Large</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While many cultures showcase rich diversity, being in a new place, and discovering new things also reveals to you that people aren’t that different from one another. We all share a common humanity.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No matter where you travel, people:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Work hard for their families</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aspire to give their children a better life</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have similar hopes, fears, and dreams</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Enjoy celebrations, music, and great food</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This unified sense of humanity will help you cultivate more empathy for those who are different than you, whether they live at home or abroad. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">6. Traveling Allows You to Try New Cuisines</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re a foodie, traveling can take your taste buds’ on the experience of their lifetime. There’s nothing like visiting a new country to expand your culinary horizons.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Imagine sitting down to a fresh plate of homemade Italian pasta from a family-owned “trattoria.” They’ve been perfecting their craft for hundreds of years. One bite in, you'll discover the purpose of travel and be lost in spaghetti heaven. Or maybe you try out some authentic Japanese sushi or Mexican food South of the border—after experiences like these, you’ll have a whole new appreciation for their cultures of origin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you eat your way through your destination, you may even pick up a few tips and tricks to enhance your kitchen at home! There’s no better way to impress a dinner date than with some “authentic” cuisine inspired by your travels. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">7. Traveling Connects You with New People</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling also gives you the opportunity to meet some new friends! As a traveler, you have a perfect excuse to start up a conversation with locals. All you have to do is ask them about the best things to do in their city. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you meet some </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">especially </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">friendly locals, they may even offer to show you around. You could end up exploring the hidden treasures and “locals-only” hot spots of your travel destination. Even if you’re on the shyer side, traveling has a way of forcing people out of their shells (in the best of ways, of course).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By developing friendships with</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">people abroad, you’ll return home with an international social network—and possibly even an invitation to visit again soon!</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">8. Traveling Lets You Build Meaningful Memories with Loved Ones</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As we know you're discovering, there are many reasons to travel and while solo </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is all the rave these days </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">(especially for young people)</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, family travel or going with friends is equally valuable. It gives you and your loved ones a chance to make memories that you'll look back on for years to come.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From long travel days spent hauling your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> across the airport to unforgettable afternoons traversing a new country, group trips promote a special type of bond. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you’re planning a romantic getaway with your new spouse or a big family bash abroad, or wondering what the <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">best bachelorette party destinations</a> are, you can rest assured that you’ll leave your vacation closer with your travel-mates than you were when you arrived.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-carry-on-roller-in-sakura-pink" target="_blank" title="light pink carry-on luggage" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2-memories_480x480.jpg?v=1605696063" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></a></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">9. Traveling Can Make You More Attractive</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yes, it’s true, posting a photo from your trip to Bali increases your dating app matches by 300%. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s science. </span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All jokes aside, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">studies</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> show that traveling makes you more dateable and desirable. Here’s why:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You’ll have tons of captivating stories to tell</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You’ll exude a newfound sense of confidence</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You’ll be more open-minded due to your exposure to other cultures</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You’ll possess a unique perspective on the world </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a well-traveled person, you inherently become more interesting. Others will see your travels as an indication that you’re adventurous, open-minded, and confident. By embodying this magical travel charisma, you’ll attract like-minded love interests and show them that you’re up for some adventure. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">10. Traveling Amplifies Your Appreciation for Home</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Distance makes the heart grow fonder. This sentiment certainly applies to your hometown after a long stint abroad. Even if you cherish every moment in a foreign country and experience </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">the world’s i</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ncredible cultural diversity </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">and cultural traditions</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, there's something deliciously comforting about returning home </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">to everyday life.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your need for novelty will be satisfied. After experiencing daily life in a different way, you’ll welcome some routine and structure. You’ll also have a newfound appreciation for everything you took for granted in the past. Even being around other native English speakers can feel like a refreshing return to normalcy! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With this elevated sense of gratitude for </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">your</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> home </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">country</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, you can take on your day-to-day life with a new and improved attitude, and you'll be in great company- 86% of people claim that traveling and shaking up their daily routine improves their mood and perspective on life.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want in on this attitude upgrade, it’s just one plane ticket away. </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel in Style</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you can see, there are so many reasons to travel. If you want to jet-set in style, make sure you have the right luggage for your next adventure. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At </span><a href="https://beistravel.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÈIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, we carry a beautiful, top-of-the-line collection of luggage. Whether you need a new toiletry bag, a weekend carryall, or a hardshell suitcase, we’ve got you covered. Best of all, our luggage features weight indicators and TSA-approved locks for ultimate travel convenience.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">:</span></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Forbes. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Science Says Travel Makes You Smarter.  <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bishopjordan/2017/09/05/science-says-travel-makes-you-smarter/?sh=5365daa3719a" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></span></i><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bishopjordan/2017/09/05/science-says-travel-makes-you-smarter/?sh=5365daa3719a" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Contiki. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How does travel change you? 3000 millennials will tell you. <a href="https://www.contiki.com/six-two/travel-change-you-millennials/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></span></i><a href="https://www.contiki.com/six-two/travel-change-you-millennials/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">TransAmerican Center For Retirement Studies. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Journey to Healthy Aging: Planning for Travel in Retirement. <a href="https://www.transamericacenter.org/docs/default-source/resources/travel-survey/tcrs2013_op_travel_and_aging_executive_summary.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></span></i>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/travel-baggage-experiences-of-a-black-woman-traveling</id>
    <published>2020-08-07T08:46:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-05T07:41:46-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/travel-baggage-experiences-of-a-black-woman-traveling"/>
    <title>Travel Baggage: Experiences of a Black Woman Traveling</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Interested in learning more about what it's like to travel as a black woman to a foreign place? Read on for personal experiences and stories.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/travel-baggage-experiences-of-a-black-woman-traveling">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When I was a little girl, my parents used to take me on nighttime drives to put me to sleep. Probably because I wouldn’t stop talking, but I like to think it’s because they knew I was born to travel. As I’ve grown older, I still find that I’m my most peaceful when I’m on a trip to someplace new. I’ve felt exploring new destinations to be a rite of passage, as do most Millennials and Generation Z folks. However, when I travel as a Black Woman -- whether in the United States or abroad -- I’m met with experiences that you can only know if you’re in </span><b>this skin.</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling is -- for lack of better words -- dope! Exploring new destinations can be beautiful, exciting, enriching, and surreal. It can also be scary, nerve-racking, and disorienting. For a Black woman, in congruence with those mentioned above, it’s also invasive, political, and dangerous - especially when solo traveling.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Group travel is my favorite mode of exploration -- who doesn’t love exploring the world with friends?! However, having been in groups with mixed demographics, I’ve seen how my skin tone and accent change how I am treated.  For instance, we might all arrive at the same airport with the same destination in mind, however, when it’s time to show our passports, my white friends will be lackadaisically scanned and sent through while mine will be scrutinized.  I can recall an occurrence when I arrived in Mexico and was standing in the passport check line for International security. I noticed a white family that was on both my initial and connecting flights.  They went up to the counter and were waved through with cursory glances over their documents. On the other hand, I was glared at, looked up and down, and then asked the question...</span></p>
<h2><strong>FIRST IMPRESSIONS?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Soooo...where are you from?” The answer is never, “Texas” or “Los Angeles,” since what they’re really asking about is my African descent. There’s always a look of disappointment on their faces when I tell them I’m simply a Black American from Texas or live in Los Angeles. In these situations, I often wonder: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Should I lie and say I’m from Nigeria? I have a lot of Nigerian friends, maybe they’ll believe me. Should I tell them that it’s possible that I’m from Africa, but my ancestors were slaves, so I truly don’t know exactly where I’m from? </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">I always decide to give them an uncomfortable little giggle and say, “Just Texas, yeehaw!” (People that aren’t from Texas love the nod towards cowboy culture -- I’ve never actually seen a cowboy, and I promise I don’t ride a horse to the grocery store.)</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then there’s the hair situation.  For me, doing my hair every morning is like creating a masterpiece: artistic, time-consuming, and </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">not</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to be tampered with. At the airport, I’ve had to give up that mantra. For the texture and the artistry of the artwork upon my dome </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">must </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">mean that I’m hiding some kind of contraband.  </span><b>Spoiler alert:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> I’m not, and now you just messed up my really cute ‘do...thanks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally, there are the paparazzi -- or at least that’s how I see them.  I don’t think that the rich and famous are particularly fond of being photographed without their consent, but they accept it as the price of fame.  I, however, am neither famous nor being paid, so these particular paparazzi are doubly unwanted. The main people I am referring to are those who have likely never seen a Black person in real life. They’d come up to my friends and me asking for pictures with us, and at first, it didn’t phase me.  I was like, “Ooooo; you think my outfit is fresh today.  Please photograph away, be my guest.” As my awareness of their ask grew, I started to feel uncomfortable. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> What were these people going to do with my picture, and why did I have no agency in it? Would it be rude to say no though my body is my own and belongs to me, even in a picture? </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">These are the questions that I still have.  I never want to come off culturally insensitive, but today, I’m not a cultural attraction. I’m just a person. </span></p>
<h3><strong>REWRITING THE NARRATIVE</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="mayaesthetic.com" target="_blank" title="black woman with flowers" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/sanfrancisco_1_large.jpg?v=1596776073" style="float: none;"></a></p>
<p><b><i>“Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness.”</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">~ Mark Twain</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When black women travel, it can be an incredibly nuanced experience. There’s some bad, but so much beauty.  One of the most special opportunities is the chance to create peace and promote intelligence through understanding.  As a black traveler, I am afforded the opportunity -- should I decide I have the mental capacity -- to reverse negative perceptions of the Black Community, in the travel industry often perpetuated by the media.  Those that have never met a Black American tend to have an extremely monolithic view of us.  While the media may show us as the trio of rappers, athletes, and “thugs.” We have the power to show the world that we are doctors, lawyers, academics, professionals, and so much more than cinema’s often myopic view of us.  I’m able to have the interactions that bridge gaps between cultures of the world and make us understand that even though our outsides are different, we’re more alike on the inside than we may know.</span></p>
<h3><strong>LOOK, BUT DON’T TOUCH!</strong></h3>
<p><b><i>“Don’t touch my hair.”</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">~ Solange Knowles, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don’t Touch My Hair</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So picture this: I’m sitting on a bench outside of my hotel and out of nowhere, a hand is launched towards my head. In confusion, I stand still.  “Wow your hair is so.... Can I touch it?” </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well, I would have said no, but you’ve already got your fingers intertwined with my curls, so now I feel slightly powerless and very...violated?</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling as a black woman means that people will likely ask to touch your hair -- </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">I hope you’ve practiced your Matrix lean.</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> It means men may grab your arm in crowded areas or offer you money on public transit.  It means they may follow you on the street.  It means that your personal space will be invaded and because of the color of your skin, people will assume they have unlimited access to your personal being. They shouldn’t, and they don’t.  Black women are often hypersexualized and fetishized in the media; these depictions lead to degrading assumptions and actions by those who may not interact with Black women often or at all.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">To any Black woman that may read this</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, as we pray for the world to change and for our bodies to be respected on every continent, be careful and aware as you travel.</span></p>
<h3><strong>RE-CONNECTING WITH HISTORY</strong></h3>
<p><b><i>“Travel is an inherently political act, even as it is an intensely personal journey.”</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">~ Mary-Alice Daniel, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling While Black Can Be Downright Bizarre</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">My dear grandmothers could have only dreamed of going to the places I’ve been to! As much as domestic and international travel feels to be a rite of passage for me, the ability to do so is powerfully political. When my grandmothers and their mothers were growing up -- around the time of the Civil Rights Era -- there was scarcely enough disposable income in the African American population for leisurely activities, let alone lavish travel. Even more than that, traveling at that time was life-threatening for the Black community, which is why Victor H. Green published </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Negro Traveler’s Green Book.  </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">This book gave Black travelers a list of safe places to stay and stop whilst traversing the United States.  In one edition, Green optimistically wrote, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">“There will be a day sometime in the near future when this guide will not have to be published.  That is when we, as a race will have equal opportunities and privileges in the United States.” </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Although this book no longer boasts new editions, we haven’t yet made it to the America that Green describes. That is why I feel empowered when I travel. I feel that the generations that came before me, those who fought for me to have the right and the means to immerse myself in new cultures, the ancestors who walked the paths that I now trot, are with me wherever I go. I go there for them and for my descendants to come.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">I’m eternally thankful for sites like</span></i><a href="https://www.blackgirlstraveltoo.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> <i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Black Girls Travel Too</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and</span></i><a href="https://travelnoire.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> <i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel Noire</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> -- our modern day Green Books -- for creating communities where we can see ourselves traveling the United States and abroad. They share their travel stories and help us</span></i> <i><span style="font-weight: 400;">envision ourselves as a part of the traveling communities and alleviate some of the anxiety we might feel walking into a space where we’re unsure whether or not they accept Black people.</span></i></p>
<h3><strong> CLAIMING MY WORLD</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="mayaesthetic.com" target="_blank" title="black woman at disney" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/disneyland_large.JPG?v=1596776071" style="float: none;"></a></p>
<p><b><i>“This world can be our place, too.”</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">~ Farai Chideya, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Traveling While Black</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I can easily recall the time that I felt the most freedom in my </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">entire</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> life. It was at the top of a hike in Cape Town, South Africa. My friends and I found a secluded lake, on a cloudy day, and decided our exploration wouldn’t be complete without a swim. No cell phone service. No other people around. No </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">actual</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bathing suit. Just me, the water, nature, and great company.</span></p>
<p><b><i>“Travel to Africa is among the most healing of all. You go there and get part of your soul back.”</i></b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">~ Elaine Lee</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel is healing. Exploration is liberating. Freedom is exhilarating. I find myself at peace when I’m traveling, expanding my horizons, and learning more about myself and the limits of my imagination. Being in </span><b>this skin</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, in the United States and abroad, can make you feel like you don’t belong. It can make you feel like nature, exploration, travel, luxury and excitement are for lighter people with lighter worries. That’s simply untrue. I said that Black travel is political, and I meant it. Every time we leave our homes, fly to another state or country or simply go to the grocery store, we are claiming the world as our own. We have just as much a right to it as anyone else on the planet.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">To my Black family, friends, and community: </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">We may travel domestically and internationally. We may explore virtually or physically. We may be free at home or abroad. The important thing is, as we travel and invoke inevitable change in this world, we must remember to </span><b>never stop exploring because the world is ours too</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maya Pete curated this post. She is a Stanford Alumna, digital media marketer, plus size fashion blogger, and fitspo enthusiast. Read more from Maya at <a href="mayaesthetic.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">mayaesthetic.com</a> and on Instagram as @maya.esthetic and @fat.fit.fly.</span></i></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="mayaesthetic.com" target="_blank" title="Maya Pete" rel="noopener noreferrer"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/cutesie_large.JPG?v=1596776069" style="float: none;"></span></i></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maya’s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">B</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ÉIS</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Faves:</span></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/all/products/the-everyday-tote-in-natural" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Everyday Tote</span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-black/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Work Tote</span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage/products/the-26-check-in-roller-in-sakura-pink" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Check-In Roller</span></a></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/all/products/the-weekender-in-sakura-pink-woven" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weekender</span></a></p>
<br>
<h4><b>Sources:</b></h4>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YTtrnDbOQAU" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YTtrnDbOQAU</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/traveling-while-black-often-can-be-downright-bizarre?ref=scroll" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.thedailybeast.com/traveling-while-black-often-can-be-downright-bizarre?ref=scroll</span></a></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2014/01/05/travel/traveling-while-black.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2014/01/05/travel/traveling-while-black.html</span></a></li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/the-importance-of-understanding-different-cultures</id>
    <published>2020-07-08T00:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:55:12-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/the-importance-of-understanding-different-cultures"/>
    <title>The Importance of Understanding Different Cultures</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">Understanding different cultures allows you to be more open, accepting, and tolerant of other people. Read on to discover more.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/the-importance-of-understanding-different-cultures">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>As societies become more intertwined on a global scale, countries’ demographics diversify, and our cross-cultural exchanges become more frequent. Our world is getting bigger, richer, and more culturally diverse. Understanding different cultures is more than having an appreciation for our differences, but paving the way for a new world where we all stand together.</p>
<p>We’re at a moment in time when we need to do more than tolerate each other. One of the reasons <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone" title="why traveling is important for everyone">why traveling is important for everyone</a> is because it helps us become more inclusive and have a more well-rounded approach to the way we engage with other human beings. We need to form a global community that encourages mutual understanding, learning, and growing together.</p>
<h2><strong>Why Is It Important to Understand Different Cultures?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Understanding different people and their cultures is one of the best ways we can learn from each other, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> learn more about ourselves. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But what is culture? It boils down to this: culture is what informs our way of being—it’s what shapes our beliefs and values and influences our behaviors. For example, chugging a cup of coffee and a bagel on-the-go is unique to New York culture, while other countries and cultures—like in France and Japan—might strictly treat eating and walking as two separate activities. You engage in culture every day, in small ways and in big ones. </span></p>
<p>Culture is the shared language of a community, the holidays that are celebrated, and the religion that is practiced. It’s the recipes that are made, the material objects passed down through generations, and the ways we communicate with one another.</p>
<h2><strong>What Are the Benefits of Studying and Understanding Other Cultures?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cultivating a positive, accepting, culturally diverse society allows us to embrace multiculturalism and reevaluate old beliefs. We reflect on what </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">we</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> see as normal or abnormal—like eating a bagel on the way to the Metro—and challenge ourselves to see the world from new perspectives. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By studying and understanding new cultures, an important lesson becomes deeply ingrained in our minds—that we have nothing to gain from judging something or someone, we don’t know.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sociologists<sub>1 </sub></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> believe that multiculturalism is defined by the following actions:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Recognizing</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">that there are tons of different cultures and they’re all individually diverse</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Respecting</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">the differences between one another</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Acknowledging</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">the validity of different cultural backgrounds and expressions</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Valuing</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">what other cultures have to offer</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Encouraging</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">diverse groups to contribute to communities and public discourse</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Empowering</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">people to achieve their maximum potential by being critical of their own biases</span>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Celebrating</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">one another, rather just tolerating our differences</span>
</li>
</ul>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/1.png?v=1619029621" alt="shop BEIS bags" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>What Can Different Cultures Teach Us?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By immersing ourselves in other cultures beyond our own, we can learn about each other—where people came from, what their traditions are, and what they struggle with as a community. It also forces us to criticize assumptions held about our own daily life and practices, encouraging incredible personal growth. Who knows, maybe you'll even learn something new about your own culture in the process. </span></p>
<p>There are plenty of ways you can start learning about other cultures, from asking your friends questions to reading up on various cultural norms online, but one of the best ways to truly grasp what a different culture is like is to put yourself at a culture’s epicenter—travel. Embracing different cultures through travel allows you to experience what it’s like to be a part of a community other than your own. It also gives you cultural awareness and acceptance, which can help break down cultural barriers while interacting with people of different backgrounds. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span>Here are some of the ways to do that:</p>
<ul>
<li>Try a native language and dialect to achieve cultural competence—the ability to effectively interact with people across cultures. Even learning a few phrases and words can help you make deep connections with a culture different than your own! Learning a different language will also help you learn effective communication skills when speaking English with people who are not from the same cultural background as you.  </li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Join in on local celebrations with an open heart and an open mind.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Cuisine <i><span style="font-weight: 400;">is </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">culture. Tap into your inner Anthony Bourdain and try the foods and drinks that locals are having.</span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Artistic expression can open up whole new doors to your understanding of a new culture. Visit art exhibits, performances, and history museums in the area.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Don’t be afraid to ask questions, but make sure you’re being an active listener—it’s important to go out of your way to be respectful when someone is kind enough to open up and share their world or cultural values. </li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>How Does Learning About Other Cultures Help Us Grow?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond gaining knowledge about a certain culture, you can become a better ally to a community you want to support by: </span> </p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trying new experiences outside your comfort zone</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taking the time to learn about different cultures</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Carrying those valuable skills into all other aspects of your life</span> </li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Increased Cultural Sensitivity</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learning about one culture is a lot like learning a different language—once you’ve done the work to understand and connect with one, it’s easier to learn about more. Increasing your cultural sensitivity about one culture helps you be more mindful of other cultures too, and may inspire you to learn more about different communities in the future. It also makes you want to be more open and share your culture with others who are interested. Win-win.</span></p>
<h3><strong>Reevaluating Biases</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cross-cultural experiences help you be more aware and cognizant of the way you act—from the things you think to the words you say, to the clothes you wear. But it doesn’t just make you rethink your own cultural biases. It also makes you question the root of where they came from—where do we subconsciously pick up learned behaviors and opinions that are culturally insensitive?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By normalizing the fact that you can change your opinions and allowing yourself to admit personal biases, you’ll start to recognize other groups of people for who they are—people just like you. </span></p>
<h3><strong>Becoming More Empathetic</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Absorbing new information, seeing the world from different points of view, and practicing active listening skills are all humbling—and even joyful—acts that make you a more empathetic person.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Especially in America, where demographic projections</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> have shown that diversity will continue to rise no matter what, even if immigration slows down, applying these new skills to life in the US is more important than ever.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Embracing Cultural Diversity</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learning about different cultures is a crucial part of personal and societal development. When preparing to travel to other countries, get your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and gear from brands whose message you identify with.</span> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÈIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, our mission is to embrace cultural exchange through travel, because we recognize the value of learning and growing together.</span> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2.png?v=1619029735" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Purdue University. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">What is Cultural Diversity?</span></i> <a href="https://www.purdueglobal.edu/blog/social-behavioral-sciences/what-is-cultural-diversity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.purdueglobal.edu/blog/social-behavioral-sciences/what-is-cultural-diversity/</span></a>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Brookings. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reducing immigration will not stop America’s rising diversity, Census projections show</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><a href="https://www.brookings.edu/research/reducing-immigration-will-not-stop-americas-rising-diversity-census-projections-show/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.brookings.edu/research/reducing-immigration-will-not-stop-americas-rising-diversity-census-projections-show/</span></a>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
