<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/luggage.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/types-of-luggage</id>
    <published>2021-03-02T12:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:52:36-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/types-of-luggage"/>
    <title>Types of Luggage</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Ready to find the type of luggage that is right for you? In this guide, we break it all down for you including sizing, features, and wheel type.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/types-of-luggage">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you’re an avid traveler or you enjoy the occasional weekend getaway, you need a reliable set of luggage bags. Not all types of luggage are built the same; each one offers a different degree of durability, functionality, and style. By choosing the right type of </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for your needs, you can make your travel days a lot easier and more comfortable. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below, we’ve broken down the different types of luggage by their styles, features, and sizes so you can choose the one that’s right for you.</span></p>
<h2><strong>The Most Common Types of Luggage</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some of the most popular luggage options:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Rolling suitcases</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – The standard rolling suitcase is many people’s go-to piece of luggage. It’s spacious, functional, and easy to take from place to place. Since rolling luggage is on wheels, you can easily glide it through airports and down long hotel hallways. Rolling suitcases come in a range of sizes, materials, and styles, giving you plenty of options to choose from. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Backpacks </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– If you pack on the lighter side, a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">backpack</a> may be your perfect carry-on bag. Due to its hands-free style, you can carry your Starbucks latte and bag of duty-free goodies with ease. If you’re nervous that a backpack may strain your shoulders, simply choose one with comfortable padded back straps.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Duffel bags </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– A Duffel bag offers the space of a suitcase and the soft shape of a backpack. They’re easy to fit into overhead compartments and can hold unconventionally-shaped items. Some duffel bags also come with wheels and retractable handles, turning them into a hybrid suitcase. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Hard Luggage vs Soft Luggage</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you choose to purchase a rolling suitcase, you have an important decision to make: </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hard-vs-soft-luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hardside or softside</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">? </span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hardside luggage is made of a hard material, like aluminum or polycarbonate, while softside luggage is made of fabric. Both types of suitcases offer unique advantages. </span></p>
<h3><strong>The Benefits of Hardside Luggage</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hardside luggage stands out for its:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Durability </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Hardside luggage offers unparalleled durability. It will never rip or tear on you. Since it’s harder to overstuff, you’ll also be much less likely to damage its zippers.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Weather-resistance</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If your adventures take you through wet weather conditions, hardside luggage is the way to go. Due to its impermeable exterior, it can withstand snow, rain, and hail much better than its softside counterpart. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Cleanliness</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Hardside luggage is super easy to clean. You can wipe it down with a damp cloth or antiseptic wipe at any time. If you’re a germaphobe, this can offer you a lot of relief. Due to its hard exterior, it also won’t absorb any liquids or mildew-aromas. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Protection</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you need to transport fragile items, a hardside suitcase can offer them more protection. Its hard outer shell will safeguard your valuables from anything that might bang up against them at the bottom of the plane. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<div style="text-align: left;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" title="travel luggage"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/5.png?v=1617295096" alt="" style="float: none;" width="482" height="241"></a></div>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong>The Benefits of Softside Luggage</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Compared to hardside luggage, softside luggage offers more:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Accessibility</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you need to grab something from your suitcase in a pinch, softside luggage is easier to squeeze your hand into without opening the luggage completely. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Flexibility</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you want the freedom to overpack a few items here and there, softside luggage is much more flexible, though overstuffing could cause issues with its zippers.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Depending on your priorities, one of these types of luggage will appeal to you more than the other. At BÉIS, we believe that hardside luggage takes the cake. That’s why we offer a line of </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hardside luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> made of super-durable polycarbonate. </span></p>
<h2><strong>Two-Wheeled vs Spinner Suitcases</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When shopping for a suitcase, you have another important choice to make: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you want two static wheels or four spinner wheels? </span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The wheels you choose can make or break your travel experience. If they’re flimsy or hard to control, your travel day will be filled with frustration. When they glide smoothly and sturdily, your travel experience will follow suit.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Two-wheeled static suitcases</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Two-wheeled luggage has been around for a long time. You’ve probably used it before. It rolls forward and backward and you have to tilt it back to get it moving. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since the wheels only move in two directions, they’re a little easier to control on uneven surfaces. However, they can become burdensome if your bag is heavy, since you’ll always have to lean your suitcase back to drag it behind you. If your suitcase is super-heavy, this can put a great strain on your wrist and shoulders.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Four-wheeled spinner suitcases</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Four-wheeled spinner suitcases have a much greater range of motion. Their wheels can rotate 360 degrees, enabling you to turn and spin your suitcase in any direction. With four wheels supporting your bag, you can glide it in an upright position as you walk through the airport or hotel lobby, taking all of the weight off your wrists and shoulders. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a result, it’s the favored option for most people and the type of suitcase we carry at BÉIS.</span></p>
<h2><strong>The Different Luggage Sizes</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Depending on your next getaway’s length and occasion, you’ll need to choose a suitcase of adequate size. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Most luggage lines come with the following options:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Carry-on bag </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– If you’re a light packer or if you don’t want to wait around at the baggage claim, you need a carry-on bag. Most airlines only allow carry-on bags that are 22 by 14 by 9 inches or smaller.<sup>1</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> At BÉIS, our carry-on bag is 21 inches tall, so you can trust that it will fit into the overhead bin with ease.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Medium check-in bag </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– If you need a little more space, you may be willing to check in your bag instead. At BÉIS, our medium-sized check-in bag is 26 inches tall. It offers the perfect amount of space to comfortably pack for a weeklong vacation. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Large check-in bag</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you want to check in a larger piece of luggage, 29 inches is a great size. This larger bag will offer you the extra room you need to pack bulky items or to bring more clothes for a longer travel excursion.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÉIS, you can get all three sizes in our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hardside luggage set</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. In turn, you’ll always have the size of suitcase you need on hand. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Types_of_Luggage_copy_img1.jpg?v=1614801211" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>The Most Important Luggage Features</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to choosing the right style, size, and wheels for your luggage, you should also look for some added features that can make your life easier, including:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Weight indicators</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – After packing your bag to the brim, you may be concerned about its weight. Will it exceed that 50-pound weight limit?<sup>2</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To find out, you can lug your bag on top of your home scale. If you don’t have a scale, you’ll have to take your chances at the airport and risk getting hit with an overweight fee or having to transfer some items to your carry-on.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can kiss these hassles goodbye for good by choosing a suitcase with a built-in weight indicator. If your bag is over 50 pounds, this indicator will turn red, letting you know you need to lighten the load before heading to the airport.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Water-resistant zipper tape</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Standard zippers often have tiny crevices where water could creep inside. By choosing a suitcase with water-resistant zipper tape, you won’t need to worry about this.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>TSA-approved locks</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you want to keep your valuables secure, you may choose to add a lock to your suitcase. However, it’s important to know that TSA has rules about the types of suitcase locks that are allowed.<sup>3</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> At BÉIS, we make things easier for you by including a TSA-approved lock with each of our suitcases.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A retractable bag attach strap</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – After lugging your carry-on bags around all day, it’s nice to load them onto your suitcase after you pick it up at the baggage claim. However, your carry-ons may fall off if you don’t secure them properly. By purchasing a suitcase with a retractable bag attach strap, you can attach them with confidence. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Cushioned pillow handle </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Even if your suitcase has four wheels, it can still hurt your hands if the handle is uncomfortable. By choosing a suitcase with a cushioned pillow handle, you'll enjoy a pillow-soft grip. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÉIS, our luggage comes with all of these useful features so you can enjoy a comfortable, hassle-free travel experience every time. To further your luggage experience, check out BÉIS packing cubes for h<a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ow to use packing cubes</a> in your new suitcase purchase!</span></p>
<h2><strong>What Are the Best Places to Buy Luggage?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Luggage shopping can be done online or in-store. If you visit an in-person store, your options may be limited to what they have on the floor. If you shop online, you can easily compare different models and choose the one that offers the features you need most. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÉIS, we make the online shopping experience easier by including detailed descriptions for each of our products. You can also check out our product reviews to find out just how much our customers love our luggage. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Best of all, buying online with BÉIS has no risk. If you want to return or exchange something, no problem. Most of our products can be returned or exchanged within 90 days of your original purchase free of any shipping charges.</span></p>
<h2><strong>BÉIS: Your One-Stop-Shop For Beautiful Luggage </strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you want stylish, practical luggage, </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> has got you covered. We create all of our products with the fashionable jet setter in mind. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No matter where your travels take you, our durable multi-purpose <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel bags</a>, </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hardside luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can help you get there in style. </span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Jamie Ditaranto, “Carry-on and Personal Item Size Limits for 32 Major Airlines.” <i>SmarterTravel</i>, 27 July 2020, <a href="https://www.smartertravel.com/personal-item-vs-carry-on/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
<div></div>
</li>
<li>
<p>Vulcan, Nicole. “How to Prevent Overweight Luggage.” <i>USA Today</i>, Gannett Satellite Information Network, 21 Nov. 2017, <a href="https://traveltips.usatoday.com/prevent-overweight-luggage-103471.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Walsh, Kathryn. “TSA Luggage Guidelines.” <i>USA Today</i>, Gannett Satellite Information Network, 5 Feb. 2019, <a href="https://traveltips.usatoday.com/tsa-luggage-guidelines-107047.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
<p> </p>
<div></div>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-suitcase</id>
    <published>2021-01-21T05:15:32-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T11:35:55-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-suitcase"/>
    <title>How to Clean a Suitcase</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning a suitcase can feel like a daunting chore but it doesn't have to be! Read more for easy ways to clean your luggage.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-suitcase">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>You travel because you want to see the world and take home all the experiences it has to offer you. However, you’re not too jazzed about taking home the world’s germs.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between riding to the airport, cycling through the luggage carousel, and rolling through the cobblestone streets of Rome (or the asphalt of Chicago), your suitcase has touched a lot of unfamiliar hands and rubbed against a lot of new surfaces.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today, we’ll discuss how to clean a suitcase and </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, covering: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Difference between cleaning and disinfecting (and how to do both)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to clean the inside of a suitcase</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to clean the outside of a suitcase</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to clean fabric <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage">luggage</a></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let’s get started!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unpack Your Suitcase</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first thing to do after returning from a trip is to resist the urge to plop your suitcase down on your bed, empty it halfheartedly, then plop yourself on the bed shortly after.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is because there’s probably a bunch of germs that hitched a ride on your suitcase that you don’t want to bring deep into your home. So, until your suitcase is clean and disinfected, try to keep it in your entryway, garage, or on your porch.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Start by unpacking. If unpacking for you is more like shoving the contents of your suitcase, unfolded and unorganized, into a closet corner until you’re ready to deal with them, who can blame you? Just make sure that anything that makes it into your home is clean first. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For clothes, this means you can simply throw all your dirty clothes into a washer when you get home. As for shoes, toiletry bottles, electronics, and other hard objects, you can wipe these down with a disinfecting wipe. Easy peasy! Now, the real cleaning begins.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Unpack_Your_Suitcase_07b3482d-c866-4727-b239-e31ed3992673.jpg?v=1611234185" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning vs Disinfecting</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First of all, there’s a difference between cleaning and disinfecting, and one is not better than the other. When it comes to how to clean luggage (or any surface for that matter), you have to do both. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take it from the CDC. They say that cleaning is “the removal of germs, dirt, and impurities from surfaces. It does not kill germs.” Meanwhile, disinfecting is the use of chemicals “to kill germs on surfaces.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, if you’re doing one and not the other, there may still be dirt or germs from who-knows-where vacationing on your luggage. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That goes for both the inside and outside of your suitcase. Let’s start with the inside.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning the Inside of Your Suitcase</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make sure everything is out of your suitcase and check all the pockets before you get started on cleaning the interior. Now it’s time to do three things:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>De-crumb your suitcase</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – You’ll want to get rid of crumbs or big pieces of debris. You could do this by vacuuming the inside of your suitcase or, if you’re outside, by just turning your suitcase upside down and giving it a good shake. You’d be surprised how many snack crumbs and gum wrappers you can find living in the crevices of your suitcase.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Wash the interior</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – All kinds of things touch the interior of your suitcase—maybe your hiking shoes or your favorite book that goes with you everywhere (and has touched more surfaces than you can count). So, give the inside a good wash with a wet washcloth, mild soap, and water (nothing too crazy, you still want to preserve the fabric). Of course the next step is to disinfect. This can be done with a disinfectant wipe.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Remove stains</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – As long as makeup and wine exist, stains are an inevitable part of life and travel. Luckily, a stain remover and a bit of scrubbing should do the trick.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Use Packing Cubes</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning luggage is great fun and all, but you could keep dirty items away from your suitcase’s interior lining altogether by using </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes?_pos=1&amp;_sid=116d84be6&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This way, when you get home, you can simply empty everything from each packing cube and wash the cubes themselves rather than the interior lining. This will save you time and elbow grease, but also preserve your suitcase.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2.png?v=1619029735" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Do You Clean a Smelly Suitcase?</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maybe your suitcase isn’t dirty, per se—it just smells funky. Here are a few things that can cause this:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You don’t travel very often, so your suitcase spends a lot of time stored away in a dark, warm place (like a basement or a garage).</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">You have a very old or vintage suitcase that has a lot of stories, and some smells to go along with them.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your suitcase has simply held one too many wet swimsuits or opened chip bags.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whatever the reason for your smelly suitcase, consider:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Airing it out</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Sometimes what a suitcase needs after being stored away for a long time is some air and sunlight. Try opening up your suitcase for a few hours where the sun and air can get to it.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Using baking soda</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Sprinkling baking soda inside a suitcase is a popular method for getting rid of the musty smell. The amount of baking soda will depend on the amount of stink, so sprinkle until you’re happy. Then shut the suitcase for up to a week and vacuum it up when the stink is gone.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Using kitty litter</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – This can be effective, but messy. So, you can do this by filling a pillowcase with kitty litter and placing the pillowcase inside the suitcase for a few days.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Spraying with white vinegar and water</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – White vinegar truly is the versatile household product everyone says it is. Try one part white vinegar and three parts water in a spray bottle and allow your suitcase to air dry.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For preventing odor, stick a dryer sheet in your suitcase before leaving home to keep everything in it smelling like you just washed it.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning the Outside of Your Suitcase</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If the outside of your luggage could talk, it would have some pretty wild stories, but you probably don’t want your luggage to look as battle-worn as it is. Cleaning it efficiently can make it look like new.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hard Shell Luggage</span></h3>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wondering about <a href="%20https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hard-vs-soft-luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">hard vs soft luggage?</a> The exterior of a hard shell suitcase is water resistant and much more durable to washing and scrubbing than soft shell suitcases. So, if you’re a clean freak, this is your time to shine.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning a hard sided suitcase can simply be done with a damp cloth and some mild soap. Scrub to your heart’s content. Then rinse and disinfect.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once again, this is where a disinfecting wipe comes in handy. An alternative to a disinfectant wipe is a solution of half a cup of bleach per gallon of water. Wipe all around the suitcase exterior and try to keep your suitcase wet with this solution for five minutes. This should kill whatever germs your suitcase picked up from being roughly handled and rolled around in that greasy stuff they put on luggage carousels.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scuffed Luggage</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s rare that your suitcase will make it home without at least one scuff mark. Even after a good scrub, finding some scuff marks on your beautiful suitcase is heartbreaking, but normal. Don’t worry! That is why we created the </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-beis-buffer" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BEIS Buffer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, to keep your hardside luggage looking just as chic as when you bought it.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Do You Clean Fabric Luggage?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To clean the exterior of a fabric suitcase, you’ll need:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A scrub brush</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A foaming fabric spray (i.e. carpet cleaner or sofa cleaner)</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A vacuum</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spray your entire suitcase with foaming spray. Then scrub with a brush, focusing mostly on visible tough stains. After letting your product sit on your suitcase (for however long the product advises), vacuum off the foam. You can repeat this for stubborn dirt and tough stains.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning the Bits and Bobs</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you’re cleaning your suitcase, it’s important to get it </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">all</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> clean. Make sure you’re not skipping over these areas:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The handle</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – This is the part of your suitcase that is probably touched the most by unknown hands.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The wheels</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Suitcase wheels that are stopped up with dirt, not only perform worse, but also become really efficient at germing up your floors. Put on some gloves, close your eyes, and give your wheels a good scrub.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The bottom</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Similar to the wheels, the bottom of your suitcase picks up a lot of dirt from the ground, so give this part of your suitcase some extra attention when you’re cleaning.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The pockets</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Consider using a small brush to get into the small corners and crevices of your suitcase pockets and remove any dirt that might be tucked away in there. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Cleaning_the_Bits_and_Bobs.jpg?v=1611234225" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;"></span></h2>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let Your Suitcase Dry Overnight</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After your suitcase is fresh and spotless, open it up and lay it out (outside if you can), so that it can completely dry overnight (a closed, wet suitcase is a recipe for mold and mildew).</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clean Yourself!</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally! It’s time to wash your hands, change your clothes, and officially come home. Take a load off, you’ve earned it.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make Travel Easy</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With all the preparation that goes into traveling, knowing how to wash a suitcase is just one of the many things you have to plan for. The last thing you want to worry about is if your luggage can handle the trip. So, durable and easily washable luggage can mean a shorter distance between you and your television when you get home. Luckily, that’s exactly what BEIS specializes in- hard luggage sets that add a flair to your travel look while also providing functionality.</span></p>
<br><br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleaning and Disinfecting Your Home</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prevent-getting-sick/cleaning-disinfection.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prevent-getting-sick/cleaning-disinfection.html</a><a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prevent-getting-sick/cleaning-disinfection.html"><br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Conde Nast Traveler. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Clean Your Luggage After a Trip, Because Germs</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.cntraveler.com/story/how-to-clean-your-luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.cntraveler.com/story/how-to-clean-your-luggage</a><a href="https://www.cntraveler.com/story/how-to-clean-your-luggage"><br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel Nite. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Deodorize Suitcase</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://travelnite.com/how-to-deodorize-suitcase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://travelnite.com/how-to-deodorize-suitcase/</a><a href="https://travelnite.com/how-to-deodorize-suitcase/"><br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Hawk Hill.</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> 5 Methods for Cleaning Vintage Suitcases and Deodorizing Old Luggage.</span></i> <span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://www.hawk-hill.com/cleaning-vintage-suitcase-smell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.hawk-hill.com/cleaning-vintage-suitcase-smell/</a><a href="https://www.hawk-hill.com/cleaning-vintage-suitcase-smell/"><br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Clever Journey. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Clean Your Suitcase to Make it Look Brand New</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><a href="https://www.cleverjourney.com/how-to-clean-luggage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cleverjourney.com/how-to-clean-luggage/</span></a>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hard-vs-soft-luggage</id>
    <published>2021-01-10T11:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:54:53-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hard-vs-soft-luggage"/>
    <title>Hard vs Soft Luggage</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">There are plenty of luggage options out there but it can be difficult to know if you should get a hard or soft shell. Learn more about both types here.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hard-vs-soft-luggage">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>When planning for a trip, it can be easy to feel like luggage comes last. Maybe you’ve already created a strict budget, made a hundred reservations, and agonized over what you’re going to wear. When it’s time to grab the luggage, you might want to just settle for whatever gets you from point A to point B.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But a lot can happen between point A and point B. One thing is for sure: You need </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that will last you throughout this journey and many more. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, what makes </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">good </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage">luggage</a>? And between hard or soft luggage, which one will not only get you where you need to go, but with comfort and ease? This article will guide you through everything you should consider when deciding on hard vs soft luggage including:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanliness </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Accessibility</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flexibility</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durability</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobility</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Protection </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanliness </span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When it comes to</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-suitcase" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">how to clean a suitcase</a> and keeping them clean, is hard or soft luggage better?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While hard sided luggage is more prone to scuffing, these scuffs can be </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-beis-buffer" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">buffed away</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> quite easily while soft sided luggage tends to take on more persistent damage from:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Dirt</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – The fabric of soft sided luggage can make dirt more noticeable than it does on hard sided luggage. Also, the slicker surface of hard sided luggage can make it easy to wipe away dirt with a stray cafe napkin as you wait for your flight. When it comes to soft luggage, causal wiping can quickly turn into vigorous scrubbing, until you realize only soap and water will really do the job. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Germs </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Soft sided luggage is made of more porous fabric, while hard sided luggage is made of less absorbent material. With a hard sided suitcase, you can worry less about germs burrowing into the material of your suitcase, and you can wash away germs more easily.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Smells</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Soft luggage can absorb water, making it easier for it to trap smells and (if it stays wet for too long) mold and mildew. With hard sided cases, you can expect a level of water resistance that resists </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">smelliness</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> too.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Accessibility</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are plenty of situations where soft sided luggage makes your stuff more accessible. For example, this comes in handy in a cramped space where you can just squeeze your hand through a half-open zipper and get something out. Hard luggage can require you to completely open your bag which may not always be possible.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the lower accessibility you get with hard sided luggage may be more of a pro than a con. A cut or a slightly opened zipper on a soft suitcase can leave your items vulnerable to being lost or stolen. A hard sided suitcase requires more effort to get into, especially if it has a lock (as many </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hard suitcases do</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">).</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Accessibility.jpg?v=1611233196" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flexibility</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Soft sided suitcases—as is their namesake—are softer and more flexible than hard sided suitcases. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, hard luggage has made great strides in flexibility. Many of today’s hard sided luggage is made with materials that offer more give than before:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Polycarbonate</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – </span><a href="https://petergreenberg.com/2014/07/29/consider-buying-soft-hard-shell-luggage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polycarbonate luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> flexes a little to absorb impact (it’s flexible enough to be used in contact lenses). If you’re wondering if hard luggage cracks, polycarbonate makes that concern a thing of the past.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2.png?v=1619029735" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Want to Avoid Overpacking? Hard Luggage is the Secret</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The flexibility of soft luggage may appeal to doomsday packers, but in many instances, overpacking is an </span><a href="https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">emotional response</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> rather than a rational one. If you’re trying to curb your overpacking ways, hard luggage might actually do the trick. The rigidness of a hard sided suitcase can not only keep you from filling the limited space in your accommodations with the three extra outfits you brought, but it can also save you money by keeping your baggage weight in check.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durability</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re an avid traveler, you’ll want luggage that will stand up to all your adventures and not need frequent replacing. A quality hard sided suitcase can be the answer to this because hard luggage is:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Less prone to ripping</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – As mentioned above, it’s so much more tempting to overpack with a soft suitcase. If you’re prone to overpacking, your poor zippers are working overtime and it’s a matter of time before you start to see tears in your luggage. This is not a problem with hard luggage.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>More weather resistant</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – While a quality soft suitcase shouldn’t just disintegrate in the snow or wash away in the rain, hard luggage is simply better at standing up to weather conditions because it doesn’t take on as much water.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>More resistant to wear-and-tear</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Over time, luggage inevitably gets beat up. The material of hard sided luggage resists this by absorbing less dirt, grease, and water, which maintains the quality of the luggage. Also, luggage made with polycarbonate is more scratch resistant than the plastic materials of the past.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mobility</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have you ever tried to wheel a bloated, overstuffed soft suitcase around a crowded airport or onto a tight bus? It’s, to put it delicately,</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> an experience</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. You’re half-wheeling and half-lifting a leaning suitcase with a very unpredictable range of motion. And if you’re in a hurry? Good luck.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the other hand, hard sided suitcases are easy to roll (either behind, in front, or beside you). Also, the rigidness of a hard sided suitcase makes it more stable, even when it’s heavily packed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, in situations where you need to bob, weave, and glide quickly, hard luggage is the obvious choice.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Protection</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re traveling with valuable, breakable items, hard luggage is the way to go. Soft luggage can squish and flatten under the weight of other luggage, but hard luggage will keep its shape, so that the stuff inside isn’t smashed. This is particularly important if you’re traveling with electronics, lotions, sunscreens, shampoos, or wine bottles.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The weight of hard sided luggage vs soft sided luggage will depend on the individual luggage, but you may be surprised to find that many hard suitcases made of polycarbonate can be lighter than some soft luggage.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What About Aluminum Luggage?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, we talked mostly about how soft luggage compares to polycarbonate luggage because of how common they are, but </span><a href="https://maphappy.org/2018/12/road-tested-the-core-differences-between-polycarbonate-and-aluminum-suitcases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">aluminum</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is another kind of hard luggage you may be considering for your travels. How does it stack up? </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleanliness</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aluminum luggage is pretty comparable to polycarbonate in its ability to stay clean. Neither of them need much more than a wipe-down to get off dirt.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flexibility</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aluminum luggage is the least flexible of the current suitcase options on the market. Most people aren’t the most efficient packers, and while polycarbonate suitcases nudge you to stop overpacking, aluminum suitcases give you a real shove.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weight</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since aluminium is such a heavy material, aluminum suitcases can really pack on the pounds, which can be uncomfortable in your hands and a bit scary to lift into the overhead bin.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durability</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An aluminum suitcase is designed to be nearly indestructible, and its rigid frame offers supreme protection of the items inside it. It is also resistant to weather and water. So, one of these could last you a lifetime.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Well, it </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">could</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> last you a lifetime if you’re willing to look past all its nicks, dings, and dents that it will inevitably collect. Aluminum suitcases are far worse than soft or polycarbonate luggage at hiding their battle scars. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cost</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aluminum luggage is in the upper echelon price-wise. But for a heavy suitcase with very little flexibility that’s bound to show all its bang-ups, you probably won’t consider this option very cost-efficient.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Cost.jpg?v=1611233231" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, Is Hard or Soft Luggage Better?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here’s the recap of the hard shell vs soft shell luggage battle.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Soft luggage is:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">More accessible</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">More flexible</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While hard polycarbonate luggage is:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Easier to keep clean </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">More secure than softside luggage </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Less prone to overstuffing</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">More durable than soft luggage</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">More mobile</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Better than soft luggage at protecting breakable items</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Able to be very lightweight</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally, aluminum luggage is:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The most durable</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The least prone to overstuffing</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best at protecting breakable items</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In several categories, hardside luggage takes the gold (and all the clothes; </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">hurry up, we need to get packing!</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">). </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">BEIS Hard Luggage: Made for Traveling in Style</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is why BEIS specializes in polycarbonate, hard shell luggage that can go anywhere you go. Along with the standard features of hard luggage, BEIS offers:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>An extra 2 inches of expandable space</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Throwing in one more outfit won’t hurt.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A weight indicator</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Avoid overweight fees. Being prepared shouldn’t cost you.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>TSA approved locks</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – No one is getting a hold of your favorite little black dress.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Water resistant zipper tape</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – This makes your luggage a fortress against water.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Retractable bag attach strap</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – On the days when you’re carrying bags on top of bags, let your suitcase do some of the work. It can hold up to 15 pounds of luggage for you.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whatever adventure you are on, trust BÉIS to provide suitcases that are along for the ride.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Peter Greenburg. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">What to Consider Before Buying Soft or Hard Shell Luggage</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><a href="https://petergreenberg.com/2014/07/29/consider-buying-soft-hard-shell-luggage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://petergreenberg.com/2014/07/29/consider-buying-soft-hard-shell-luggage/<br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Expert World Travel. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hard Side vs Soft Side Luggage</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://expertworldtravel.com/hardside-vs-softside-luggage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://expertworldtravel.com/hardside-vs-softside-luggage</a><a href="https://expertworldtravel.com/hardside-vs-softside-luggage/">/<br><br></a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Consumer Reports. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Choosing Between Hard-Sided and Soft-Sided Luggage</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/luggage/choosing-between-hard-sided-luggage-and-soft-sided-luggage/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.consumerreports.org/luggage/choosing-between-hard-sided-luggage-and-soft-sided-luggage/<br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Vox.</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The psychology behind over- (and under-) packing. </span></i><a href="https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing<br><br></span></a>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Map Happy. The Key Difference Between Polycarbonate and Aluminum Suitcases. </span><a href="https://maphappy.org/2018/12/road-tested-the-core-differences-between-polycarbonate-and-aluminum-suitcases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://maphappy.org/2018/12/road-tested-the-core-differences-between-polycarbonate-and-aluminum-suitcases/</span></a>
</li>
</ol>
<br><br>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
