<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/packing-tips.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-packing-cubes</id>
    <published>2021-03-02T12:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-11T01:16:12-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-packing-cubes"/>
    <title>How to Use Packing Cubes</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Ever wondered if packing cubes are worth it? In this blog, learn what packing cubes are and how they can help you pack for your next adventure!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-use-packing-cubes">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Packing for a trip can go one of two ways. If you’re a meticulous packer, you may make a detailed packing list before carefully loading your belongings into your suitcase. If you’re a little more laissez-faire, you may toss everything in at the last minute, unbothered by said packing space and call it a day. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No matter which method you gravitate toward, there’s a decent chance that your stuff will get jumbled around during your travels. That’s where </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> come in handy. These revolutionary tools and packing tips can help you pack your suitcase more efficiently and offer you unparalleled organization during your trip. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So what </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">are</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> packing cubes and how do they work? Below, we’ll break it all down for you.</span></p>
<h2><strong>What Are Packing Cubes?</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Put simply, packing cubes are small fabric pouches with zip closures. You can think of them like dresser drawers for your luggage. Rather than tossing everything into one big dark pit (i.e. your suitcase), a travel packing cube allows you to enjoy a little more organization when packing a bag. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, you can use packing cubes to:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Group certain outfits together </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pack different clothing categories together (like pants, shirts, undergarments, etc.)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Separate clean clothes from dirty clothes</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have one designated compartment for your toiletries, electronics, etc. </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With all of your belongings strategically placed in convenient compartments, you’ll have a much easier time finding what you need on your trip. As a result, many packing cube aficionados swear by them. They are well worth the small investment, especially if you choose a durable brand. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/3_ef142f9f-4516-49eb-aaf2-da7369103eb8.png?v=1623324699" alt="shop luggage accessories Blog 4" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>How to Find the Best Packing Cubes</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are many different brands of packing cubes on the market. Each one boasts different features and degrees of quality depending on <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/types-of-luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">types of luggage</a>. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">best </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes come with the following features:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Stiff, durable fabric</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you’re an avid traveler, you want your travel cubes to last for a long time. Choosing a brand that uses durable fabric can make all the difference. A stiff, durable packing cube will hold its shape and keep your items contained. You won’t need to worry about it tearing, ripping, or becoming misshapen after a few uses.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Strong zippers</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Similarly, high-quality packing cubes should come with strong zippers. This way, they will be able to withstand the pressure of containing your clothing and other items for years to come. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A mesh opening </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– By choosing mesh packing cubes, you’ll be able to see exactly what’s inside at a glance. In turn, you won’t need to unpack your entire suitcase or rummage through each packing cube to find your favorite bikini, a clean pair of socks, or whatever else you’re looking for. You’ll be able to pinpoint the right packing cube in a matter of seconds. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Labels </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Some types of packing cubes come with handy labels on the outside. These labels can take your organization up a notch. By clearly labeling each packing cube, you can find what you need faster, whether it’s your glamorous dinner outfit, your beach day supplies, or some comfy athleisure wear. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Handles </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Handles are another helpful packing cube feature you don’t want to miss out on. Packing cubes with handles are much easier to take out of your luggage. Rather than scooping up your chosen packing cube, you can conveniently grab it by its handle instead. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A selection of sizes</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Packing cubes are available in a wide range of sizes. A large packing cube can be big enough to hold your thick winter coats, while a small packing cube is compact enough to contain your tiny toiletries. The best packing cube size is a matter of personal preference. However, it’s nice to have a few different sizes to mix and match with your various belongings.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking for high-quality packing cubes with all of these helpful features, look no further than </span><a href="https://beistravel.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">six-piece packing cube set</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> comes with three packing cubes, two shoe bags, and a small zip pouch. Each piece is made of durable PVC and polyester fabric and comes with strong nylon zippers, mesh peekaboo openings, and convenient label slots. In turn, you can enjoy all of the best packing cube features in one.</span></p>
<h2><strong>The Many Advantages of Using Packing Cubes</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At this point, you may be wondering, “Are packing cubes worth it?” According to many avid travelers, they certainly are. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some of the advantages you can look forward to once you start using packing cubes:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A more efficient packing experience </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– While planning a vacation is an exciting endeavor, packing for one can be a challenge. If you’re wondering how to pack a suitcase efficiently, packing cubes can make all the difference. They give you clear compartments for each of your items and help you save the most space in your suitcase.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Better use of your luggage space</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Speaking of saving space, packing cubes help you do this by compressing your clothing down to a smaller volume. As a result, you can pack more without needing to size up your suitcase. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>An easier time finding things on your trip </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Since packing cubes serve as dresser drawers for your luggage, you won’t need to unpack everything when you get to your final destination if you don’t want to. Instead, you can simply pull items from your packing cubes as needed. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A way to separate dirty and clean clothes</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If your next adventure doesn’t involve a washing machine, chances are you’ll have a growing collection of dirty clothes to drag around with you. Rather than letting them mix in with your clean clothes, you can tuck them away conveniently in a designated dirty clothes packing cube. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>More privacy </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– When you travel, you often have to submit your luggage for inspection. While this is necessary for security reasons, it’s not always fun to think about a TSA agent rummaging through your underwear. By keeping your items stowed away in packing cubes, you can enjoy a little more privacy.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Less likelihood of overpacking </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Roughly 60% of people admit to being chronic overpackers.<sup>1</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> If you’re one of them, you’re certainly not alone. When you’re under pressure to pack everything you need, it’s easy to get carried away with the packing process and toss in some unnecessary items at the end. This can temporarily reduce your packing anxiety, but it may also cost you a ton of money in oversize fees. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rather than stuffing your bag with everything besides the kitchen sink, use packing cubes to help you strategize and plan ahead. You can give each packing cube a purpose and pack it with intention. In turn, you’ll feel more confident that you packed everything you need. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Using packing cubes can level up your travel organization tenfold. Once you get used to the perks of packing cubes, you’ll never want to go back. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s a lot like setting up a dresser in a new house after living with all of your clothes on the ground for a few days—the new and improved organization makes your life a lot easier! </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/packing_cubes_0002_Layer_3_769x1153_crop_center_b86cb757-3c94-46c1-9d16-0098663f7219_480x480.jpg?v=1616093964" alt=""></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>More Ways to Use Packing Cubes</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing cubes can transform your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel luggage</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, but that’s not the only thing they’re good for. They have many useful applications. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, you can use your packing cubes to:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Streamline your linen closet</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Store your off-season clothing</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Organize your child’s toy room</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Simplify your <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-diaper-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">diaper bag backpack</a></span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Spruce up your craft room or home office</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The organizational options for packing cubes are truly endless. </span></p>
<h2><strong>How to Use Packing Cubes</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The best part about packing cubes is that they’re super easy to use. All you have to do is open one up and place your stuff inside. As you zip the packing cube closed, try to squeeze out any excess air. This will help you compress your belongings down in size. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If your packing cubes have a slot for labels, make sure to label them as soon as you can so you don’t forget what’s inside. Your future self will thank you!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you’re done packing, position your collection of packing cubes strategically in your suitcase. If you’re doing it right, it will feel like a game of Tetris. By packing each cube close together, you can use up every inch of your suitcase, duffel bag, or carry-on bag.</span></p>
<h3><strong>Should You Roll Clothes in Packing Cubes?</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Generally, rolling your clothes is the best way to keep them wrinkle-free as you travel. Rolling them will also help them fit comfortably in your packing cubes.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Pack Like a Pro with BÉIS</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing cubes are a simple yet powerful organizational tool that can streamline the packing process significantly. With their help, you can rest easy knowing that everything will be in perfect order the next time you unzip your bag. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They can help you spend</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> less time </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">rummaging through your suitcase and</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> more time</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> enjoying your adventure. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re ready to revolutionize your packing experience with packing cubes, look no further than </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. We offer many different types of luggage. We can set you up in style with our durable </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hardside luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and convenient carry-on bags. </span></p>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>“Overpacking For Holidays.” <i>Villa Plus Blog</i>, 15 May 2019, <a href="https://blog.villaplus.com/2019/05/15/overpacking-for-holidays/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
<div></div>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/essentials-for-any-makeup-bag</id>
    <published>2021-02-23T13:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-05T07:38:55-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/essentials-for-any-makeup-bag"/>
    <title>Essentials For Any Makeup Bag</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Makeup bags can get cluttered and difficult to organize! In this blog, we'll talk through the must-haves for your cosmetic case and how to organize them.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/essentials-for-any-makeup-bag">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re tuned into the online world of beauty gurus, like James Charles and Michelle Phan,<sup>1</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> you may be tempted to accumulate plenty of makeup products in the pursuit of looking your best. However, this can leave you with an overflowing makeup bag that’s hard to organize. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When it comes to your beauty routine and skin care, sometimes less is more.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By going back to basics, you can simplify your makeup bag and organize it properly. In turn, your morning routine will be that much easier.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Below, we’ll review the essential products you should have in your makeup bag and offer a few ways that you can organize them strategically.</span></p>
<h2><strong>Essentials for Makeup Bags</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Everyone has their own set of makeup staples. Here’s a makeup bag essentials list that you can pick and choose from to create your ideal setup. </span></p>
<h3><strong>Face Products</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who doesn’t want flawless, radiant skin? One of the many gifts of makeup is that it can transform your complexion, even on your worst skin days. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some product</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">s</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> essentials for makeup bag that can give you the fresh look you’re searching for:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Face primer</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Face primer isn’t the most exciting beauty product on the market so it's easy to overlook. However, face primer can give your skin a smoother look and keep your makeup looking fresh all day. By adding this product to your list of essentials, you can spend less time on touch-ups throughout the day. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Foundation</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Foundation is truly the “foundation” of flawless skin. It can even your skin tone, brighten your complexion, and mask any imperfections. Depending on your skin type and coverage preference, you can choose a sheer, medium, or full coverage foundation. For example, this best-selling </span><a href="https://www.violetgrey.com/product/vital-skin-foundation-stick/WES-BF2112002" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Westman Atelier Vital Skin Foundation Stick</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> offers a luminous full coverage. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you don’t already have a favorite foundation, many makeup artists would be happy to help you find your perfect match. Once you’ve found the right shade of foundation, you can enjoy flawless skin every day and the confidence that comes with it.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Concealer </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– While foundation can give you a clean slate, sometimes you need a little </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">extra</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> coverage in certain areas. Whether you have dark circles under your eyes or the occasional blemish, a little concealer can do the trick. Like foundation, concealers come in a range of shades, formulas, and coverages. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Bronzer</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Having an even skin tone is one thing, but many people also want some color in their complexion. Bronzer can give you a sun-kissed glow </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">without </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">UV ray damage. If you’re advanced in your makeup application skills, you can even use bronzer to contour your face like the Kardashians.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Highlighter </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Highlighter is another staple product if you want a radiant face. It can give your face a luminescent glow and enhance the dimension of your complexion. Simply add a little highlighter to the tops of your cheeks, the forefront of your nose, below your eyebrows, and in your cupid’s bow. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Blush </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– After concealing and contouring, you may want to add a bit of rosiness back to your cheeks. Blush can help you do just that. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Depending on your skin tone, certain shades of blush will compliment you better than others. If you’re looking for some inspiration, this </span><a href="https://www.violetgrey.com/product/baby-cheeks-blush-stick/WES-BF2617002" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Westman Atelier Baby Cheeks Blush Stick</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> offers six different stunning shades. Once you’ve found your perfect shade, add a touch of it to your cheeks and enjoy your newfound healthy glow.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Setting powder</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – After perfecting your makeup, the last thing you want is for it to fade off throughout the day. A setting powder can ensure that your makeup stays put. Some setting powders even prevent your skin from getting oily during the day or offer moisturizing benefits if you're prone to dry skin. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><strong><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" title="travel bags"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/4.png?v=1617295530" alt="" style="float: none;" width="462" height="231"></a></strong></h3>
<h3><strong>Eye Products</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once your face makeup is ready to go, it’s time to draw some attention to your beautiful eyes. They’re the window to your soul, after all. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some essential eye makeup essentials to include in your makeup bag:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Eye primer </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Like face primer, eye primer gives your eyelids the perfect base for the rest of your eye look, whether you do a sultry smokey eye or something simpler. Primer will also keep your eye makeup from sliding off, getting smudged, or creasing throughout the day.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Eyeshadow </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– The eyes may be the window to the soul, but they’re also the perfect canvas for your cosmetic creativity. Eyeshadows come in many different shades and finishes. While you can experiment with any color of the rainbow, a neutral eyeshadow palette should be on your list of essentials. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Eyeliner </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– After dusting your eyelids with a shimmery shadow, the next step is to line them with a little eyeliner. Not only can eyeliner make your lashes look thicker, but it can also make your eyes pop, especially if you choose the right color. Black eyeliner is a go-to for many people, but brown, dark gray, and deep purple eyeliners can bring out the color of your eyes.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Mascara</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – To finish off the eyes, you need a good mascara, like the luxurious </span><a href="https://www.violetgrey.com/product/eye-love-you-mascara/WES-BE3324001" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Westman Atelier Eye Love You Mascara</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Mascara may be the most essential product in your eye makeup routine. After all, mascara does wonders for your eyes by lengthening, thickening, and darkening your eyelashes. Adding a little mascara can instantly make you look more awake and put together, even if you opt for an otherwise minimal makeup get-up. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Lip Products</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Next, you need to give your lips a little TLC. Here are some essential lip products you should always have on hand:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Lip balm </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– No amount of lip gloss or lipstick can overcompensate for dry, cracked lips. Before you do anything else, start your lip routine with a hydrating lip balm, like this replenishing </span><a href="https://www.violetgrey.com/product/baume-de-rose/BYT-V18300008" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">By Terry Baume de Rose</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This way, your lips won’t get dry or chapped during the day.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Lip gloss </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Lip gloss can add a lovely sheen to your smile and polish off your entire look. As an added bonus, it’s easy to apply, even when you don’t have access to a mirror. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Lipstick</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Even if you don’t wear lipstick every day, having a little lip color or statement lipstick on hand is essential. A bold red or bright pink lipstick can serve as the focal point of your outfit. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Application Products</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After stocking your makeup bag with the essentials, you need the right tools to apply them. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are the basic beauty tools you need: </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Makeup brushes</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – High-quality makeup brushes can help you blend your favorite products like a pro. While high-quality brushes are a little costlier, they are well worth the investment. They will stand the test of time, especially if you clean them regularly and store them properly. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A beauty blender</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – If you prefer using liquid face products, you may also want to add a beauty blender to your applicator arsenal.<sup>2</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> These strategically shaped sponges can give you a flawless finish, free of any streaks or lines. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Tips for Organizing Makeup Bag</strong></h2>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Essentials_For_Any_Makeup_Bag_copy1.jpg?v=1614285215" style="float: none;"></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know the essentials of a well-stocked makeup bag, let’s review some ways you can keep all of your beauty products organized, clean, and easy to find. </span></p>
<h3><strong>Choose the Right Makeup Bag</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When looking for the ideal makeup bag, try to find one that:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Is made of durable material</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Since you're going to use your makeup bag daily, you should invest in one that will stay in good condition. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Is easy to clean </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Makeup can get messy. After a couple of weeks, your makeup bag will probably be covered in shimmery dust and debris. By choosing a cosmetic case that’s easy to clean, you can freshen it up faster and save yourself a lot of trouble. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Has a separate compartment for brushes</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – After investing in high-quality makeup brushes, it's important to take good care of them. You can protect their bristles by storing them in a separate compartment within your makeup bag. This will also ensure that they’re easy to find. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Place Your Makeup Products Inside Strategically</strong></h3>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Essentials_For_Any_Makeup_Bag_copy2.jpg?v=1614285262" style="float: none;"></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you’ve chosen a makeup bag, you need to know how to place your makeup essentials inside of it properly. Here are some helpful organizational tips:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Place larger products at the bottom of your makeup bag and smaller products on top</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Place cotton pads inside your makeup palettes if they have glass mirrors inside (this will keep them from shattering)</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stack palettes and group together long, slender products (like eyeliner, mascara, lipstick, etc.)</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You should also wipe down your products with a makeup wipe every so often and wash your brushes regularly. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By following these tips, you’ll always have a fresh, organized makeup bag ready to go. </span></p>
<h2><strong>Stylishly Store Your <i>Must Haves</i> in Makeup Bags</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Organizing your makeup bag is an easy process once you know these helpful tips and tricks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re ready to treat yourself to a new makeup bag, look no further than the </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÈIS travel makeup &amp; cosmetic case</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This case comes fully-equipped with a separate pocket for brushes, a removable brush holder, and a compact mirror. Best of all, it’s made of easy-to-clean, water-resistant material.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re looking for more stylish </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, BÈIS has plenty to choose from, ranging from our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hardside suitcase sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to our convenient </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">jewelry transport case</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. If you need any tips on <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-pack-jewelry" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">how to pack jewelry</a>, we can help you out with that too. </span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Perelli, Amanda. “The Top 15 Makeup and Beauty YouTubers in the World, Some of Whom Are Making Millions of Dollars.” <i>Business Insider</i>, Business Insider, 6 Aug. 2019, <a href="www.businessinsider.com/beauty-and-makeup-youtube-channels-with-most-subscribers-2019-7." target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bakkila, Blake. “Is a Beautyblender Sponge Really Worth $20?!” <i>Good Housekeeping</i>, 18 Jan. 2019, <a href="www.goodhousekeeping.com/institute/a21898/beauty-blender-review/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
<div></div>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-pack-jewelry</id>
    <published>2021-02-22T13:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:53:53-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-pack-jewelry"/>
    <title>How to Pack Jewelry</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing jewelry can be a challenge especially if you're traveling! Learn how to keep all your special pieces safe, organized, and tangle-free.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/how-to-pack-jewelry">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Half the fun of booking a vacation is daydreaming about it beforehand. During the days leading up to your trip, you can imagine all the Instagrammable moments that await you. What will you do each day? Where will you eat? Most importantly, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">what will you wear</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">? </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As any fashionista knows, no outfit is complete without its finishing touches. Jewelry can take a plain t-shirt and jeans to the next level or glam up an already dazzling dress. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re wondering how to pack jewelry when traveling, it’s important to understand the challenges involved. Jewelry items are fragile, tangle-prone, and easy to lose. Fortunately, we have some tips and tricks for packaging jewelry properly when traveling.</span></p>
<h2><strong>How to Pack Jewelry For Travel</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you love costume jewelry or fine diamonds, you naturally want to keep your special pieces safe, organized, and tangle-free as you travel. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some tips on packaging material to help you do just that:</span></p>
<h2><strong>#1 Choose Your Travel Jewelry Wisely</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First and foremost, you need to decide what jewelry items you’re going to bring with you. It’s tempting to bring all of your favorite pieces. However, you should be cautious about what jewelry you bring on vacation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In some cases, it might be best to leave expensive or precious jewelry at home. Traveling with valuable pieces is not recommended, especially if you’re going somewhere where they could make you a target for theft.<sup>1</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Before you decide to bring a special piece on your trip, ask yourself:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Would I struggle to afford to replace this piece if it got lost or stolen?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Is this piece sentimental to me?</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Would my trip be ruined if this piece went missing?</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you answer “yes” to any of these questions, it might be a better idea to play it safe and leave these high-value items at home.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/3_ef142f9f-4516-49eb-aaf2-da7369103eb8.png?v=1623324699" alt="shop luggage accessories" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<h2><strong></strong></h2>
<h2><strong>#2 Decide Which Jewelry You’re Going to Wear On Your Travel Day</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you absolutely </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">must</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bring a few pricey pieces with you, like your wedding set or everyday necklace, it’s a good idea to wear them while you travel to your destination. This way, they’ll be safely on your person at all times, rather than in an unsupervised suitcase somewhere. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, if your luggage gets lost (</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">fingers crossed it doesn’t</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">), you won’t need to go through the added stress of losing your favorite jewelry pieces. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you know what jewelry you’re going to wear on your travel day, you can start packing the rest of your adornments.</span></p>
<h2><strong>#3 Pack Each Piece of Jewelry Carefully: The DIY Addition</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you’ve chosen the jewelry pieces you’re comfortable traveling with, it’s time to pack them in a way that will ensure they stay organized, protected, and most importantly, untangled! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every piece of jewelry comes with slightly different travel considerations. For example, a delicate necklace is notorious for turning into a tangled mess,<sup>2</sup></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> earrings often lose their backs, and rings can act like secret escape artists if they're not properly stored away. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some useful DIY strategies for packing each type of jewelry:</span></p>
<h3><strong>How to Pack Necklaces</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re wondering how to go about packing necklaces for travel, the secret is to keep them physically separated from one another. You can do so by putting each necklace in its own jewelry case or Ziploc bag. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While this strategy will keep your necklaces from tangling with </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">each other</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, it’s not a foolproof method for preventing tangles within the necklace chain itself. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To accomplish </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">this</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> goal, you have a few options:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The Straw Method</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – One DIY trick is to thread your necklace through a straw and fasten the clasp afterward. The straw will serve as a physical barrier, preventing the chain from getting tangled and knotted together. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The Cling Wrap Method </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– If your travel necklace is too thick for the straw method (most statement necklaces would fall into this category), you can use cling wrap to keep it tangle-free instead. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For this method, simply lay down a large piece of cling wrap and place your necklace on one side of it. Make sure the necklace chain isn’t overlapping anywhere. After that, wrap the other side of the cling wrap over your necklace and press it down to create a cling wrap seal. This seal will keep your necklace in place and tangle-free.</span></p>
<h3><strong>How to Pack Rings</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you decide to bring a few rings with you, it’s important to make sure they don’t get lost in your luggage. These tiny accessories are easy to lose and hard to find. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can keep your rings from wandering off by storing them in a designated jewelry pouch or plastic baggy. If you want to go one step further, consider attaching all of your rings together with a metal O-ring. This will ensure that none of them slip out of the pouch or bag while they’re packed away in your luggage. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another DIY hack for packing rings is to place them in a pill case or mint tin. Just make sure that whatever container you use won’t pop open inside your luggage. </span></p>
<h3><strong>How to Pack Bracelets</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From bangles to beaded bracelets, a little arm candy can instantly jazz up your outfit. However, similar to tangled necklaces, some types of bracelets are more prone to tangling and scratches than others. If your chosen bracelets are slightly malleable, they could also get squished, bent, or damaged under the pressure of the rest of your luggage. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To keep your bracelets safe, simply roll up a small washcloth or towel to create a DIY bracelet display. After that, slide your bracelets onto it and place the display in a large plastic bag. This will keep all of your bracelets from getting squished, scratched, tangled, or lost. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If your travel bracelets aren’t prone to get damaged or tangled, you can simply place them in soft jewelry pouches for safekeeping. </span></p>
<h3><strong>How to Pack Earrings</strong></h3>
<div style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/How_to_Pack_Jewelry_featured_image_copy_image_1.jpg?v=1614286333" style="float: none;"></span></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-weight: 400;"></span></div>
<div style="text-align: left;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Earrings are possibly the trickiest </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel accessories</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to pack. Whether you love studs, hoops, or dangling earrings, these jewels tend to be delicate and easy to lose. The last thing you want is to lose an earring back on your way to your destination.</span>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To prevent these packing problems, you need to get a little creative. Here are some options:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Use a button</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Buttons are a fantastic DIY earring storage solution. Simply insert your earrings into the holes of the button and secure them with the backs. Most buttons have two holes, making them ideal for a pair of earrings. After that, place the bejeweled buttons in a soft jewelry pouch or plastic bag. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Use a piece of cardboard </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Another way you can keep your earrings in one place is by piercing a piece of cardboard with them and fastening them to it. This will create a DIY earring display. After that, place the entire cardboard earring display into a plastic baggy or small bag to ensure none of your earrings fall off and go missing.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Use a pill case </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– As with rings, pillboxes are great earring organizers. Their tiny compartments can help you separate each pair of earrings from one another. Just make sure to seal the compartments securely to prevent them from popping open in your suitcase. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>#4 Simplify the Packing Process With a Hanging Jewelry Organizer</strong></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While all of these DIY jewelry packing tips are viable options, they result in a hodgepodge of different jewelry containers. You can streamline everything significantly by purchasing a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hanging jewelry organizer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. This will enable you to ditch the cumbersome pillboxes, plastic baggies, and other DIY packing solutions for good. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/How_to_Pack_Jewelry_featured_image_copy_image_2.jpg?v=1614286381" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The BÉIS hanging jewelry organizer comes with:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Clear zipper pockets in a variety of sizes</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – With a hanging jewelry organizer, you can swap out your slew of jewelry pouches for a streamlined set of compartments instead. These compartments come in a variety of sizes, giving everything from your statement necklaces to your tiny studs a dedicated home. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since these compartments are clear and connected to one another, they allow you to view all of your travel jewelry from one place. In turn, you’ll never need to unpack your jewels and risk misplacing them. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Soft microfiber lining</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Your jewelry is precious and should be treated with care. That’s why our BÉIS hanging jewelry organizer is lined with soft, gentle microfiber that will keep your delicate jewelry safe and scratch-free.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Necklace hangers</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – To keep the tangles away, our hanging jewelry organizer comes with a designated necklace hanging section. Simply fasten your necklace, slip its pendant in the soft pouch, and secure its chain with the convenient snap tabs. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A hanger hook </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Our hanging jewelry organizer makes settling into your hotel or Airbnb a breeze. All you have to do is unpack your jewelry organizer and hang it up somewhere safe. </span>
</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Pack Your Precious Jewels Like a Pro</strong></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you can see, there are many ways to pack jewelry for your next vacation. If you want the most elegant solution, there’s </span><a href="https://beistravel.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÉIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At BÉIS, we carry a beautiful, top-of-the-line collection of luggage. Whether you need a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hanging jewelry organizer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, a hardshell suitcase set, a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel makeup bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, or a weekend carryall, we can set you up in style. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more travel organization tips, check out our article on the <a href="%20https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/essentials-for-any-makeup-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">essentials for makeup bags</a> next.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources:</b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>Moon, Chris. “Does Homeowners Insurance Cover Damaged or Lost Jewelry?” <i>ValuePenguin</i>, ValuePenguin, 26 June 2020, <a href="www.valuepenguin.com/does-homeowners-insurance-cover-jewelry." target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>TodayShow. “How to Untangle a Necklace - without Losing Your Mind.” <i>TODAY.com</i>, 13 Sept. 2017, <a href="www.today.com/style/how-untangle-necklace-without-losing-your-mind-t116187" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></p>
<div></div>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/ultimate-guide-for-what-to-pack-in-a-carry-on</id>
    <published>2020-11-19T03:37:22-08:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:52:59-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/ultimate-guide-for-what-to-pack-in-a-carry-on"/>
    <title>Ultimate Guide For What to Pack in A Carry On</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Knowing what to pack in a carry-on and packing light doesn't have to be complicated. Learn some simple packing tips and get ready to travel!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/ultimate-guide-for-what-to-pack-in-a-carry-on">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">This content was updated for accuracy and relevance on January 28th, 2021</span></em></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The carry on might just be the GOAT of <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage">luggage</a> types. It’s portable, easy-to-use, and can fit right beside you on your flight. Anyone who has ever flown knows that a carry on is the perfect travel companion. Whether you’re headed on a trip with friends or going on a solo trip for the weekend, <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage/products/the-carry-on-roller-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">carry on luggage</a> can save you packing time and money!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you're expecting a long flight, sometimes checked baggage can save you the headache. But you may be wondering what to bring in a carry on to fulfill your travel needs, while also following TSA and airline guidelines </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> saving space in your <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel bag</a>. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re not good at Tetris, don’t worry. Knowing what to pack in a carry on and packing light doesn't have to be complicated! By using some of these simple </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing tips</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, you’ll quickly find that becoming a carry on connoisseur is easy as pie. So pop open your bag, get ready for takeoff, and read on for our ultimate carry-on packing list guide! </span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What To Pack in a Carry On... Depends on the Carry On!  </span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many people shy away from packing a carry on bag because they’re afraid it won’t hold all the things they want to bring. While it’s true that there is a maximum capacity for carry-ons, it’s actually much larger than you may think even though it fits in an overhead bin. Anything from a tote bag to a medium-sized suitcase can be classified as a carry-on. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For shorter trips, sometimes this is the only bag you need to bring if you know how to pack it correctly. So whether you’re sporting a fun little purse or full-blown luggage, let’s take a look at what you’ll want to put inside your carry on.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We all know <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-reasons-why-traveling-is-important-for-everyone" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">why traveling is important</a> but now that you know the best way to pack a carry on you might be wondering what to bring in a hardside carry on. It often depends on where you’re going and for how long. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br></span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/1.png?v=1619029621" alt="shop BEIS bags" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></p>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tote bag or Purse</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For those who are either packing light or have most of their belongings in a checked bag, bringing a <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/tote-bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tote bag or purse</a> on the plane is a perfect way to ensure all your essentials are accessible. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get the most out of this small carry on, you’ll want to choose a bag that has multiple pockets without compromising on style—you’re going to be strutting around the airport holding this, there’s no reason it can’t look nice! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Take our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Work Tote</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, for example. With two external pockets, a padded laptop sleeve, and a removable zip pouch for smaller items, there’s room for everything you need and more. Plus, it’s sleek, fashionable, and pairs well with almost any outfit.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now it’s time to get down to the nitty-gritty: What do you put in all these pockets? These pockets are a lifesaver for the traveler who is packing light. For a carry on bag this small, it’s important that you pick only the most essential items. This leaves some room for personal preference, but some examples of what you may reach for during a flight include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Laptop and phone</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eye mask</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Portable chargers</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A book or magazine</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earplugs or earbuds</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wallet and passport</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<span style="font-weight: 400;">Keys (the our</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-black"> </a><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-work-tote-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Work Tote</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> has its own key fob so you don’t lose them!)</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All of these items will fit comfortably in a tote-sized carry on, and the right amount of pockets will ensure nothing gets lost or cluttered if you hit any unexpected turbulence. </span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Backpack</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The next step up from a tote bag carry-on is a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">backpack</a>. Choosing to bring a backpack on a plane is great because it holds more than a purse, but—unlike a suitcase—can typically still be stored under your seat while still holding all your travel essentials.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When choosing the perfect carry on backpack, it’s important to find a balance of sleekness and storage. While a bulky backpack may fit a lot of items, you don’t want it so big that it can’t fit comfortably in a tight space.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags/products/the-2-in-1-backpack-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2-in-1 backpack</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> fits the bill on this one. With a convenient front pocket, removable pouch, and spacious interior with a 15” laptop sleeve, it’s surprising how much you can fit in this do-it-all backpack.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All this storage space may have you wondering what to bring (we know; </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">the possibilities are endless</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">). Similar to a tote bag, a classic and stylish backpack such as a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-rucksack-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">rucksack</a> allows you to have easy access to essential items like your phone, toiletries, or a book. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>Packing Tip -</strong> Additionally, you can also fit items such as:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A sweatshirt in case the plane is chilly</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Laptop bag </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hand Sanitizer to keep any unwanted germs away </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A water bottle or another beverage you purchased at the airport</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Any cosmetic items you might need to freshen up</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Larger, over the ear headphones</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Any valuables you don’t want in a checked bag</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A backpack leaves more room for any additional items you want to keep close by, including bulkier items that won’t fit in your tote bag like a travel pillow. If you plan on packing a bit heavier, a backpack may be the way to go.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case?_pos=1&amp;_sid=8a18d2430&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="hanging jewelry case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/body_image_1.jpg?v=1605784974" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carry On Suitcase</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The final evolution of carry on luggage is the hardside suitcase. Choosing a suitcase as your carry on can sometimes be a gamble, even if you’re not flying to Las Vegas. Oftentimes, it’s difficult to determine whether or not your suitcase fits the exact dimensions of a carry on prior to arriving at the airport.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fortunately, at BÈIS we carry a line of hardside luggage specifically designed for carry-on purposes. Our</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-carry-on-roller-in-beige"> </a><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-carry-on-roller-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">21” Carry On Roller suitcase</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> will fit perfectly in any overhead compartment and eliminates the fear of a potential checked bag fee. The Carry On Roller suitcase comes with easy glide 360° spinner wheels, tons of luggage space, a cushioned handle, and even an indicator window that will light up red if you surpass 50 lbs when packing (no battery required)!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With a carry on suitcase, you have the opportunity to ditch a checked bag entirely, even when packing for a longer trip. A rolling bag can be easier on your shoulders too! In a carry on suitcase, one packing tip is bringing along items such as:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clothes (we recommend using packing cubes)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Toiletries (that follow TSA and airport security guidelines)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Electronics</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An extra pair of shoes</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Basically, anything that fits in your suitcase and is allowed inside a carry-on can be packed in this form of luggage. Sometimes opting for a larger carry-on instead of a checked bag is a great way to save time and money on baggage fees. Don't forget to create your carry on packing list beforehand so you don't forget any travel essentials. </span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" title="beige cosmetic case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/body_image_2.jpg?v=1605785021" alt="" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p> </p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">TSA Guidelines</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When packing for a flight, it’s important to understand the TSA rules and regulations regarding what items you can bring. Checked bags typically offer a little more leeway when it comes to packing restrictions. If you’re planning on bringing a carry-on bag, it’s vital to remember these guidelines:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Containers of liquids or creams must contain 3.4 ounces (100 milliliters) or less</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">All liquid items must fit in a 1 quart, clear plastic bag</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">A maximum of 1-quart bag is allowed per passenger</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Electronics must be removed from your bag during TSA screening</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">No food that isn’t purchased at the airport, post-screening</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">No weapons, explosives, or sharp objects</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The TSA has a long list of prohibited and accepted items, so always remember to double-check online if you’re ever unsure about bringing something in your carry on.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Moms Should Pack In Their Carry On</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite extensive restrictions for carry-on items, TSA understands the fact that babies have certain needs that can’t be put on hold because of a flight. This means you don't have to go through the hassle of putting all your child's necessities in your checked luggage.</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">The following items are perfectly acceptable to bring in your carry on:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby formula and breast milk (3.4 ounces or less)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby wipes</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diapers</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby powder</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby carrier</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re a mom searching for the perfect baby-friendly carry-on, look no further than our functional</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black"> </a><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-diaper-bag-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Diaper Bag</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Who said diaper bags have to </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">look</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> like they have diapers in them? This stylish bag comes equipped with tons of pockets to fit essentials for you and your little one. The diaper bag even comes with a built-in teething ring to help avoid any mid-flight meltdowns, especially during a long flight.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">What About Mile High Diaper Changes?</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For baby luggage on the lighter side, try our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-portable-changing-pad?_pos=1&amp;_sid=8b1aaf7b2&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Changing Organizer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. With a portable changing matt, pockets for diapers and wipes, and a slick material that’s perfect for easy cleanup, this product is ultra travel-friendly and makes diaper changes on the go easier than ever.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moms have places to be just like anyone else, and they shouldn’t have to sacrifice their baby’s comfort in order to get there!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hit The Skies in Style with The Best Luggage Brand</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing a carry on has never been easier (or more fashionable) than with BÈIS <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">luggage</a>! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We get it, packing for a flight is stressful. It’s also not the most </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">exciting</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> endeavor. But a good packing job can reduce future stress that could potentially ruin your trip. Our luggage pieces come with enough packing space that you won’t find yourself having to make the tough decision of which pair of boots to leave behind. Save yourself the heartbreak and pack everything you want in your BÈIS bag.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ditch the grueling baggage claim line and start enjoying your vacation by using these helpful tips when packing a carry-on. Good luck, and safe travels!</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Source:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TSA. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Can I Bring? </span></i><a href="https://www.tsa.gov/travel/security-screening/whatcanibring/all" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.tsa.gov/travel/security-screening/whatcanibring/all</span></a></p>
<br><br>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup</id>
    <published>2020-10-12T12:05:44-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-15T13:55:02-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup"/>
    <title>Hacks For How To Pack Toiletries and Makeup</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you have a weekend vacay coming up but aren't sure what and how to pack? Keep reading to learn how to pack toiletries for your next trip!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re headed out for business travel, or you’re packing for your next girls’ trip, you need your favorite face wash, makeup, and hair care products to ensure that your skin and mane look their best while you’re away from home. It all comes down to having <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" title="travel luggage">travel luggage</a> that sets up for packing success.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With today’s TSA restrictions, making it through security with each and every product can be quite a feat. And beyond the risk of confiscation, you don’t want to end up with a concealer or your go-to curl cream ruining half the clothes you’ve packed in your </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="travel bag"><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How can you make sure your deodorant, sunscreen, and makeup all arrive at their final destination? Don’t sweat it! We’ve assembled this guide on how to pack toiletries and makeup so that you can pack your essentials without worrying about TSA requirements, spills, or space.</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span data-slate-leaf="true">Without further ado, here's the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">best way to pack toiletries for travel</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">. Learn how to travel with </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">makeup</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyV2l0aG91dCUyMGZ1cnRoZXIlMjBhZG8lMkMlMjBoZXJlJ3MlMjB0aGUlMjBiZXN0JTIwd2F5JTIwdG8lMjBwYWNrJTIwdG9pbGV0cmllcyUyMGZvciUyMHRyYXZlbC4lMjBMZWFybiUyMGhvdyUyMHRvJTIwdHJhdmVsJTIwd2l0aCUyMG1ha2V1cCUyQyUyMHRvaWxldHJpZXMlMkMlMjBhbmQlMjBhbGwlMjB5b3VyJTIwZXNzZW50aWFsJTIwYmVhdXRpZnlpbmclMjBsaXF1aWRzJTIwYW5kJTIwZ2VscyUyMGFjY29yZGluZyUyMHRvJTIwVFNBJTIwcmVndWxhdGlvbnMhJTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA==">, toiletries, and all your essential beautifying liquids and gels according to TSA regulations!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">To Get Started, Survey Your Toiletries</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you wondering how to pack makeup for air travel? First things first—size matters.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When it comes to carry-on, you’re restricted in both the size of your toiletries and in the total amount of liquid, gel, and cream you carry on.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The TSA </span><a href="https://www.tsa.gov/travel/frequently-asked-questions/what-3-1-1-liquids-rule" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">explains</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> the “3-1-1 liquids rule” as follows:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You are allowed to bring a quart-sized bag of liquids, aerosols, gels, creams and pastes through the checkpoint. These are limited to 3.4 ounces (100 milliliters) or less per item.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why is it called the 3-1-1 rule? Each passenger is allowed:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">3.4 oz items</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 1 quart-sized plastic bag</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1 bag allowed per passenger</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This translates to about nine 3-oz items (since there are 32 oz in a quart). To break it down further, 3-oz items are those travel-size </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">bathroom items, or reusable bottles, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">found at most convenience stores. However, depending on the size of each container or liquids bag , you may have room for a few more or less toiletries.</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/3.png?v=1619029886" alt="shop luggage accessories" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The good news? You can also place additional full- and travel-sized liquids in any luggage you’re checking. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><span data-slate-leaf="true">To get started </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">packing</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> toiletries</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyVG8lMjBnZXQlMjBzdGFydGVkJTIwcGFja2luZyUyMHRvaWxldHJpZXMlMjBhbmQlMjB0JTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA=="> and t</span>o maximize your space, decide what to check and what to carry on. Start by making a list of your liquid, cream, and gel travel essentials, including:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Contact solution</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Toothpaste</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sunscreen</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shampoo or dry shampoo</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conditioner</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shower Gel</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Styling products</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Face wash</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moisturizer</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Night cream</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under-eye cream</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Primer</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Foundation or BB cream</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Concealer</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mascara</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brow gel</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nail polish</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perfume</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We recommend packing your most irreplaceable products </span><span data-slate-leaf="true">like </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">moisturizer</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">face wash</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, or </span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyJTIwbGlrZSUyMG1vaXN0dXJpemVyJTJDJTIwZmFjZSUyMHdhc2glMkMlMjBvciUyMHRvb3RocGFzdGUlMjAlMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">liquid foundation</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> </span>in your carry-on bag. While you hope checked luggage will be at baggage claim when you arrive, something can always go wrong. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you arrive at your destination without toothpaste</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (or toothbrush!)</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, it's easy enough to buy a tube, or even use the complimentary option in your hotel. But going a few days without your favorite makeup and moisturizer is a little more inconvenient. And if your suitcase goes missing permanently , you could lose hundreds of dollars worth of cosmetics.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once you decide what to carry on and what to pack, the next step is learning how to organize toiletries in your luggage </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">without</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> risking spills.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maximize Space With Travel Size, Refillables and Solids</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have you narrowed down the list of what you need to pack in your 1-quart carry-on bag?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you feel like you have </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">twice</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> as many cosmetics as can fit, you’re not alone.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Figure out how to economize space by bringing only the products you need.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More manufacturers than ever now put their perfumes, CC creams, and smoothing balms in TSA-compliant 3.4 oz containers. However, you may not really need 3.4 oz for a short overnight trip. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-cosmetic-case?_pos=7&amp;_sid=8833ec563&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="hanging cosmetic case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Hacks_1_480x480.jpg?v=1602524289" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Try a few different strategies to make sure each product is as petite as possible:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Invest in travel-sized products </span>– It’s easy to get a teensy tube of toothpaste or mouthwash to take with you during travel. There are also a travel-sized skincare product options.</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Switch from liquid to solid</span> – Solid perfume, facial soap, makeup remover (makeup wipes), and even shampoo and conditioner can be your best friends when it comes to travel toiletries. Every solid item you bring is one less liquid in your quart sized bag—and one less goopy spill to worry about in your luggage. Just be sure to place any solid toiletries in a plastic bag of their own to avoid residue on your clothes.<br><br>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Try refillable containers</span> – It’s easier than ever to find chic, refillable containers to deposit a smidge of your sunscreen or perfume. Made of soft silicone and other spill-proof materials, you’ll never have to worry about a fancy glass bottle breaking again!<b> <br><br></b>
</li>
<li>Now that you’ve downsized your collection, you’re ready to stash it in your luggage!</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pack Your Carry-On</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, you know exactly what you’re going to put in your hand luggage.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But what are you going to put it </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">in?</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many of us have gotten away with putting a regular, old makeup bag jam-packed with liquids through security. However, there’s nothing worse than finding you’re in a security line with sticklers who rifle through your non-compliant bag in great detail, swabbing and scanning every item. This could delay your connection or even make you miss your flight!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That's why you need a travel toiletry </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">kit </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">that contains a reusable, TSA-compliant clear pouch.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A hanging </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/makeup-cosmetic-cases" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">cosmetic travel bag</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is perfect for the traveler who needs to pack </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">all</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> her cosmetics for the weekend away. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Designed for ladies who want to keep their hair, skin, and makeup on point, the BÈIS hanging </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">toiletry</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bag features:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<b>A unique hanging design</b><span> – use the hanger to set up your case in your hotel room and enjoy the next best thing to your medicine cabinet. </span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">A</span><span style="font-weight: bold;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;">TSA-complaint pouch</span><span> –</span>Pop this clear bag out of your carry-on at a moment's notice to make sure your travel-size <span style="font-weight: 400;">liquid</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> toiletries get through the security checkpoint in the blink of an eye.</span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Three compartments</span><span> – It’s easy to stash powdered makeup, hairbrushes, and more in your makeup case alongside your liquid cosmetics. Use the compartments to spread out and see all the components of your beauty routine at once.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<p> <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-cosmetic-case?_pos=7&amp;_sid=8833ec563&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="beige cosmetic case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Hacks_2_480x480.jpg?v=1602524330" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Organize Your Checked Bag</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You may need to place any cosmetic overflow into your checked luggage. Besides, if you’re going on a long trip, it makes perfect sense to take full-size versions of your contact solution, shampoo, body wash, and more. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The key is to make sure they don’t leak all over your clothes, requiring you to invest in a dry cleaner (or maybe a whole new wardrobe) when you arrive!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Try these <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" title="luggage packing tips">luggage </a></span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" title="luggage packing tips"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing tips</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to avoid dreaded spills:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Maximize space from the get-go</span><span>. Do you have to sit on your luggage to get it closed? There’s a better way. Use </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="font-weight: bold;" title="packing cubes">packing cubes</a> </span>to compress and organize your clothing into neat squares and rectangles so that you're not squeezing your hair <span style="font-weight: 400;">product </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">between your heels and leather jacket. Using a packing cube to group certain clothes together also makes finding the perfect outfit that much easier at your destination!<br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Cover the opening</span><span>. We know—your cosmetics already </span><i style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">have</span></i><span> lids. But you can add another layer of protection by opening each bottle and placing a piece of flexible saran wrap underneath it. Be sure not to stretch it too tightly, so there’s a little room for the liquid to expand. Trust us: losing a little bit of product in the plastic wrap is much better than risking an all-out explosion in your travel bag!<br><br></span>
</li>
<li>
<span style="font-weight: bold;">Buy a </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-dopp-kit-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="font-weight: bold;" title="dopp kit">dopp kit</a><span>. The best way to pack toiletries in a suitcase is to place them in a leak-proof bag. A zippered bag with sturdy sides ensures that spillage will never make its way into your suitcase. Our dopp kit excels in the hotel room, too. Place it on the bathroom vanity or use the snap-loop to hang it from your towel rod, so you never have to worry about your favorite vacation perfume cascading from the narrow sink.</span><b> <br> </b>
</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Travel Light, Travel Smart and Enjoy Your Trip</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overpacking is incredibly tempting. When you’re visiting a new city, you might feel like you need a full arsenal of hair products—mousse, pomade, hairspray, the works—not to mention every eyeshadow in your collection so you can make sure your look matches your mood.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We completely sympathize!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, there's nothing more stressful than having to throw out products to make it through security, or realizing you need to check an extra bag for your return flight after you've purchased one too many products on your trip! Set yourself up for success and make a </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">toiletries packing</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> list before you start packing.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Avoid the temptation to stash nail polish, lip balm and face serums in the little pockets of your suitcase. Pack your toiletries in a TSA-approved </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">toiletries</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> bag </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">or ziplock bag</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that's easily accessible from your carry on bag. If there's anything that won't fit, you'll just have to treat yourself to a manicure or blow-out on your trip, won't you? Now that's how you start a trip.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stress-Free Travel with BÈIS</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Embarking on a new adventure (did someone say <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" title="girls trip">girls trip</a>?) can give you a break from the everyday stress, allowing you to recharge your batteries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">getting there</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> can be stressful—from making your packing list and checking it twice to dealing with long lines at security and impossibly short layovers.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And the wrong luggage can make the stress even worse.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you ready to upgrade your travel game so that you can always hit the road with ample space, amazing organization, and style? At BÈIS, our </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" title="luggage sets"><span style="font-weight: 400;">luggage sets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" title="travel accessories"> travel </a><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">accessories</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> combine form and function.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you know your essential travel toiletries, skin care and beauty products are on lock, it’s that much easier to travel stress-free.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Arneson, Krystin. “The 8 Best Travel Toiletry Bottles of 2020.” TripSavvy. <a href="www.tripsavvy.com/best-travel-toiletry-bottles-4772308" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a><br><br></span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">“What Is the 3-1-1 Liquids Rule?”. Transportation Security Administration. <a href="www.tsa.gov/travel/frequently-asked-questions/what-3-1-1-liquids-rule" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">URL</a></span></li>
</ol>
<br><br><br>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier</id>
    <published>2020-05-27T09:30:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T11:34:30-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier"/>
    <title>Genius Luggage Packing Tips You Wish You Knew Earlier</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you excited about your upcoming trip? Shay Mitchell and the rest of the BÈIS team put together the ultimate list of packing tips!</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Whether you travel once a week or once a year, it feels like packing <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" title="travel luggage">travel luggage</a> never gets easier. Chances are, you’re one of two types of travelers: the chronic over-packer who gets ready way in advance, or the last-minute packer who throws whatever’s clean in a bag an hour before boarding your plane. </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Either way, you’re causing yourself unnecessary stress. Believe it or not, you can actually enjoy packing for vacation, you just need to learn how to do it well. Let us share some pro luggage packing tips!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether you’re traveling with a carry-on bag under your arm, an entire <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" title="luggage set">luggage set</a>, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">travel bags, or <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/weekender" title="weekender bags">weekender bags</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, we’ve got the packing tips to make every trip feel as relaxing as a beach vacation, even before you leave home. Keep reading to learn all the travel packing hacks you’ll ever need to avoid extra baggage fees!</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Are Some Travel Packing Tips and Tricks?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hopping from flight to flight year-round makes you pretty great at packing a bag. If you watch Harper’s Bazaar’s Little Black Book series, you know Shay’s a self-proclaimed professional packer. Trust us, we’ve seen it go down and it is impressive. Check out this video to see Shay show how to pack for a trip and share her travel essentials for women.</span></p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6A7S4bkrgmQ" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keep reading for some packing tips inspired by the expert herself—starting with packing checklists.</span></p>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing Checklist: Carry-On Travel Bag</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, you’ll want to pick a travel bag with multiple compartments and the storage capabilities of a Mary Poppins bag, like our</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-weekender-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">weekend bag</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. You’ll want an outer pocket to keep things you’ll need easy access to, like your phone and headphones, and a separate zipper compartment at the bottom for shoes and workout equipment that you don’t want touching the rest of your stuff. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then, the rest goes in the main compartment. In case you’re wondering, “</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">What should I start packing first?” </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">we broke the packing down into two smaller steps. </span></p>
<p><b>Important travel tip:</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> always remember to put your heavy items on the bottom and more fragile items, or lighter items on the top. We know that seems self-explanatory, but you'd be surprised how easy that tip is to forget when packing. </span></p>
<br>
<h4><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing Method: Bags Within Bags</span></i></h4>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Resist the urge to throw everything into the main compartment and create an organized system that’ll keep everything clean and easy to find, and save extra space. In fact, don't be afraid to bring extra bags if you're going on a big trip. <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" title="Hardside luggage sets" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hardside luggage sets</a> are a great, easy way to keep all your belongings organized. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are the items that should either have a designated place in your bag, or that you should group together into smaller bags yourself:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Essentials </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Keep your small items such as your wallet, passport holder, and sunglasses in a zipper pocket inside the main compartment to keep them extra safe and easy to locate.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Electronics </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Put your laptop or tablet in the padded computer sleeve inside your bag.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>A “staying alive bag”</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Take a quart-sized ziploc bag or a small zippered pouch and fill it with daily vitamins and supplements (like turmeric, vitamin C, or probiotics) and tea bags. All the essentials for when that check in luggage inevitably goes missing at the bag carousel!</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Germ protection</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Keep another small bag of disinfecting wipes and hand sanitizer so you can clean down your seat and tray table, and do a once-over on high-touch surfaces in the hotel room—Shay even brings a shower cap to put over the remote.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="text-align: left;">
<strong>Toiletries</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– A </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">spill-proof <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-dopp-kit-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">dopp kit</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (toiletry bag) for smaller items like deodorant, a pill organizer, a toothbrush and toothpaste, your daily skincare routine, and face masks to use in-flight.<br></span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="text-align: left;">
<strong>Cosmetics</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">–</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">A </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">multi-tasking <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">makeup case</a></span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to hold your makeup and brushes.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><span data-slate-leaf="true">Ready to take an even deeper dive into learning <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup" title="How to Pack Toiletries and Makeup">how to </a></span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup" title="How to Pack Toiletries and Makeup"><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">pack</span></span></a><span data-slate-leaf="true"><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup" title="How to Pack Toiletries and Makeup"> toiletries and makeup</a>? We have all the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">packing</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> hacks</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> you need for your next </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">trip</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyUmVhZHklMjB0byUyMHRha2UlMjBhbiUyMGV2ZW4lMjBkZWVwZXIlMjBkaXZlJTIwaW50byUyMGxlYXJuaW5nJTIwaG93JTIwdG8lMjBwYWNrJTIwdG9pbGV0cmllcyUyMGFuZCUyMG1ha2V1cCUzRiUyMFdlJTIwaGF2ZSUyMGFsbCUyMHRoZSUyMHBhY2tpbmclMjBoYWNrcyUyMHlvdSUyMG5lZWQlMjBmb3IlMjB5b3VyJTIwbmV4dCUyMHRyaXAuJTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA==">.</span></span></p>
<a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-cosmetic-case-beige" target="_blank" title="cosmetic case" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Cosmetics_large.png?v=1591278782" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </a>
<ul></ul>
<h4><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Throw the Rest in</span></i></h4>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Okay, now here are the things you throw in:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Charging supplies</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> – Chargers for your phone, laptop, or tablet, at least one portable power bank, and a travel adapter.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>An extra pair of headphones</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Bluetooth headphones are great for your devices, but you’ll also want regular 3.5mm headphones, just in case you want to use the in-flight entertainment system. Don’t make yourself decide if the latest Oscar-winner is worth putting on the $2 headphones you buy from the airline.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Reading materials</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Besides any work-related reading you need to do, bring a journal or calming book, a highlighter, and a pen.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Snack setup</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– You shouldn’t rely on a bag of four mini pretzels and a tiny cup of water to sustain you throughout the flight. Bring a reusable water bottle to use at the airport, pack snacks, some napkins or tissues, mints or gum, and most importantly, some Shay-approved hot sauce to-go.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Nap-time must-haves</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– Pack a pair of socks or slippers to keep your toes from freezing, a sleep mask, hair scrunchie, and travel or neck pillow. Bring a silk or copper pillowcase for when you arrive, seeing as the </span><a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/beauty-skin-care/pillowcase-benefits#copper-pillowcases" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">medically-backed benefits</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> will totally hide the fact you didn’t sleep on the plane because of all the crying babies.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h3><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing Checklist: Checked Luggage</span></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that we’ve got the hand luggage out of the way, the checked bag will be a breeze—thanks to the fact that with checked bags, there’s one major travel packing tip to rule them all: </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="packing cubes"><span style="font-weight: 400;">packing cubes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. There’s a reason travel packing tips always include them. It's a huge luggage space saver that keeps you organized when you're packing your bags and unpacking them at your destination. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Essentially, you’re following the bags within bags concept for the carry-on, except each type of clothing goes together in whatever size cube you need (shirts with shirts, pants with pants...you get the idea). And that’s it. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How’s that for an easy packing list?</span></p>
<br>
<h4><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Use Packing Cubes</span></i></h4>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Packing cubes are the best way to pack a suitcase so you can kiss your years of folding goodbye (and wearing crunchy-looking blouses to dinner) and roll your clothes. Seriously. Choose the size of the packing cube you’ll need and then roll each item, packing them tightly side by side, but not overcrowding. This will keep your clothes from moving around too much when your bag is inevitably tossed around during travel (which will help prevent wrinkles).</span></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/2.png?v=1619029735" alt="shop luggage" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Do You Save Space When Packing? (Besides Packing Cubes)</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saving suitcase space is the name of the game when it comes to packing a travel bag, especially if you’re planning on shopping. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And honestly, who isn’t?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some packing tips that’ll make your trip a whole lot less stressful:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Strategic outfit planning </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Bring neutral colored basics that you can re-wear and statement pieces to pair with them, so you create multiple outfits with the same clothes.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>The three shoe rule </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Decide on one color of shoes that will go with all your outfits, and then only pack shoes that are that color. Most trips only require three pairs of shoes: casual shoes, going-out shoes, and sneakers.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Lighten up your checked baggage </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">– Wear your heaviest shoes to the airport, and switch them out for the socks or slippers in your carry-on bag during the flight. Between the heavy shoes you’re wearing and the sneakers you have with you, you’ll have enough room to bring a fourth pair home. Wink wink.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Bring scarves</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– They take up basically no space, add a new element to clothes you’re re-wearing, have multiple uses (like a sarong for the beach), are great for unpredictable weather changes, and are fantastic for countries or events that require a little more cover up.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Get a collapsible bag</strong> <span style="font-weight: 400;">– A foldable <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-garment-bag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">garment bag</a> is a great way to bring a bag for the beach, gym, or local markets without trying to squeeze yet another thing into your suitcase.<br><br></span>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>Pack liquids together</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - our luggage, travel backpack, and several other bags come with a water-resistant plastic pouch built right in so you don’t have to worry about minty toothpaste explosions all over your brand new tops. We’ve all been there.</span>
</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How Should I Pack for 60 Days?</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fitting enough clothes for one month between two carry-ons and a checked bag is doable, but what about two months? Before you go searching for a second large suitcase, there’s a much easier alternative. Long-term travel packing hacks are the same as they are for a regular trip, except… you do laundry. </span><span data-slate-leaf="true">Don't forget to make a <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women" title="List of Stylish Travel Essentials">list of stylish </a></span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women" title="List of Stylish Travel Essentials"><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">travel</span></span></a><span data-slate-leaf="true"><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women" title="List of Stylish Travel Essentials"> essentials</a> you won't be able to live without to make sure you aren't missing something important like a </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">laundry </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">bag</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyRG9uJ3QlMjBmb3JnZXQlMjB0byUyMG1ha2UlMjBhJTIwbGlzdCUyMG9mJTIwc3R5bGlzaCUyMHRyYXZlbCUyMGVzc2VudGlhbHMlMjB5b3UlMjB3b24ndCUyMGJlJTIwYWJsZSUyMHRvJTIwbGl2ZSUyMHdpdGhvdXQlMjB0byUyMG1ha2UlMjBzdXJlJTIweW91JTIwYXJlbid0JTIwbWlzc2luZyUyMHNvbWV0aGluZyUyMGltcG9ydGFudCUyMGxpa2UlMjBhJTIwbGF1bmRyeSUyMGJhZyElMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE">!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are laundry facilities at most hotels, rentals, and even hostels. You can easily find a local dry cleaner too. If you’re worried about something happening to an expensive, one-of-a-kind, or sentimental piece during the away-from-home laundry process, don’t wash those items until you’re back. Just make sure to bring clothes you do feel comfortable washing, that way you have something to re-wear.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are some traveling tips for doing laundry on a trip:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dirty clothes bags (one for regular clothes, one for dry clean only). Our luggage comes with a Dirty Bag, you’re welcome.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Make sure you have the local currency so you can support small businesses that don’t take credit cards.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Buy detergent when you get there, but if you want to bring dryer sheets, add one to every cube to keep things fresh, and then use them when the time comes.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re doing your own laundry, consider bringing mesh laundry bags, a travel clothesline, and a travel steamer to take care of your delicates.</span></li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Stop Overpacking</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have to make peace with leaving things behind and worry more about how efficiently we’re packing rather than how much stuff we can squeeze into a suitcase. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><span data-slate-leaf="true">It's time to say goodbye to the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">luggage</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> scale</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIySXQncyUyMHRpbWUlMjB0byUyMHNheSUyMGdvb2RieWUlMjB0byUyMHRoZSUyMGx1Z2dhZ2UlMjBzY2FsZSElMjAlMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE">! </span>Psychologist and author </span><a href="https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Laura Fielding</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> says that most people are “aiming to cover their butts when they pack", yet they're all capable of packing light. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We’ve been taught that if we’re going into the unknown, we have to be prepared for absolutely everything. But in your day-to-day life, are you ever prepared for </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">everything? </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who hasn’t been stuck in unexpected traffic, or showed up to a party underdressed, or spilled red wine on literally anything? And we all lived to tell the story.</span></p>
<br>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Being Efficient with BÈIS</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now that you know how to pack a suitcase efficiently for a day trip, long trip or weekend trip </span><span data-slate-leaf="true">(need a few <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" title="Girls Trip Ideas">dreamy </a></span><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" title="Girls Trip Ideas"><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant">girls </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">trip</span></span></span></a><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyKG5lZWQlMjBhJTIwZmV3JTIwZHJlYW15JTIwZ2lybHMlMjB0cmlwJTIwaWRlYXMlM0YpJTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA=="><a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" title="Girls Trip Ideas"> ideas</a>?)</span>, what was your favorite packing tip? Remember, traveling efficiently means focusing on quality over quantity. That goes for what you’re packing, and what bags you’re packing it in. Having the travel gear to pack better gets rid of all that stress you feel right before going on a trip—but you shouldn’t have to sacrifice a fashionable form for a bag with great function.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At </span><a href="https://beistravel.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BÈIS</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, you can get beautiful multi-purpose travel bags and luggage that are just as stylish as they are crafty. From toiletry bags to a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-passport-holder-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">passport holder</a>, to roller luggage fully equipped with weight indicators and TSA-approved locks, you aren’t just looking good, but you’re traveling like a pro.</span><br><br><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li>
<span>Healthline. </span><i><span>It’s Time to Add Silk or Cotton Pillowcases to Your Sleep Routine</span></i><span>. </span><span><a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/beauty-skin-care/pillowcase-benefits#copper-pillowcases" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.healthline.com/health/beauty-skin-care/pillowcase-benefits#copper-pillowcases</a></span>
</li>
<li>
<span>Vox. </span><i><span>The psychology behind over-(and under-) packing</span></i><span>. </span><a href="https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>https://www.vox.com/the-goods/2020/1/16/21065669/psychology-over-under-packing</span></a>
</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
