<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/tagged/travel-essentials-for-women.atom"/>
  <title>Béis - News</title>
  <updated>2021-05-26T15:17:49-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Béis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women</id>
    <published>2020-05-12T08:30:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-10T23:12:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women"/>
    <title>15 Stylish Travel Essentials for Women</title>
    <author>
      <name>Alexandra Koury</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taking you from the airport runway to the fashion runway. Read on for our holy grail list of travel essentials for women!</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/15-stylish-travel-essentials-for-women">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><em>This content was updated for accuracy and relevance on December 30th, 2020</em></p>
<p>Most women have a hard time packing light. As female travelers, we usually have more toiletries, <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="travel accessories">travel accessories</a>, and shoes. We also like to disinfect everything, be prepared for sickness or injury, and bring back a little something for everyone. There’s nothing wrong with that—in fact, it’s kind of incredible. The ability to pull an overweight checked bag up a cobblestone street at a 30-degree incline… that’s the stuff superheroes are made of. </p>
<p>But there’s an easier way.</p>
<p>We've created a list of travel essentials for women so you’ll still be able to bring everything you need but in a more productive way. These 15 travel items for women will help your packing checklist be organized and efficient, while keeping you prepared and keeping your vacation look on point. <span data-slate-leaf="true">Read on as we explain </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">how to </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">pack</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> light and stylish for your next trip on the road or to the beach. Or, if you're planning a weekend <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/10-dreamy-girls-trip-ideas-across-america" title="Girls Trip Ideas">girl's trip</a> these packing tips are exactly for you! </span></span></p>
<br>
<h2>#1 A Hard Shell Suitcase</h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Hard_shell_suitcase_large.png?v=1591276262" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Whether you need a carry-on or check-in sized suitcase, having durable and functional <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage" title="travel luggage">travel luggage</a> on wheels is the most important of all travel necessities for women—here’s why:</p>
<ul>
<li>You never have to put unnecessary strain on your body carrying a heavy bag around. These roll like a dream with Hinomoto 360 wheels.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Your <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-carry-on-roller-in-beige" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">carry-on</a> travel bag or purse can easily sit on top of it. All our bags are made with trolley sleeves to slide right over your handle.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>If you have checked luggage, the hard shell will hold everything in place.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Some luggage, like the BÈIS Carry-On and Check-In Rollers have a ton of packing space and a built-in TSA lock and a weight indicator, which means no more heavy lifting, overweight baggage fee surprises, or cuttable padlocks, and no more sacrificing style.</li>
</ul>
<br>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/luggage-bundle" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="Hardside luggage">Hardside luggage</a> also gives you a wider variety of color and design options, which helps your bag stand out in a sea of soft, black suitcases. You’ll never have to tie a ribbon around your handle again just so you know which one’s yours, and you’ll know right away if someone tries to walk off with your bag. Now you know the benefits of hard shell luggage, but do you know the best <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/genius-packing-tips-you-wish-you-knew-earlier" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">packing tips and tricks</a> for them?</p>
<br>
<h2>#2 Packing Cubes</h2>
<p><a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-packing-cubes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="packing cubes">Packing cubes</a> are the talk of the town these days and should be on everyone’s ultimate packing list, and for a good reason. There are various sizes, depending on the set you get, and will change your life forever. You’ll maximize your luggage space, stay organized, and avoid overpacking.</p>
<p>Here are some tips for packing cubes:</p>
<ul>
<li>For a carry-on suitcase (one-week vacation), you’ll probably only need three or four cubes, but if you’re checking a bag (two-week vacation), you should look at sets of six or seven.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Pick a packing cube size for each type of clothing item, so they all stay together.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Roll (don’t fold) each piece of clothing and pack them in so they’re snug—it’s a great way to use all your space, prevent wrinkling, and stay organized once you’ve arrived.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Play luggage Tetris and place your capsule wardrobe cubes inside your suitcase.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Throw the cubes in the wash when you get home and store them inside one another.</li>
</ul>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/accessories" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/3.png?v=1619029886" alt="shop luggage accessories" style="float: none;"></a></div>
<h2></h2>
<h2>#3 A Versatile Weekender</h2>
<p>When it comes to travel bags for women, an efficient, stylish, carry-on sized travel bag like the BÈIS <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-weekender-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Weekender</a> is a must. There’s a reason it’s our best seller! It lets you store tons of stuff without looking bulky, making it the only bag you’ll need for a quick trip and the perfect addition to your roller bags for a long flight.</p>
<p>Here’s why weekenders are the ultimate travel bag, depending on the length of your trip:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Weekend trip</strong> – With a separate compartment for shoes at the bottom, you can bring a spare pair and keep all the clothes you’ll need clean in the main compartment. You won’t need to pack a second shoe bag unless you want to.<br><br>
</li>
<li>
<strong>One-week trip</strong> – Between your carry-on roller and your weekender bag, you’ll have plenty of space to hold everything, and still have room for souvenirs.<br><br>
</li>
<li>
<strong>Two-week trip</strong> – If you’re planning on doing international travel, you probably have to take a longer flight to get there. Having a bag that can hold a ridiculous amount of travel gear (while still looking cute) is exactly what you need for a big travel day, and you’ll be able to fit it all under the seat in front of you.</li>
</ul>
<b> </b><br>
<p><i>Don’t forget to look into travel insurance if you’re planning an international trip. </i></p>
<br>
<h2>#4 Bluetooth Noise Canceling Headphones</h2>
<p>You may already have Bluetooth headphones, but the benefit of having noise-canceling ones is that they can double as earplugs since you can turn on the noise-cancellation feature even if you’re not listening to anything. </p>
<br>
<h2>#5 Portable Charger</h2>
<p>Travel tip: a portable power bank is a super great travel accessory for women and men to stay on the grid while you’re on the go. If you have multiple devices, like a phone, Bluetooth headphones, and a tablet, you should use <a href="https://www.pcmag.com/news/the-best-portable-chargers-and-power-banks-for-2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">this guide</a> to figure out exactly what size, capacity, and number of ports you need. Is there anything worse than being stuck in a new city with a dead phone?</p>
<br>
<h2>#6 Reusable Water Bottle</h2>
<p>Bringing a reusable water bottle when traveling is a great way to save money, reduce your impact on the environment, and stay hydrated while you’re on the go. </p>
<p>These are two of the best water bottle picks for travel:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<b>CrazyCap </b>– This brand’s rechargeable sanitation system purifies your drinking water in anywhere between one to two and a half minutes, depending on the sterilization mode, and has an auto-clean function using built-in UV light. The best part? It’s actually all in the cap and is compatible with tons of popular water bottle brands like S’well, so you can buy the cap alone if you want.<br><br>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">
<strong>S’well</strong> – Insulated, condensation-free, and leakproof, this eco-friendly water bottle comes in many different sizes and is guaranteed not to ruin anything else in your bag. Plus, it’s compatible with CrazyCap, so you can still keep that option open.</li>
</ul>
<b> </b><br>
<h2>#7 High-Quality Dopp Kit</h2>
<p>Some things get better with age: wine, cheese, the duo of Martha Stewart and Snoop Dogg...but other things should stay the way they were, and toiletry bags are one of them. From a flat bottom to a wide opening, a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/beis-dopp-kit-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="dopp kit">dopp kit</a> is a classic toiletry kit that can hold all of your travel size, essential toiletries for vacation <span data-slate-leaf="true">(i.e. </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">body wash</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">toothpaste</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">shower gel</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">face wash</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, sunscreen, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">conditioner</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">shampoo</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">nail clippers</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyKGkuZS4lMjBib2R5JTIwd2FzaCUyQyUyMHRvb3RocGFzdGUlMkMlMjBzaG93ZXIlMjBnZWwlMkMlMjBmYWNlJTIwd2FzaCUyQyUyMGNvbmRpdGlvbmVyJTJDJTIwc2hhbXBvbyUyQyUyMG5haWwlMjBjbGlwcGVycyUyQyUyMGV0Yy4pJTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA==">, etc.)</span>. <span data-slate-leaf="true">Break up with the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">ziploc </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">bag</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyQnJlYWslMjB1cCUyMHdpdGglMjB0aGUlMjB6aXBsb2MlMjBiYWclMjBhbmQlMjB1cGdyYWRlJTIwdG8lMjBhJTIwRG9wcCUyMEtpdCUyMiU3RCU1RCUyQyUyMnR5cGUlMjIlM0ElMjJwYXJhZ3JhcGglMjIlN0QlNUQ="> and upgrade to this amazing travel product.</span></p>
<br>
<h2>#8 Electric Toothbrush</h2>
<p>Electric toothbrushes, on the other hand, have gotten better with time. They’re compact, powerful, and sometimes even come with a dual-purpose travel case and toothbrush stand. Plus, most can last a week or more on a single charge.</p>
<br>
<h2>#9 Cosmetic Case</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Cosmetic_Case_large.png?v=1591276328" alt=""></p>
<p>Travel beauty essentials beyond a nice toiletry bag include <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/makeup-cosmetic-cases" title="makeup bag"><span style="font-weight: 400;">makeup bags</span></a>, brush holders, and a compact mirror. Purchasing a <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-cosmetic-case-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="cosmetic case">cosmetic case</a> that covers all three at once, and has extra space to store hair ties and clips, is a one-stop-shop that streamlines your packing process. Knowing <a href="https://beistravel.com/blogs/news/hacks-for-how-to-pack-toiletries-and-makeup" title="how to pack toiletries and makeup">how to pack toiletries and makeup</a> can be big challenge but you'll become an expert in no time.</p>
<br>
<h2>#10 Jewelry Case</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Jewelry_Case_large.jpg?v=1591276509" alt=""></p>
<p>The last essential travel item is a bag to store all your jewelry. A <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-hanging-jewelry-case" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="hanging jewelry organizer">hanging jewelry organizer</a> lets you look at all your options at once, and gives your necklaces enough space to hang without getting tangled during travel.</p>
<br>
<h2>#11 DIY Disinfecting Kit</h2>
<p>Did you know that if someone sitting near you on a flight is sick, you have an 80% chance of getting it too? According to <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/getting-sick-on-an-airplane-flight-2018-3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Business Insider’s report</a> on the study, the window seat is the safest place to be. But with people getting up during the flight and not knowing who sat there before you, the risk is unavoidable.</p>
<p>To stay as healthy as possible your travel packing list should include a small bag with the following items:</p>
<ul>
<li>Disinfecting wipes to clean your tray table</li>
<li>Mini disinfectant spray for soft surfaces like seats</li>
<li>Hand sanitizer to use before you eat</li>
</ul>
<br>
<h2>#12 Universal Travel Adapter</h2>
<p>As a savvy traveler you should get a worldwide all-in-one travel adapter so you’re prepared no matter where your travels take you. Something to be mindful of: universal adapters work in most countries, but not all, so be sure to research the plugs and voltage of wherever you’re headed.</p>
<br>
<h2>#13 Insulated Jacket</h2>
<p>You might think that travel essentials for women going to a warmer climate wouldn’t include a down jacket. But down jackets actually have a huge range of fill density, making them perfect for a breezy night at the beach—plus, they take up way less space than even a knit cardigan would.</p>
<br>
<h2>#14 Silk or Satin Pillowcase</h2>
<p>Typical pillowcases can cause friction that frizzes hair and breaks down the youthful properties of the skin. Still, it’s thought (although not scientifically proven) that silk and satin pillowcases keep your hair silky and skin glowing. Bringing a pillowcase along with you means you’ll be safe from allergens like dust mites, and not have to worry about sensitive skin acting up. There are tons of brands with rave reviews, so you’ll be sure to find one within your price range. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span data-slate-leaf="true">P.S. Don't forget your </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">sleep mask</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"> and </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">noise cancelling </span><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">headphones </span>especially if you're enjoying </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">international </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">travel</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyUC5TLiUyMERvbid0JTIwZm9yZ2V0JTIweW91ciUyMHNsZWVwJTIwbWFzayUyMGVzcGVjaWFsbHklMjBpZiUyMHlvdSdyZSUyMGVuam95aW5nJTIwaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCUyMHRyYXZlbCElMjIlN0QlNUQlMkMlMjJ0eXBlJTIyJTNBJTIycGFyYWdyYXBoJTIyJTdEJTVE">!</span></p>
<br>
<h2>#15 Sunglasses</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0032/3423/4479/files/Sunglasses_large.png?v=1591276450" alt=""></p>
<p>Some people say you should have a cheap pair of sunglasses for traveling, but you should always prioritize your eyesight especially when going on a sunny tropical vacation. If your sunglasses don’t guarantee 100% UVA/UVB protection, and at least a category two sunglass category (meaning there’s medium glare protection), you don’t want to be wearing them. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span data-slate-leaf="true">There are plenty of affordable, quality sunglasses you can get to protect your eyes and match your </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">travel</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> outfit</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyVGhlcmUlMjBhcmUlMjBwbGVudHklMjBvZiUyMGFmZm9yZGFibGUlMkMlMjBxdWFsaXR5JTIwc3VuZ2xhc3NlcyUyMHlvdSUyMGNhbiUyMGdldCUyMHRvJTIwcHJvdGVjdCUyMHlvdXIlMjBleWVzJTIwYW5kJTIwbWF0Y2glMjB5b3VyJTIwdHJhdmVsJTIwb3V0Zml0LiUyMiU3RCU1RCUyQyUyMnR5cGUlMjIlM0ElMjJwYXJhZ3JhcGglMjIlN0QlNUQ=">.</span></p>
<h2>Travel Tips</h2>
<p>Say goodbye to stress and hello to stylish travel. These travel essentials for women are perfect for any vacation, no matter where you’re going, for how long, or what time of year it is. These 15 stylish and practical must-haves will change your traveling experience for the better—you won’t even remember what it was like to stress about packing essentials for your next trip. <span data-slate-leaf="true">Don't forget to add these items to your </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">travel</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> checklist</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyRG9uJ3QlMjBmb3JnZXQlMjB0byUyMGFkZCUyMHRoZXNlJTIwaXRlbXMlMjB0byUyMHlvdXIlMjB0cmF2ZWwlMjBjaGVja2xpc3QhJTIyJTdEJTVEJTJDJTIydHlwZSUyMiUzQSUyMnBhcmFncmFwaCUyMiU3RCU1RA==">!</span></p>
<p>And for that last part, there’s us. Whether you need a travel <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-backpack-in-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">backpack</a> or other small bag to hold your wallet, lip balm, flip flops, leggings, eye mask, neck pillow, or any other travel essentials you can think of, BÈIS has you covered. Check out our website to view all <a href="https://beistravel.com/collections/bags" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">travel bag</a>, checked luggage and carry on luggage collections and other essential travel items. <span data-slate-leaf="true">Some of our favorites for a frequent traveler include the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">luggage</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic"> set</span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant">the </span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">duffle </span></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">bag</span></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, the </span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">garment </span></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 iOyhdl highlight--variant"><span class="getHighlights__Term-sc-1s71y2o-0 bOHVYF highlight--related-topic">bag</span></span></span><span data-slate-leaf="true">, and the <a href="https://beistravel.com/products/the-messenger">black messenger bag</a></span><span data-slate-leaf="true" data-slate-fragment="JTVCJTdCJTIyY2hpbGRyZW4lMjIlM0ElNUIlN0IlMjJ0ZXh0JTIyJTNBJTIyU29tZSUyMG9mJTIwb3VyJTIwZmF2b3JpdGVzJTIwaW5jbHVkZSUyMHRoZSUyMGx1Z2dhZ2UlMjBzZXQlMkMlMjB0aGUlMjBkdWZmbGUlMjBiYWclMkMlMjB0aGUlMjBnYXJtZW50JTIwYmFnJTJDJTIwYW5kJTIwdGhlJTIwbWVzc2VuZ2VyJTIwYmFnLiUyMCUyMiU3RCU1RCUyQyUyMnR5cGUlMjIlM0ElMjJwYXJhZ3JhcGglMjIlN0QlNUQ=">.</span></p>
<br>
<p><b>Sources: </b></p>
<ol>
<li>PC Mag. <i>The Best Portable Chargers and Power Banks for 2020</i>. <a href="https://www.pcmag.com/news/the-best-portable-chargers-and-power-banks-for-2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.pcmag.com/news/the-best-portable-chargers-and-power-banks-for-2020</a>
</li>
<li>Business Insider. <i>Airplane passengers have an 80% chance of getting sick on a flight if they sit in the wrong spot, scientists have found</i>. <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/getting-sick-on-an-airplane-flight-2018-3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.businessinsider.com/getting-sick-on-an-airplane-flight-2018-3</a>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
